{"index": 0, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl was a member of independent politician, which political party did Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Denmark Democrats - Inger St\u00f8jberg in October 24, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Party of Communists of the Republic of Moldova in January 18, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Istiqlal Party in May 23, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Pro Patria Union in June 18, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Communist Party of Germany in December, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Liberals in March 11, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Alliance for the Union of Romanians in November, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the independent politician in March 11, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Liberal Party in January 18, 2019.", "Emma Carlsson L\u00f6fdahl is a member of the Vox in July, 2019."], "answer": ["Liberals"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 1, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Thomas Wenski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Thomas Wenski during the same time period?", "facts": ["Thomas Wenski holds the position of President of Vietnam from 1999 to 2001.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of Director of the Federal Security Service in May, 1999.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of Deputy President of the Supreme Court of the United Kingdom in November, 2002.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of titular bishop in June 24, 1997.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Employment from November, 2004 to December, 2004.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of Head of the Security Service of Ukraine in April 13, 1999.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 3, 1997.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 24, 1997.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of Minister for Children (Denmark) in June 2, 1998.", "Thomas Wenski holds the position of diocesan bishop in November 13, 2004."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 2, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Marie-Daniel Dadiet was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Marie-Daniel Dadiet simultaneously?", "facts": ["Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 22, 1998.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of diocesan bishop in October 10, 2002.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 11, 1998.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of Grand Master of the Teutonic Knights from March 4, 2001 to September 4, 2001.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Energy and Climate Change from October 5, 1999 to November 14, 1999.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of titular bishop in May 22, 1998.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of President of the Chamber of Deputies of Romania in March 10, 1998.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of hegumen in 2002.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of Secretary-General of the State Council in July, 1998.", "Marie-Daniel Dadiet holds the position of Chairman of the Chiefs of Staff Committee from April, 2001 to November, 2002."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 3, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jacob Muricken was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jacob Muricken during the same time period?", "facts": ["Jacob Muricken holds the position of Beyer Chair of Applied Mathematics in October, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of titular bishop in August 24, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 24, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 1, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of state attorney general in December 24, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of State Secretary in March, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of Governor of Louisiana in October 8, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of Secretary General of the Council of Europe in September 16, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of President of the Principality of Asturias in May 24, 2012.", "Jacob Muricken holds the position of Solicitor General of the United States in November, 2012."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 4, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Simon Pimenta was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Simon Pimenta at the same time?", "facts": ["Simon Pimenta holds the position of titular bishop in June 5, 1971.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Minister for Public Health from August 19, 1972 to February 28, 1985.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 5, 1971.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 29, 1971.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Minister for the Climate (Sweden) from July 25, 1975 to September 25, 1983.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Minister for Youth (New South Wales) in February, 1985.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Head of the Prime Minister's military cabinet from 1987 to 1988.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Governor of Tasmania from July, 1976 to September, 1978.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of Lord Keeper of the Great Seal in 1975.", "Simon Pimenta holds the position of cardinal in June 28, 1988."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 5, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Decio Azzolino was holding the position of Catholic bishop, which position did Decio Azzolino at the same time?", "facts": ["Decio Azzolino holds the position of leader in June 6, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of cardinal in December 18, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of deputy in January 14, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 15, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of Minister for Gaelic in August 24, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of President of Turkey in August 18, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of Governor of North Carolina in February, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of Mayor of Minneapolis in October, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of diocesan bishop in November 15, 1585.", "Decio Azzolino holds the position of Governor of Vermont in April 13, 1585."], "answer": ["diocesan bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 6, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Erasmus Perchinger was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Erasmus Perchinger during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of Prime Minister of Malta in August 28, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of Governor of Tasmania in November 11, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of member of the Australian Capital Territory Legislative Assembly in February 26, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of heir apparent in October, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of Leader of Opposition in May, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of titular bishop in November 6, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 6, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 18, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of the Republic of Poland in January 3, 1482.", "Erasmus Perchinger holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand in January, 1482."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 7, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong during the same time span?", "facts": ["Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of President of Guinea in 1978.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Indiana in February, 1979.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of President of Serbia from February, 2005 to August, 2005.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 25, 1977.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of Minister for Enterprise and Lifelong Learning from December 18, 1997 to May 22, 1998.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of secretary from October 3, 1988 to August 17, 2000.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 3, 1977.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of titular bishop in February 3, 1977.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of Secretary of State for Northern Ireland from 1998 to 2001.", "Joseph Kyeong Kap-ryong holds the position of diocesan bishop from July 2, 1984 to April 1, 2005."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 8, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While William Levada was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did William Levada during the same time period?", "facts": ["William Levada holds the position of First Deputy Chairman of the Government of the Russian Federation from January, 2005 to July, 2005.", "William Levada holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 12, 1983.", "William Levada holds the position of theatre manager from 2004 to 2005.", "William Levada holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 25, 1983.", "William Levada holds the position of President of South Africa in 1992.", "William Levada holds the position of European Commissioner for Competition from July, 2005 to September, 2005.", "William Levada holds the position of titular bishop in March 25, 1983.", "William Levada holds the position of Republican Party from September, 2003 to May, 2006.", "William Levada holds the position of cardinal in March 24, 2006.", "William Levada holds the position of Minister of Small Business and Tourism in 2002."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 9, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Gerhard Schaffran was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Gerhard Schaffran concurrently?", "facts": ["Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of Amir al-Mu'minin from 1985 to 1986.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of Secretary of the Interior and Local Government in August 21, 1985.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 24, 1962.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of titular bishop in November 24, 1962.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of Cathaoirleach from April 23, 1971 to June 23, 1972.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of diocesan bishop from 1970 to August 1, 1987.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of United States Ambassador to Mexico from 1966 to 1976.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of Chancellery of the President of the Republic of Poland in 1974.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 22, 1963.", "Gerhard Schaffran holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Work and Pensions in September, 1974."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 10, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Verran was a member of Australian Labor Party (South Australian Branch), which political party did John Verran belong to concurrently?", "facts": ["John Verran is a member of the Party of Democratic Socialism in 1910.", "John Verran is a member of the Australian Labor Party (South Australian Branch) in June 28, 1917.", "John Verran is a member of the National Party in June 28, 1917.", "John Verran is a member of the Politics Can Be Different from September 25, 1919 to November 26, 1928.", "John Verran holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from August 30, 1927 to November 16, 1928.", "John Verran is a member of the Czech National Social Party from 1925 to 1926.", "John Verran is a member of the Kadima from May 24, 1921 to November 26, 1926.", "John Verran is a member of the British Socialist Party in June 24, 1924.", "John Verran holds the position of Minister of Public Works from June 3, 1910 to February 17, 1912.", "John Verran is a member of the Australian Labor Party in June 28, 1917."], "answer": ["Australian Labor Party", "National Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 11, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Joseph James Keane was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Patrick Joseph James Keane simultaneously?", "facts": ["Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of Chief of Staff of the French Navy from April, 1922 to May, 1922.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of curator from July 17, 1922 to August 18, 1922.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of Chairman of the Council of People's Commissars from April 26, 1922 to August 26, 1922.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of titular bishop in September 10, 1920.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of United States Permanent Representative to NATO in 1922.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 10, 1920.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of President of the European Parliament from October 16, 1921 to November 25, 1921.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 4, 1920.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of diocesan bishop in March 17, 1922.", "Patrick Joseph James Keane holds the position of Speaker of the Supreme Council of Kyrgyzstan from September 8, 1922 to October 25, 1922."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 12, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Gustavo Oscar Carrara was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Gustavo Oscar Carrara during the same time period?", "facts": ["Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of President of Georgia in July, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of Minister for Economic Affairs in May, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 16, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Oxfordshire in February, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of titular bishop in November 20, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of defence minister in May, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of Minister of Climate and the Environment in July, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of Chief Minister of Punjab in December, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 20, 2017.", "Gustavo Oscar Carrara holds the position of Federal Bureau of Investigation in September 7, 2017."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 13, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Cheryl Kernot was a member of Australian Democrats, which political party did Cheryl Kernot belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Cheryl Kernot is a member of the People's Movement Party in April 18, 1994.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the Liberal Conservative Reformers in 1994.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the Christian Democratic People's Party in 1990.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the New Hope in August, 1994.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the Polish People's Party \"Piast\" in November, 1992.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the New Azerbaijan Party from October 9, 1991 to January 24, 1994.", "Cheryl Kernot holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from July 1, 1990 to October 15, 1997.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the Australian Labor Party in October 15, 1997.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the Australian Democrats in October 15, 1997.", "Cheryl Kernot is a member of the Freedom Movement in July, 1993."], "answer": ["Australian Labor Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 14, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While William Anthony Hughes was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did William Anthony Hughes during the identical time period?", "facts": ["William Anthony Hughes holds the position of President of Georgia in May, 1991.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of titular bishop in July 23, 1974.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of Speaker of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly in November 10, 1985.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 23, 1974.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of United States Attorney from 1980 to 1989.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of Attorney General of California in 1992.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 12, 1974.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of Speaker of the Knesset from August 25, 1985 to June 27, 1993.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of diocesan bishop from April 13, 1979 to July 4, 1995.", "William Anthony Hughes holds the position of Regius Professor of Botany in 1979."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 15, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Chen Li-chen was a member of independent politician, which political party did Chen Li-chen belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Chen Li-chen is a member of the Democratic Progressive Party in March 30, 2003.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the Reiwa Shinsengumi in 2004.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the independent politician in March 30, 2003.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the United Development Party from 2004 to 2005.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the Alliance for the Union of Romanians in December, 2003.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the National Alliance Party in October, 2005.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the Christian Democracy from July 22, 2004 to September 26, 2004.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the Denmark Democrats - Inger St\u00f8jberg in 2004.", "Chen Li-chen is a member of the Socialist People's Party of Montenegro in August, 2005.", "Chen Li-chen holds the position of Mayor of Chiayi from December 20, 2001 to December 20, 2005."], "answer": ["Democratic Progressive Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 16, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Yael Dowker was working for Massachusetts Institute of Technology, which employer did Yael Dowker work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Yael Dowker worked for Billund Airport in February 24, 1947.", "Yael Dowker works for Massachusetts Institute of Technology from 1943 to 1946.", "Yael Dowker worked for University of Lyon in January, 1947.", "Yael Dowker worked for Kamerny Theatre from April 17, 1949 to April 19, 1950.", "Yael Dowker attended Radcliffe College in 1948.", "Yael Dowker worked for United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit in December 14, 1951.", "Yael Dowker worked for The Sun from May 23, 1947 to May 28, 1950.", "Yael Dowker worked for Scripps Research from 1950 to 1951.", "Yael Dowker works for University of Manchester in 1951.", "Yael Dowker works for Radiation Laboratory from 1943 to 1946."], "answer": ["Radiation Laboratory"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 17, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of diocesan bishop from May 2, 1985 to June 15, 2007.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs from April, 2005 to December, 2005.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of Minister of Democracy in September 20, 1991.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Defense from 1977 to 2007.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Safeguarding from 1985 to 1995.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 6, 1975.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of titular bishop in May 30, 1975.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 30, 1975.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of Minister of Road Transport and Highways from March, 1987 to November, 2004.", "Hugolino Cerasuolo Stacey holds the position of Minister of Justice and Attorney General of Canada in March, 1992."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 18, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Theodor Riphaen was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Theodor Riphaen simultaneously?", "facts": ["Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 3, 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 30, 1606.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Minister of State for Communities and Local Government from August 5, 1607 to December 19, 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Canada in January 24, 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Monarch of Norway in 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Secretary for the Civil Service from July, 1607 to August, 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Principal Private Secretary to the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs in July 28, 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of President of the King's Privy Council for Canada in May 10, 1607.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of titular bishop in August 30, 1606.", "Theodor Riphaen holds the position of Deputy Premier of South Australia in March 5, 1606."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 19, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luciano Bux was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Luciano Bux during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Luciano Bux holds the position of Minister for International Development from January, 2008 to March, 2011.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand from 1996 to 2001.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 25, 1995.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of Lord Mayor of Dublin from 2004 to 2008.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of Deputy Premier of New South Wales from January 2, 1999 to April 19, 2010.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of titular bishop in January 21, 1995.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of diocesan bishop from February 5, 2000 to July 2, 2011.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Bath and Wells from July, 1996 to July, 2010.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 21, 1995.", "Luciano Bux holds the position of Secretary of State for Dominion Affairs from September, 2010 to May, 2011."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 20, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While \u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did \u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 during the identical time period?", "facts": ["\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Administrator of the Small Business Administration in November 23, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 5, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Governor of British Ceylon in August 5, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 5, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of wing commander in January, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Shadow Chief Secretary to the Treasury in September 25, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Lord Chamberlain in September, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of titular bishop in July 5, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development in June, 1996.", "\u0110uro Ga\u0161parovi\u0107 holds the position of Minister for Youth and Sports in November 10, 1996."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 21, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Frank Henry Greteman was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Frank Henry Greteman within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Shadow Foreign Secretary from November, 1981 to February, 1983.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Bedfordshire in November, 1976.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 26, 1965.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of titular bishop in April 14, 1965.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of diocesan bishop from October 15, 1970 to August 17, 1983.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Leader of the Opposition of Australia in October, 1970.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 14, 1965.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Warsaw City Council from April 12, 1969 to June 13, 1977.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Dean of Windsor in March 13, 1967.", "Frank Henry Greteman holds the position of Minister of Economic Affairs from 1966 to 1974."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 22, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Norbert Strotmann was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Norbert Strotmann concurrently?", "facts": ["Norbert Strotmann holds the position of Governor-General of Tuvalu from 1994 to 1997.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of titular bishop in December 19, 1992.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport from January, 1994 to June, 1996.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of diocesan bishop in January 11, 1997.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of Minister of Culture of Denmark from 1995 to 1996.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 6, 1993.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of town supervisor in October, 1994.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of Chancellery of the President of the Republic of Poland in April, 1995.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of Governor of Maine from March 14, 1993 to April 21, 1997.", "Norbert Strotmann holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 19, 1992."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 23, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Willem Aantjes was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Willem Aantjes belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Willem Aantjes is a member of the New Power Party from May 20, 1969 to January 27, 1978.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the Democracy Is Freedom \u2013 The Daisy from December 14, 1959 to November 24, 1964.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the The Olive Tree from July 10, 1958 to May 17, 1966.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the FRELIMO from July, 1960 to November, 1965.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the Greek Solution from February, 1948 to December, 1959.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the Fine Gael in June 17, 1973.", "Willem Aantjes attended Utrecht University from September 10, 1945 to July 10, 1952.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the Anti-Revolutionary Party in October 11, 1980.", "Willem Aantjes is a member of the Patto Segni in 1977."], "answer": ["Anti-Revolutionary Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 24, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 21, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State in October 8, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of Minister for Finance of Australia in May 3, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of Chief of Staff of the French Army in June 26, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of White House Press Secretary in July, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 8, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of High Commissioner for Palestine and Transjordan in February 21, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of titular bishop in January 8, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of Regius Professor of Botany in November 18, 1652.", "Rodrigo Cruzado Caballero holds the position of Minister of Justice in March, 1652."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 25, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Angelo Di Pietro was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Angelo Di Pietro concurrently?", "facts": ["Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of treasurer general from February 11, 1880 to October 17, 1893.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of titular bishop in June 25, 1866.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of Cloistered Emperor in 1879.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 1, 1866.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of Florida Commissioner of Agriculture in July 19, 1885.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of cardinal in January 16, 1893.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of Minister for the Union from February 28, 1890 to February 28, 1891.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 25, 1866.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of Vice President of the Federative Republic of Brazil from 1891 to 1893.", "Angelo Di Pietro holds the position of Camerlengo of the Sacred College of Cardinals from 1895 to 1896."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 26, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Teofilius Matulionis was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Teofilius Matulionis during the same time span?", "facts": ["Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 8, 1928.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 9, 1929.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs in January, 1928.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of Speaker of the Senate in 1929.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of solicitor from August 7, 1929 to November 19, 1929.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of European Commissioner for the Environment in December, 1929.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of Secretary of State for Justice in January 23, 1928.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of titular bishop in December 8, 1928.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of Minister for Institutional Reforms in June 12, 1928.", "Teofilius Matulionis holds the position of Minister of Public Services and Procurement in April 15, 1928."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 27, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Stephen Lee was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Stephen Lee during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Stephen Lee holds the position of Minister-President of Flanders in July 28, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 11, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of United States Ambassador-at-Large for International Religious Freedom in May, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of titular bishop in July 11, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of President of Zimbabwe in October, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of Mayor of Richmond, Virginia in January 23, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of Military District Commander in August, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 30, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of mayor of Cape Town in August, 2014.", "Stephen Lee holds the position of director of communications in February 21, 2014."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 28, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Sylvester Horton Rosecrans was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Sylvester Horton Rosecrans during the same time period?", "facts": ["Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of United States Ambassador to Lithuania from February, 1865 to November, 1865.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of diocesan bishop in March 3, 1868.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of member of the European Parliament from February, 1863 to February, 1866.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of Governor of Victoria from September 2, 1865 to December 11, 1866.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of Secretary of State of Texas from March, 1867 to February, 1868.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 25, 1862.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of Minister responsible for the Francophonie from July, 1868 to September, 1868.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 7, 1862.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of titular bishop in January 7, 1862.", "Sylvester Horton Rosecrans holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs in October 23, 1864."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 29, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Fabio Betancur Tirado was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Fabio Betancur Tirado during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of titular bishop in May 24, 1982.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of President of Romania in September 27, 1983.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 24, 1982.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of President of Estonia in September, 1982.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of Minister for Agriculture from August 1, 1984 to September 18, 1984.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of Foreign Service officer in 1983.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of Vice Chief of Army Staff in March, 1983.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of Governor of Maine from September, 1984 to December, 1984.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of diocesan bishop in March 29, 1984.", "Fabio Betancur Tirado holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 3, 1982."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 30, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana simultaneously?", "facts": ["Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of chief of police in March, 2007.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of Prince of Wales from January 2, 2010 to September 16, 2010.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Jordan in 2010.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of Minister for Youth in September 13, 2010.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of District Judge from 2010 to 2011.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of diocesan bishop in December 30, 2011.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of Landesrabbiner in July, 2009.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 24, 2006.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 2, 2006.", "Oscar Vicente Ojea Quintana holds the position of titular bishop in May 24, 2006."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 31, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jean Kockerols was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jean Kockerols within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Jean Kockerols holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 3, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of Minister of State for Schools and Childhood in August 15, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of Prime Minister of Malaysia in April, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of President of Brazil in October, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of State Councilor of the People's Republic of China in February 3, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of Deputy Assistant Secretary in February 3, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 22, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of Menteris Besar of Selangor in August 6, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of Cabinet Secretary in November, 2011.", "Jean Kockerols holds the position of titular bishop in February 22, 2011."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 32, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Bob Such was a member of Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division), which political party did Bob Such belong to concurrently?", "facts": ["Bob Such is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia in October 12, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the New Alliance in July 4, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division) in October 12, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the independent politician in October 12, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the New Hope in March, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Finnish Rural Party in May, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Union for French Democracy in May, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Tahya Tounes in April 22, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Unionist Party in June, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Catalan European Democratic Party in January 15, 2000."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Australia", "independent politician"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 33, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Edward Vardon was a member of Liberal Union, which political party did Edward Vardon belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Edward Vardon is a member of the United Australia Party in September, 1925.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Jacqui Lambie Network from October 26, 1927 to February 26, 1930.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Liberal and Country League of South Australia in 1930.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the National Coalition Party Pro Patria in May 2, 1928.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Communist Party of Czechoslovakia in December 13, 1927.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Alliance of Liberals and Democrats Party in October 14, 1925.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Democratic Federal Republican Party from January 27, 1927 to June 27, 1928.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the One NL in September, 1925.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Liberal Federation in October 16, 1923.", "Edward Vardon is a member of the Liberal Union in October 16, 1923."], "answer": ["Liberal Federation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 34, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Aurore Berg\u00e9 was a member of The Republicans, which political party did Aurore Berg\u00e9 belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Ecuadorian Roldosist Party in February 25, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Russian People's Democratic Union in July, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 holds the position of spokesperson in June 27, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Estonian Centre Party in September 2, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Renaissance in February 1, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Spanish Communist Workers' Party in May 25, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the The Republicans in February 1, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Danish People's Party in September, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in December, 2017.", "Aurore Berg\u00e9 is a member of the New Party in June, 2017."], "answer": ["Renaissance"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 35, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni was working for University of Michigan, which employer did Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni works for Georgia Institute of Technology from 2007 to 2008.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for John F. Kennedy in 2009.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni works for University of Michigan from 2007 to 2008.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for Liverpool John Moores University from November, 2012 to December, 2012.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni works for TU Dresden in 2012.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for Gakushuin University in 2009.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for Peabody Institute from November 20, 2011 to April 26, 2012.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for New York University School of Law from January, 2009 to July, 2012.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for Penn State Milton S. Hershey Medical Center in February, 2012.", "Andr\u00e9s Fabi\u00e1n Lasagni worked for Becker College from November, 2011 to November, 2012."], "answer": ["Georgia Institute of Technology"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 36, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Basil H. Losten was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Basil H. Losten concurrently?", "facts": ["Basil H. Losten holds the position of First Secretary of the Georgian Communist Party from July, 1985 to June, 1995.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of Minister for Labour from June 6, 1978 to March 7, 1994.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of titular bishop in March 15, 1971.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Singapore in 1988.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of Minister of State for Children in 1977.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 25, 1971.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of diocesan bishop from September 20, 1977 to January 3, 2006.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 15, 1971.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of Minister of Finance of Sri Lanka from March 19, 1998 to November 21, 1999.", "Basil H. Losten holds the position of Lord Chancellor of France in July, 1991."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 37, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ioan Suciu was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Ioan Suciu during the same time span?", "facts": ["Ioan Suciu holds the position of President of Venezuela in August, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of President of the United Nations General Assembly in March, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of abbot in October 16, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of Lord Chancellor of France in January 16, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Cornwall in October, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of Bishop of Blackburn in April 3, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 25, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of treasurer in October 1, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 22, 1940.", "Ioan Suciu holds the position of titular bishop in May 25, 1940."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 38, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Durk van der Mei was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Durk van der Mei belong to concurrently?", "facts": ["Durk van der Mei is a member of the Eusko Alkartasuna in April 12, 1980.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the National Labor Party in 1978.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Communist Party of India from July 13, 1977 to June 23, 1978.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Alternative for Germany in January 1, 1977.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Kulanu in 1976.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Colombian Liberal Party in July 16, 1976.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Croatian Democratic Union from 1978 to 1979.", "Durk van der Mei is a member of the Christian Historical Union in October 11, 1980.", "Durk van der Mei holds the position of member of the European Parliament from March 9, 1976 to December 30, 1977."], "answer": ["Christian Historical Union"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 39, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Minister for Gender Equality Affairs in July, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 19, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 24, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Cabinet Secretary for Infrastructure, Investment and Cities in November, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of titular bishop in May 24, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Governor of Queensland in May 22, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Governor of Zaporizhzhia Oblast in October 10, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Defence in September, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Minister for Institutional Reforms in October, 2006.", "Broderick Soncuaco Pabillo holds the position of Mayor of Taoyuan in January, 2006."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 40, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Edwin Michael Conway was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Edwin Michael Conway during the same time span?", "facts": ["Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 20, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of President of Guyana in June 7, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of duke in August 7, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Azerbaijan in April, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of Minister of Water and Sanitation in May, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of Associate Minister of Finance in December, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of Minister for Defence Materiel in September 10, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of President of Afghanistan in June 3, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 24, 1995.", "Edwin Michael Conway holds the position of titular bishop in January 24, 1995."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 41, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington was holding the position of Lord Privy Seal, which position did Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington during the same time period?", "facts": ["Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of United States Permanent Representative to NATO in January 17, 1998.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Prime Minister of Cuba in May, 1998.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Lord Privy Seal from July 27, 1998 to June 8, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development in May, 1998.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of President of the Republic of Lithuania in December, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Vice Prime Minister of Georgia in February, 1998.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Leader of the House of Lords from July 27, 1998 to June 8, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Defence Secretary of Pakistan in September 9, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Veterans Affairs in November, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Minister for Women and Equalities from July 27, 1998 to June 8, 2001."], "answer": ["Minister for Women and Equalities", "Leader of the House of Lords"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 42, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While William Weathers was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did William Weathers during the identical time period?", "facts": ["William Weathers holds the position of seneschal in December, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of Resident Minister in October, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Michigan in February, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of President of Sri Lanka in November 16, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of titular bishop in September 27, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 27, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of New Brunswick in March, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of High Commissioner of the Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands in November, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of visiting scholar in December 27, 1872.", "William Weathers holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 28, 1872."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 43, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Charlie Crist was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Charlie Crist belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Charlie Crist attended Wake Forest University from 1974 to 1976.", "Charlie Crist is a member of the Rassemblement Bleu Marine in December, 1983.", "Charlie Crist is a member of the Indonesian Democratic Party \u2013 Struggle from November 21, 1984 to February 26, 1989.", "Charlie Crist is a member of the Parti lib\u00e9ral du Qu\u00e9bec from August, 1984 to April, 1995.", "Charlie Crist attended Florida State University in 1978.", "Charlie Crist attended Cumberland School of Law in 1981.", "Charlie Crist is a member of the Democratic Party in December 7, 2012.", "Charlie Crist is a member of the Republican Party in December 7, 2012.", "Charlie Crist holds the position of Florida Attorney General from 2003 to 2007.", "Charlie Crist is a member of the Freedom Union \u2013 Democratic Union in 1980."], "answer": ["Republican Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 44, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Moon Jae-in was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Moon Jae-in belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Moon Jae-in is a member of the Socialist Union of Popular Forces in 2019.", "Moon Jae-in holds the position of President of South Korea from May 10, 2017 to May 9, 2022.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the Democratic Party of Korea in March 26, 2014.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the National Christian Party from 2018 to 2019.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the Democratic Party in March 26, 2014.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the Liberal-Environmental Party from November, 2017 to November, 2019.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the Justice First in 2020.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the Green Left from June 7, 2015 to June 24, 2022.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the Ob\u010dansk\u00e9 hnut\u00ed from June, 2019 to April, 2020.", "Moon Jae-in is a member of the FRELIMO in 2016."], "answer": ["Democratic Party of Korea"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 45, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Johannes W\u00fcbbe was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Johannes W\u00fcbbe at the same time?", "facts": ["Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Minister for Integration in March, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 18, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 1, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Minister of State for Northern Ireland in May, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of President of the Republic of Lithuania in October, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Pakistan in April, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of titular bishop in June 18, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Prime Minister of Pakistan in July 10, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Minister for Local Government in June 4, 2013.", "Johannes W\u00fcbbe holds the position of Prime Minister of Cuba in April 22, 2013."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 46, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Walsh was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Patrick Walsh during the same time period?", "facts": ["Patrick Walsh holds the position of Governor-General of India from 2001 to 2006.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 15, 1983.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 6, 1983.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of United States Senate Democratic Conference Secretary in November 2, 1989.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from December 9, 1989 to March 26, 2004.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of Bishop of Down and Connor from March 18, 1991 to February 22, 2008.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of titular bishop in April 6, 1983.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of European Commissioner for Economy from July, 1995 to May, 1999.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of Crown Prince of Thailand in May 11, 2003.", "Patrick Walsh holds the position of King's Counsel from February 13, 1997 to October 17, 2008."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 47, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Carl Joseph Leiprecht was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Carl Joseph Leiprecht within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 7, 1948.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of List of archbishops of Gniezno and primates of Poland from October, 1965 to September, 1968.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of Finance Minister of Pakistan in July 4, 1959.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 30, 1948.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of Mayor of New York City in September 28, 1957.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of Mayor of Budapest in January, 1967.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of Chief of Staff of the French Army from March 24, 1955 to February 26, 1971.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of titular bishop in October 7, 1948.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of President of Armenia in April, 1957.", "Carl Joseph Leiprecht holds the position of diocesan bishop from June 21, 1949 to June 4, 1974."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 48, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Marco C\u00e9 was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Marco C\u00e9 during the same time span?", "facts": ["Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 22, 1970.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of titular bishop in April 22, 1970.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of Minister-President of Flanders from 1976 to 1981.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of cardinal from June 30, 1979 to January 5, 2002.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 17, 1970.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Suffolk in August 6, 1998.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of Bishop of Kingston from October, 1999 to November, 2000.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of Minister of Justice of Finland in April 9, 1972.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of patriarch of Venice from 1978 to 2002.", "Marco C\u00e9 holds the position of Auditor-General of New South Wales from 1987 to 1995."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 49, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n at the same time?", "facts": ["Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 27, 2003.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of the Cook Islands in 2009.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of President of the National Congress of Honduras from February, 2009 to August, 2012.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of Member of the National Assembly of Pakistan in 2009.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of Chief of Defence in February 27, 2015.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of titular bishop in November 30, 2015.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of employee in October, 2008.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of Chair of the Federal Reserve in August, 2004.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of diocesan bishop in May 14, 2003.", "Luis Albeiro Cort\u00e9s Rend\u00f3n holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 30, 2015."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 50, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Henryk Broder was working for Tagesspiegel, which employer did Henryk Broder work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Henryk Broder worked for DePatie\u2013Freleng Enterprises in June, 2011.", "Henryk Broder works for Tagesspiegel from 1995 to 2010.", "Henryk Broder worked for Academy of Sciences of the GDR in October 4, 2011.", "Henryk Broder worked for Baltic House Festival Theatre from June 23, 2011 to December 26, 2011.", "Henryk Broder worked for NBC from March, 2011 to November, 2011.", "Henryk Broder worked for Institute of Oriental Manuscripts of the Russian Academy of Sciences from February, 2011 to November, 2011.", "Henryk Broder works for Die Welt in 2011.", "Henryk Broder worked for Goldman Sachs & Co. (US) in 2011.", "Henryk Broder works for Der Spiegel from 1995 to 2010.", "Henryk Broder worked for Botanic Garden and Botanical Museum Berlin in February, 2011."], "answer": ["Der Spiegel"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 51, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Anil Couto was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Anil Couto within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Anil Couto holds the position of Vice President of the Philippines in December, 2005.", "Anil Couto holds the position of President pro tempore of the Senate of the Philippines in December, 2006.", "Anil Couto holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign Affairs from 2004 to 2006.", "Anil Couto holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 22, 2000.", "Anil Couto holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 11, 2001.", "Anil Couto holds the position of attach\u00e9 in 2001.", "Anil Couto holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Tech and the Digital Economy from September, 2007 to November, 2007.", "Anil Couto holds the position of titular bishop in December 22, 2000.", "Anil Couto holds the position of Alternate Prime Minister of Israel from February, 2003 to June, 2003.", "Anil Couto holds the position of diocesan bishop in February 24, 2007."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 52, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Henryk Tomasik was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Henryk Tomasik at the same time?", "facts": ["Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Minister for International Development Cooperation in December, 2021.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 21, 1992.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of titular bishop in November 21, 1992.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Secretary of State for War and the Colonies from November 5, 1994 to November 5, 2012.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of diocesan bishop from October 16, 2009 to January 4, 2021.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Australian Botanical Liaison Officer in June 25, 1994.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Vice-Chancellor of Germany in 2020.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of governor from 1995 to 2007.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 21, 1992.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of program director from April 1, 1996 to June 3, 2011."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 53, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Nikol Joseph Cauchi was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Nikol Joseph Cauchi within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of titular bishop in February 24, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Director of SVR in January 27, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of High Sheriff of Northumberland in March 18, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Vice-Chancellor of Germany in September, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Finnish Minister of Employment in November, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 9, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 24, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Mayor of New York City in December, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Minister for Climate Change and Energy Efficiency in August 22, 1967.", "Nikol Joseph Cauchi holds the position of Chairperson of the Democratic Progressive Party in July, 1967."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 54, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jeff Van Drew was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Jeff Van Drew belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Republican Party in December 19, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Ahora Madrid in March, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Estonian Centre Party in June, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Democratic Party in December 19, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Socialist Labour Party in March, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Nye Borgerlige in July 18, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Party of Labour of Albania in June, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Citizens' Movement for Democratic Action in March, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Hungarian Socialist Workers' Party in November, 2019.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the Yabloko in September 21, 2019."], "answer": ["Republican Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 55, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Verran was a member of Australian Labor Party, which political party did John Verran belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["John Verran is a member of the Batkivshchyna from September 26, 1916 to November 27, 1916.", "John Verran is a member of the Civic Platform in 1928.", "John Verran is a member of the Muslim League from August 4, 1919 to April 14, 1927.", "John Verran is a member of the People's Union from February 2, 1920 to August 26, 1926.", "John Verran is a member of the National Party in June 28, 1917.", "John Verran holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from August 30, 1927 to November 16, 1928.", "John Verran is a member of the Australian Labor Party (South Australian Branch) in June 28, 1917.", "John Verran is a member of the New Frontier Party from November 5, 1919 to February 28, 1925.", "John Verran holds the position of Minister of Public Works from June 3, 1910 to February 17, 1912.", "John Verran is a member of the Australian Labor Party in June 28, 1917."], "answer": ["Australian Labor Party (South Australian Branch)", "National Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 56, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Leon Wetma\u0144ski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Leon Wetma\u0144ski at the same time?", "facts": ["Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Minister of the Armed Forces in June, 1928.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of titular bishop in December 19, 1927.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Chief of the Secret Intelligence Service in November 16, 1927.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 19, 1927.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Leader of the Government in the Legislative Council in October 27, 1927.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Lord Chancellor of France in 1928.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Associate Minister of Finance from November 13, 1928 to November 18, 1928.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of President of the Senate of the Netherlands in August 15, 1927.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 22, 1928.", "Leon Wetma\u0144ski holds the position of Minister for Social Inclusion from January, 1928 to June, 1928."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 57, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Leif Blomberg was holding the position of Minister of Sports, which position did Leif Blomberg at the same time?", "facts": ["Leif Blomberg holds the position of chairperson from 1982 to 1993.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of First Minister of Scotland from 1988 to 1995.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Secretary of State for Air in April, 1988.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister for Consumer Affairs from March 22, 1996 to March 2, 1998.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of United States Ambassador to Denmark from 1983 to 1987.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of President of Myanmar from January, 1986 to November, 1993.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister for Rural Affairs in September, 1998.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of adjunct professor in August 18, 1989.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister of Sports from March 22, 1996 to March 2, 1998.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister for Integration from March 22, 1996 to March 2, 1998."], "answer": ["Minister for Integration", "Minister for Consumer Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 58, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Thomas Jerome Welsh was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Thomas Jerome Welsh at the same time?", "facts": ["Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of Marshal of the Realm in May, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of Illinois Attorney General in May, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 2, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 18, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of member of the Australian Senate in August 10, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of Brazilian state deputy in April, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of titular bishop in February 18, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Finance in June, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of member of the Lok Sabha in December 26, 1970.", "Thomas Jerome Welsh holds the position of Minister of Sport and Recreation in August, 1970."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 59, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Tabbetha Dobbins was working for Grambling State University, which employer did Tabbetha Dobbins work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Tabbetha Dobbins worked for Virginia Commonwealth University in 2004.", "Tabbetha Dobbins worked for Barr\u00e9 Studio from February, 2010 to August, 2010.", "Tabbetha Dobbins works for Louisiana Tech University in September 1, 2003.", "Tabbetha Dobbins worked for University of California, Riverside in July, 2003.", "Tabbetha Dobbins worked for Christ Church from December 19, 2004 to September 20, 2007.", "Tabbetha Dobbins worked for Cadena COPE in January, 2004.", "Tabbetha Dobbins worked for Istituto Superiore di Sanit\u00e0 in December 20, 2009.", "Tabbetha Dobbins worked for Platov South-Russian State Polytechnic University in February, 2004.", "Tabbetha Dobbins works for Rowan University in September 1, 2010.", "Tabbetha Dobbins works for Grambling State University in September 1, 2003."], "answer": ["Louisiana Tech University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 60, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John F. Du was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did John F. Du within the same time interval?", "facts": ["John F. Du holds the position of titular bishop in November 21, 1997.", "John F. Du holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 21, 1997.", "John F. Du holds the position of Prime Minister of Vietnam in 2000.", "John F. Du holds the position of mayor of Beijing in 2000.", "John F. Du holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 21, 2001.", "John F. Du holds the position of European Commissioner for Internal Market and Services in January 28, 1999.", "John F. Du holds the position of Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Arts, Heritage and Tourism in June 9, 2000.", "John F. Du holds the position of Minister for Labour in October 2, 2001.", "John F. Du holds the position of Minister of State for Defence Procurement from July 2, 1999 to December 5, 1999.", "John F. Du holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 6, 1998."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 61, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Meletie Covaci was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Meletie Covaci during the same time period?", "facts": ["Meletie Covaci holds the position of Military governor of Paris in March, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Minister for Finance and Economic Planning in March 2, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Regius Professor of History in September 10, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 16, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of titular bishop in September 16, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Italian Minister for the South and Territorial Cohesion in April, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of State Counsellor of Kazakhstan in February 22, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of list of governors of Trinidad and Tobago in November, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Premier of Quebec in December, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 16, 1748."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 62, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Nunziata was a member of independent politician, which political party did John Nunziata belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["John Nunziata is a member of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union from July, 1980 to March, 1984.", "John Nunziata attended Osgoode Hall Law School from 1977 to 1980.", "John Nunziata attended York University in 1977.", "John Nunziata is a member of the Liberal Party of Canada in April 21, 1996.", "John Nunziata is a member of the Sinistra Italiana in 1987.", "John Nunziata is a member of the Valencian Union in February 4, 1983.", "John Nunziata is a member of the independent politician in April 21, 1996.", "John Nunziata is a member of the Alliance of Free Democrats from June, 1982 to February, 1987.", "John Nunziata is a member of the African National Congress in 1995.", "John Nunziata is a member of the Brazil Union in December 3, 1996."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Canada"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 63, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Michael Joseph Savage was holding the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs, which position did Michael Joseph Savage during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Singapore in April, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Governor of \u0130stanbul in June, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister of Law and Justice of India in March 27, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister of State for Defence Procurement in December 13, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand from December 6, 1935 to March 27, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Secretary of State for Canada in August 10, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs from December 6, 1935 to March 27, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister of Justice in February 5, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development from December 6, 1935 to March 27, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of list of governors of Trinidad in October, 1935."], "answer": ["Minister for M\u0101ori Development", "Prime Minister of New Zealand"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 64, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 at the same time?", "facts": ["Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of Attorney General of Ireland in 1952.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of titular bishop in December 13, 1951.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of Chief of the General Staff (United Kingdom) from January 1, 1952 to April 20, 1952.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 13, 1952.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 13, 1951.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of Magistrate of Taipei County in November, 1951.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Employment in February, 1952.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of President pro tempore of the United States Senate in May, 1952.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of organizational founder from April, 1952 to October, 1952.", "Josip Pavli\u0161i\u0107 holds the position of Minister of Justice of Belgium from February, 1952 to May, 1952."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 65, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau was holding the position of Governor of the Banque de France, which position did Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau concurrently?", "facts": ["Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of private secretary from 1997 to 2000.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of president in November 1, 2015.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of Governor of the Banque de France in November 1, 2015.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of Special Envoy for Eurasian Energy in April 4, 2002.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau attended \u00c9cole nationale d'administration from 1982 to 1984.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of Confederate States Secretary of State in May, 2012.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of Ceann Comhairle from January, 1996 to December, 2014.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of aide-de-camp in 2014.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of pr\u00e9sident-directeur g\u00e9n\u00e9ral from 2003 to 2008.", "Fran\u00e7ois Villeroy de Galhau holds the position of Minister of Defence of Hungary in February 14, 1987."], "answer": ["president"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 66, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alexius Obabu Makozi was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Alexius Obabu Makozi at the same time?", "facts": ["Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of the Republic of C\u00f4te d'Ivoire in November, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of Minister of Justice in November, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 30, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of Secretary for the Civil Service in March, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of sports director in February 2, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of governor of Rio Grande do Sul in April 13, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of titular bishop in February 20, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 20, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of Fielden Chair of Pure Mathematics in September, 1971.", "Alexius Obabu Makozi holds the position of United States Ambassador to Chile in June 1, 1971."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 67, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Daniel Anthony Hart was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Daniel Anthony Hart within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 24, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of Minister for Social Security in January 5, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of monarch of Scotland in October 10, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of Secretary for Public Works in May, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of United States Ambassador to Afghanistan in October, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of Minister for Posts and Telegraphs in February, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 18, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development in December 11, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of Vicar General for the Vatican City State in September 2, 1976.", "Daniel Anthony Hart holds the position of titular bishop in August 24, 1976."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 68, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of list of governors of the Leeward Islands in 1981.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of Minister for Consumer Affairs in July 13, 1981.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of diocesan bishop in June 8, 1982.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs of Serbia in 1982.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of titular bishop in October 1, 1979.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 18, 1979.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of President of East Timor in September, 1980.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 1, 1979.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of Disney Professor of Archaeology in 1982.", "Emilio Og\u00f1\u00e9novich holds the position of Leader of the Seanad in January 19, 1979."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 69, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Stephen Robson was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Stephen Robson simultaneously?", "facts": ["Stephen Robson holds the position of titular bishop in May 8, 2012.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of diocesan bishop in December 11, 2013.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of White House Chief of Staff in June 3, 2012.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of lieutenant general from June, 2013 to December, 2013.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of head of state from August, 2013 to October, 2013.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 9, 2012.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of Minister of Corrections from November 23, 2013 to December 28, 2013.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 8, 2012.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of Minister of Innovation, Science and Industry in January 24, 2012.", "Stephen Robson holds the position of Minister for Transport (New South Wales) from November 7, 2013 to December 20, 2013."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 70, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Maximilian von Lingg was holding the position of Catholic bishop, which position did Maximilian von Lingg concurrently?", "facts": ["Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Monsignor in 1885.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Minister-President of Saxony-Anhalt from October 3, 1893 to December 12, 1897.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Mayor of San Diego in September 27, 1888.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Minister of State for Middle East and North Africa from June 26, 1896 to June 28, 1900.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Treasurer of Queensland from 1897 to 1900.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 20, 1902.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Minister for Housing, Planning and Local Government from 1894 to 1897.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of diocesan bishop in July 20, 1902.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Kansas State Treasurer in 1885.", "Maximilian von Lingg holds the position of Governor-general from August, 1901 to November, 1901."], "answer": ["diocesan bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 71, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Reginald Weaver was holding the position of Secretary for Public Works, which position did Reginald Weaver during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Reginald Weaver is a member of the Nationalist Party of Australia from 1917 to 1931.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the United Australia Party from 1931 to 1943.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the National Party of Australia \u2013 NSW from 1913 to 1917.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Secretary for Public Works from May 16, 1932 to February 10, 1935.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Minister for Mines from April 16, 1929 to November 3, 1930.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the Liberal Reform Party in 1913.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Leader of the Opposition from February 10, 1944 to November 12, 1945.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Minister for Forests from April 16, 1929 to November 3, 1930.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Speaker of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly from August 4, 1937 to May 27, 1941.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Minister for Health from May 16, 1932 to February 10, 1935.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia (New South Wales Division) in 1945."], "answer": ["Minister for Health"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 72, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo at the same time?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of Secretary of State for Justice in August, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of President of Germany in December 10, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of titular bishop in July 10, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 28, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of Prime Minister of Spain in March 8, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Canada in October, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 10, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of United States Ambassador to Azerbaijan in December 10, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of Minister for Building and Construction in July 23, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Carlos Melo holds the position of Attorney General of New York in September 11, 1991."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 73, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joseph Walsh was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Joseph Walsh within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Joseph Walsh holds the position of Minister of Defence of Peru in 1938.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of Prime Minister of Afghanistan in 1938.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of Duke of York in July, 1938.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 16, 1937.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of Attorney General of Maryland in June, 1938.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of Manager of Opposition Business in the House in November, 1938.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of titular bishop in December 16, 1937.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 2, 1938.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of President of Abkhazia in May, 1937.", "Joseph Walsh holds the position of Mayor of Christchurch in December 18, 1937."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 74, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joschka Fischer was holding the position of Vice-Chancellor of Germany, which position did Joschka Fischer simultaneously?", "facts": ["Joschka Fischer holds the position of Mayor of Christchurch in August 18, 1998.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Vice-Chancellor of Germany from October 27, 1998 to November 22, 2005.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Minister without portfolio of the Republic of Serbia in March 18, 1998.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Vice President of the Republic of China in June, 1998.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of President of Mauritius in May 13, 1998.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Chief of the General Staff (United Kingdom) in September, 1998.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Prime Minister of Iceland in December 4, 2005.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Federal Minister for Foreign Affairs from October 27, 1998 to November 22, 2005.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Bishop of Hull in August, 1998.", "Joschka Fischer holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice and Tackling Illegal Migration in December 18, 2005."], "answer": ["Federal Minister for Foreign Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 75, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Piet Steenkamp was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Piet Steenkamp belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Catholic People's Party in October 11, 1980.", "Piet Steenkamp attended Tilburg University in November, 1949.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Conservative Party in May, 1980.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Independent Workers' Party in 1975.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Indian National Congress in July 22, 1979.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the RENAMO in February 21, 1965.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Progressive Conservative Party of Canada in January 16, 1959.", "Piet Steenkamp holds the position of President of the Senate of the Netherlands from September 13, 1983 to June 11, 1991.", "Piet Steenkamp is a member of the Liberal Party of Canada in April, 1949."], "answer": ["Catholic People's Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 76, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While David William Valencia Antonio was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did David William Valencia Antonio at the same time?", "facts": ["David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of United States Ambassador to Argentina from February 2, 2015 to April 11, 2016.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of Magistrate of Miaoli County in December 27, 2012.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 26, 2011.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 15, 2011.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of diocesan bishop in November 14, 2018.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of Downing Street Chief of Staff from May 22, 2014 to December 24, 2018.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of Mayor of Montreal in April 16, 2012.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of Minister of Labour (France) from January 6, 2018 to March 10, 2018.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of Prime Minister of Croatia in April 10, 2011.", "David William Valencia Antonio holds the position of titular bishop in June 15, 2011."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 77, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Johannes Joachim Degenhardt was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Johannes Joachim Degenhardt within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Mayor of the City of Los Angeles from August, 1974 to May, 1976.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Northern Ireland in 1985.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of titular bishop in March 12, 1968.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 12, 1968.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Finnish Minister for European Affairs from 1993 to 1996.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of cardinal in January 28, 2001.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Commissioner of the British Antarctic Territory in April 16, 1990.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Minister for Trade in February 8, 1982.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs from January 2, 1970 to March 23, 1974.", "Johannes Joachim Degenhardt holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 1, 1968."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 78, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Andriy Rabiy was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Andriy Rabiy concurrently?", "facts": ["Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Rouse Ball Professor of Mathematics in February 23, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of vicar general in June, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Speaker of the Massachusetts House of Representatives in July, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Prime Minister of Somalia in July 20, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs of Serbia in February, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of titular bishop in August 8, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Prime Minister of Finland in January 7, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 3, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of Republican Conference Chairman of the United States Senate in December, 2017.", "Andriy Rabiy holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 8, 2017."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 79, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Lawrence Joyce Kenney was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Lawrence Joyce Kenney during the same time span?", "facts": ["Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 25, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic in February, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 10, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Minister of State for Europe in August 28, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of titular bishop in March 25, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Minister for Nordic Co-operation in October, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Prime Minister of Australia in April 27, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Development in November 16, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of United States Ambassador to Nigeria in June, 1983.", "Lawrence Joyce Kenney holds the position of Archbishop of Turku and Finland in August 10, 1983."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 80, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius concurrently?", "facts": ["Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of United States Ambassador to Morocco from September 7, 1987 to September 17, 1987.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 25, 1957.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of Indian state governor in 1973.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of titular bishop in November 14, 1957.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of Minister of Plantation and Commodities from February 8, 1968 to March 19, 1978.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 14, 1957.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of researcher from 1983 to 1988.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of board of supervisors from 1977 to 1983.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of cardinal in June 28, 1988.", "Vincentas Sladkevi\u010dius holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change in September 9, 1978."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 81, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Carl Romme was a member of Catholic People's Party, which political party did Carl Romme belong to during the same time period?", "facts": ["Carl Romme is a member of the Ecology Generation from June, 1947 to September, 1952.", "Carl Romme is a member of the Catholic People's Party in December 22, 1945.", "Carl Romme is a member of the Liberal Conservative Reformers in September, 1928.", "Carl Romme is a member of the New Centre-Right in April 13, 1932.", "Carl Romme is a member of the Roman Catholic State Party in December 22, 1945.", "Carl Romme attended University of Amsterdam from September, 1914 to October 28, 1919.", "Carl Romme holds the position of minister of state from December 16, 1971 to October 16, 1980.", "Carl Romme is a member of the Swedish Social Democratic Party in 1963.", "Carl Romme is a member of the For the People in 1949.", "Carl Romme is a member of the Europe Ecology \u2013 The Greens in July 16, 1925."], "answer": ["Roman Catholic State Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 82, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Francisco Manuel Vieira was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Francisco Manuel Vieira at the same time?", "facts": ["Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of President of Venezuela from October 23, 1979 to December 25, 1990.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of United States Attorney for the Southern District of New York from 1995 to 1996.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of titular bishop in December 12, 1974.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 15, 1989 to April 24, 2002.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of Plumian Professor of Astronomy and Experimental Philosophy in 1975.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 25, 1975.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of Attorney General of Uganda in June, 1983.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 12, 1974.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of President of the Los Angeles City Council in April 1, 1990.", "Francisco Manuel Vieira holds the position of Secretary of the State of Connecticut in March 24, 1996."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 83, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez was a member of Mover, which political party did Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Reform Party of Canada in September, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Citizen Revoluci\u00f3n Movement in January 16, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Democratic Labour Party in June 27, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Sustainability Network in September 26, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Democratic Party \u2013 demokraci.pl in October 20, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Mover in January 16, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Citizen and Republican Movement in November 15, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Popular Orthodox Rally in May, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Hungarian Communist Party in October 17, 2018.", "Luisa Gonz\u00e1lez is a member of the Liberal-Environmental Party in July 3, 2018."], "answer": ["Citizen Revoluci\u00f3n Movement"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 84, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 21, 1982.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 24, 1982.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of hegumen in February 23, 1983.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of Minister of Road Transport and Highways from March, 1987 to April, 1987.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of titular bishop in June 21, 1982.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of diocesan bishop in October 30, 1987.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of Minister of Human Settlements in July, 1987.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of Senior minister of Malaysia from September 9, 1987 to September 12, 1987.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of Magistrate of Pingtung County in February 10, 1982.", "Jos\u00e9 Palmeira Lessa holds the position of designated survivor in January 15, 1985."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 85, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Maria A. Pallante was working for Library of Congress, which employer did Maria A. Pallante work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Maria A. Pallante worked for Royal Observatory from April, 1997 to January, 2003.", "Maria A. Pallante worked for Credit Suisse from September, 1992 to June, 2000.", "Maria A. Pallante worked for Louisiana State University in June 15, 2000.", "Maria A. Pallante worked for Department of Scientific and Industrial Research in February 24, 1994.", "Maria A. Pallante works for United States Copyright Office in October 21, 2016.", "Maria A. Pallante worked for University of Nice Sophia Antipolis from 2003 to 2004.", "Maria A. Pallante worked for Shrewsbury School from 2000 to 2007.", "Maria A. Pallante attended George Washington University Law School in 1990.", "Maria A. Pallante holds the position of Register of Copyrights from June 1, 2011 to October 21, 2016.", "Maria A. Pallante works for Library of Congress in October 21, 2016."], "answer": ["United States Copyright Office"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 86, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Francisco Oves-Fernandez was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Francisco Oves-Fernandez concurrently?", "facts": ["Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of treasurer in June, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 25, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 16, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of President of Kosovo in March 6, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Vietnam in April 5, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of Bishop of Woolwich in July 5, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of Lowndean Professor of Astronomy and Geometry in September, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of Chief Secretary of South Australia in March, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of Governing Mayor of Berlin in November 23, 1969.", "Francisco Oves-Fernandez holds the position of titular bishop in April 25, 1969."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 87, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira concurrently?", "facts": ["Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of Vice President of Peru from 1965 to 1973.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of European Ombudsman from 1963 to 1971.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of Secretary of Education in 1964.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 29, 1961.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of Commandant General in Stockholm from September, 1969 to October, 1973.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of President pro tempore of the Senate of the Philippines in 1975.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of diocesan bishop in December 19, 1975.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of titular bishop in August 25, 1961.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 25, 1961.", "Ant\u00f4nio Ribeiro de Oliveira holds the position of Prime Minister of Abkhazia from 1969 to 1975."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 88, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Paolo Gentiloni was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Paolo Gentiloni belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the United Malays National Organisation from May, 2018 to January, 2019.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the Union of the Centre from September 5, 2018 to March 22, 2019.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the Democratic Party in October 14, 2007.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the Real Politics Union from April, 2018 to April, 2019.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the New Deal from July 18, 2016 to July 19, 2016.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the New Democratic Party from December 1, 2009 to May 28, 2015.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the Polish People's Party in April, 2012.", "Paolo Gentiloni holds the position of European Commissioner for Economy in December 1, 2019.", "Paolo Gentiloni is a member of the Democracy Is Freedom \u2013 The Daisy in October 14, 2007.", "Paolo Gentiloni holds the position of Prime Minister of Italy from December 12, 2016 to June 1, 2018."], "answer": ["Democracy Is Freedom \u2013 The Daisy"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 89, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alin Mitu\u021ba was a member of Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party, which political party did Alin Mitu\u021ba belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Industrial Labor Party in 2020.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the German Progress Party in April, 2022.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Bharatiya Jana Sangh in April, 2020.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Azerbaijan National Independence Party from April 25, 2020 to October 28, 2020.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Renewing Romania's European Project in May 31, 2022.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the National Harmony Party in December 2, 2020.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Serbian Democratic Party in October 11, 2022.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba holds the position of member of the European Parliament in December 28, 2020.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Hungarian Communist Party in November, 2022.", "Alin Mitu\u021ba is a member of the Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party in May 31, 2022."], "answer": ["Renewing Romania's European Project"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 90, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Oscar Sarlinga was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Oscar Sarlinga during the same time period?", "facts": ["Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 12, 2003.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of Minister of Employment and Immigration in September, 2005.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of diocesan bishop from February 3, 2006 to November 3, 2015.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of President of Ireland from September 26, 2005 to July 28, 2009.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of Attorney-General of South Australia from March, 2010 to March, 2013.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Denmark in November 8, 2004.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of Master of the Order of Preachers from November 19, 2006 to March 22, 2011.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 17, 2003.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of titular bishop in April 12, 2003.", "Oscar Sarlinga holds the position of United States Ambassador to Uganda from 2011 to 2013."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 91, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jacek Pyl was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jacek Pyl concurrently?", "facts": ["Jacek Pyl holds the position of Premier of Saskatchewan in March, 2013.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of burgomaster from April, 2013 to November, 2013.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 5, 2013.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of United States Poet Laureate in 2013.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of wissenschaftlicher Assistent in 2013.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 23, 2012.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of Commissioner of the British Antarctic Territory in May 3, 2012.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of titular bishop in November 23, 2012.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of United States Secretary of State in November 15, 2012.", "Jacek Pyl holds the position of Bishop of Wakefield in August 17, 2012."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 92, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Aslak Sira Myhre was a member of Red Electoral Alliance, which political party did Aslak Sira Myhre belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Red in March 11, 2007.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Catholic People's Party in 1997.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Party of the Democratic Left in November, 2001.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the League of Communists of Yugoslavia from September 7, 2001 to September 21, 2004.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Centre Agreement in February, 2005.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Brazilian Labour Renewal Party in April 18, 2005.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Red Electoral Alliance in March 11, 2007.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Territories of Progress in 2006.", "Aslak Sira Myhre is a member of the Democratic Coalition in September 27, 2000.", "Aslak Sira Myhre holds the position of party leader from 1997 to 2003."], "answer": ["Red"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 93, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Christopher Cardone was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Christopher Cardone during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Christopher Cardone holds the position of curate in August 9, 2002.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of titular bishop in March 27, 2001.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of Minister for Children and Youth Affairs in October, 2002.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of diocesan bishop in October 19, 2004.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of heir apparent from September 15, 2004 to October 16, 2004.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 9, 2001.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 27, 2001.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of Minister of Economic Affairs and Communications in February, 2001.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of bishop in 2004.", "Christopher Cardone holds the position of United States Ambassador to Chile in 2002."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 94, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Michal Wunsch was a member of Telem, which political party did Michal Wunsch belong to during the same time period?", "facts": ["Michal Wunsch is a member of the Telem in June 19, 2020.", "Michal Wunsch holds the position of Knesset member from June 19, 2020 to April 6, 2021.", "Michal Wunsch is a member of the Lang Labor in 1997.", "Michal Wunsch is a member of the Israel Resilience Party in June 19, 2020.", "Michal Wunsch attended Hebrew University of Jerusalem in 1996.", "Michal Wunsch is a member of the Katter's Australian Party from 2002 to 2003.", "Michal Wunsch attended McGill University from 2002 to 2006.", "Michal Wunsch is a member of the Yesh Atid in December, 2009.", "Michal Wunsch is a member of the Socialists' Party of Catalonia in September, 2019.", "Michal Wunsch is a member of the Agreement in March 6, 2000."], "answer": ["Israel Resilience Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 95, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Kurt G\u00f6del was working for University of Notre Dame, which employer did Kurt G\u00f6del work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Kurt G\u00f6del worked for Institute of Advanced Studies in 1976.", "Kurt G\u00f6del worked for Eunice Kennedy Shriver National Institute of Child Health and Human Development in 1974.", "Kurt G\u00f6del worked for KMD from March 15, 1940 to August 17, 1972.", "Kurt G\u00f6del works for Institute for Advanced Study from 1940 to 1978.", "Kurt G\u00f6del worked for Leibniz Institute for Astrophysics Potsdam in September, 1973.", "Kurt G\u00f6del worked for Canal+ from 1974 to 1977.", "Kurt G\u00f6del works for University of Notre Dame from 1938 to 1939.", "Kurt G\u00f6del worked for Gide Loyrette Nouel from 1946 to 1963.", "Kurt G\u00f6del works for Princeton University from 1938 to 1939.", "Kurt G\u00f6del worked for Max Planck Institute for Terrestrial Microbiology in February, 1942."], "answer": ["Princeton University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 96, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Leif Blomberg was holding the position of Minister for Consumer Affairs, which position did Leif Blomberg concurrently?", "facts": ["Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister of Sports from March 22, 1996 to March 2, 1998.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of board member from 1984 to 1986.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Prevention, Public Health and Primary Care in October, 1995.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Shadow Attorney General for England and Wales in October, 1982.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister of Police in April, 1993.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister for Consumer Affairs from March 22, 1996 to March 2, 1998.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of chairperson from 1982 to 1993.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Minister for Integration from March 22, 1996 to March 2, 1998.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of Mayor of Bucharest in 1985.", "Leif Blomberg holds the position of First Secretary of the Communist Party of Ukraine from July 9, 1989 to October 15, 1994."], "answer": ["Minister for Integration", "Minister of Sports"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 97, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Lajos Ol\u00e1h was a member of Hungarian Socialist Party, which political party did Lajos Ol\u00e1h belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the From Five in November 6, 2004.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the France Arise in January 28, 2008.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Ensemble Montr\u00e9al from August 10, 1996 to January 26, 2006.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Reagrupament in 1998.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Democratic Coalition in October 23, 2011.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Hungarian Socialist Party in October 23, 2011.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Land and People in September 26, 2003.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h attended E\u00f6tv\u00f6s Lor\u00e1nd University in 1993.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Communist Party USA in June, 2010.", "Lajos Ol\u00e1h is a member of the Social Democratic Party \"Harmony\" in November 23, 2009."], "answer": ["Democratic Coalition"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 98, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Cecil Hunter-Rodwell was holding the position of Governor of Fiji, which position did Cecil Hunter-Rodwell concurrently?", "facts": ["Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Governor of Southern Rhodesia from November 24, 1928 to May 1, 1934.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Vice President of Egypt from August, 1926 to September, 1926.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Supreme Commander of the Swedish Armed Forces from November 7, 1926 to October 8, 1929.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Governor of Fiji from October 10, 1918 to April 25, 1925.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of United States Ambassador to Benin in April 5, 1932.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Governor of Puerto Rico from October 1, 1930 to October 25, 1930.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of High Commissioner for the Western Pacific from October 10, 1918 to April 25, 1925.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Lord Speaker from January 11, 1929 to August 17, 1934.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of Secretary of State of West Virginia in December 5, 1926.", "Cecil Hunter-Rodwell holds the position of High Court judge from July 16, 1934 to July 24, 1934."], "answer": ["High Commissioner for the Western Pacific"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 99, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joseph J. Tyson was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Joseph J. Tyson simultaneously?", "facts": ["Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 12, 2011.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of titular bishop in May 12, 2005.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of President of the Maldives in October, 2007.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 6, 2005.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of First Commissioner of Works in 2007.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of President of the Los Angeles City Council in December 8, 2011.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of President of the Legislative Yuan in June, 2005.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 12, 2005.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of Minister of Social Affairs and Health in November 14, 2010.", "Joseph J. Tyson holds the position of Minister of Defence from June, 2010 to September, 2010."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 100, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 was holding the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Serbia, which position did Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 concurrently?", "facts": ["Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of mayor of Novi Sad in September 14, 2012.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Minister of Defense in October 26, 2022.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States from 2020 to 2021.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic in May, 2015.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Serbia in October 26, 2022.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of president of Germany in January, 2015.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Secretary of Agriculture in February 3, 2014.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills from February, 2021 to November, 2021.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of United States Ambassador to Portugal from October, 2020 to August, 2021.", "Milo\u0161 Vu\u010devi\u0107 holds the position of Minister for Financial Markets from December 7, 2017 to March 13, 2018."], "answer": ["Minister of Defense"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 101, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n simultaneously?", "facts": ["Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of President of the Supreme Court of the United Kingdom in August 10, 1986.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of President of the Senate of Romania in March 19, 1989.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of titular bishop in March 21, 1986.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of Under Secretary of the Navy in October, 1987.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of Prime Minister of the Central African Republic in 1993.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of Beyer Chair of Applied Mathematics in June 2, 1989.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 23, 1986.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of diocesan bishop in May 8, 1995.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 21, 1986.", "Mario Luis Bautista Mauli\u00f3n holds the position of French Minister of the Sea in 1988."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 102, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of chief of police from 1998 to 2003.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 26, 1990 to July 23, 2005.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of Caretaker Prime Minister of Pakistan from 1993 to 2002.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of Justice of the Common Pleas in April, 1997.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of President of Moldova in 1994.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 22, 1983.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of First Deputy Prime Minister of Ukraine from 1989 to 1994.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 16, 1983.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of President of the Legislative Yuan in March 1, 1986.", "Pedro Luis Guido Scarpa holds the position of titular bishop in July 22, 1983."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 103, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Denis Matthew Lowney was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Denis Matthew Lowney simultaneously?", "facts": ["Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of titular bishop in August 24, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 23, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of trustee in June, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of Vice President of Nigeria in March 13, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of United States Ambassador to Vietnam in August 8, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees in March, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of European Union Special Representative in June 13, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of Minister of State for Policing and the Fire Service in December 17, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 24, 1917.", "Denis Matthew Lowney holds the position of Chief of the Cabinet of Ministers of Argentina in February 17, 1917."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 104, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Dawn Marie Addiego was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Dawn Marie Addiego belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Party of Communists of the Republic of Moldova in January 24, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Christian Union in April, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Serbian Democratic Party in May, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Republican Party in January 28, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Democratic Party in January 28, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Western Australian Labor Party in December 1, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Hungarian Justice and Life Party in August, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Catalan Republican Party in October, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Minnesota Farmer\u2013Labor Party in February 5, 2019.", "Dawn Marie Addiego is a member of the Servant of the People in July 10, 2019."], "answer": ["Republican Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 105, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Leon Ma\u0142y was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Leon Ma\u0142y during the same time period?", "facts": ["Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 20, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of President of Paraguay in September 14, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Prime Minister of Uganda in October 18, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Minister of Tourism in November, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 4, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Minister for Education and Science in April, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Defence in October, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of titular bishop in May 4, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Justice Minister of Denmark in January 24, 2002.", "Leon Ma\u0142y holds the position of Minister of Indigenous Services in July 18, 2002."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 106, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Edmund Barton was holding the position of Prime Minister of Australia, which position did Edmund Barton during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Edmund Barton holds the position of Prime Minister of Australia from January 1, 1901 to September 24, 1903.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Chair of the Federal Reserve from 1891 to 1893.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship in 1884.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Speaker of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly from January 3, 1883 to January 31, 1887.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Agent-general for New South Wales in April, 1895.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Leader of the Government in the Legislative Council from January 17, 1889 to March 7, 1889.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of executive officer from June 18, 1883 to April 22, 1885.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Governor of British Ceylon from 1887 to 1890.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Minister for Foreign Affairs from January 1, 1901 to September 24, 1903.", "Edmund Barton holds the position of Principal Private Secretary to the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs in May 21, 1884."], "answer": ["Minister for Foreign Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 107, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Meletie Covaci was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Meletie Covaci within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Meletie Covaci holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 16, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Prime Minister of Turkey in July, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of President of the European Commission in October 24, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of President of Slovenia in November 23, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of list of governors of British Guiana in May, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of titular bishop in September 16, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 16, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of President of Paraguay in February, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Attorney General of Arkansas in June 20, 1748.", "Meletie Covaci holds the position of Chief Prosecutor of Hungary in February, 1748."], "answer": ["Catholic bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 108, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ghida Fakhry was working for CNN, which employer did Ghida Fakhry work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Ghida Fakhry works for Al Jazeera from 2000 to 2001.", "Ghida Fakhry works for TRT World in 2017.", "Ghida Fakhry worked for London and North Western Railway in 2009.", "Ghida Fakhry worked for The Moscow Times from 2005 to 2016.", "Ghida Fakhry worked for NBCUniversal from June, 2005 to June, 2011.", "Ghida Fakhry worked for Lebanese University in 2015.", "Ghida Fakhry worked for Oticon in September 24, 2011.", "Ghida Fakhry works for CNN from 2000 to 2001.", "Ghida Fakhry worked for University of Calcutta in 2014.", "Ghida Fakhry works for HuffPost in 2016."], "answer": ["Al Jazeera"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 109, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Arnold Orowae was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Arnold Orowae at the same time?", "facts": ["Arnold Orowae holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 4, 2000.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from March 25, 2006 to April 27, 2007.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Housing and Urban Development in 2008.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 14, 1999.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of Prosecutor General of Ukraine from 2002 to 2007.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of editor-in-chief in June 15, 2005.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of Prime Minister of Turkey from January, 2000 to November, 2001.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of Texas Attorney General from 2002 to 2004.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of titular bishop in December 14, 1999.", "Arnold Orowae holds the position of diocesan bishop in June 30, 2008."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 110, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alain Robbe-Grillet was working for New York University, which employer did Alain Robbe-Grillet work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for Pomona College in December 3, 1965.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet works for L'Express from 1955 to 1956.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet works for Washington University in St.\u00a0Louis from 1972 to 1997.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for Tufts University School of Medicine from 1956 to 1967.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for Houston Police Department in October, 1971.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for University College London in November, 1964.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for London Passenger Transport Board in February, 1959.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for California Institute of Technology in August, 1958.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet worked for Robert  College in August 25, 1955.", "Alain Robbe-Grillet works for New York University from 1972 to 1997."], "answer": ["Washington University in St.\u00a0Louis"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 111, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino during the same time span?", "facts": ["Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of Deputy Premier of South Australia in December, 1985.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of school superintendent from 1988 to 1991.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of diocesan bishop from April 19, 2000 to February 18, 2009.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of titular bishop in December 12, 1974.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 25, 1975.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of Monsignor from 2000 to 2003.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of Secretary of State of Georgia from 1989 to 1991.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 12, 1974.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of Bishop of Down and Connor from March 11, 1986 to August 23, 1988.", "Ang\u00e9lico S\u00e2ndalo Bernardino holds the position of Republican Party from 2005 to 2009."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 112, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Archie Cameron was a member of Liberal and Country League of South Australia, which political party did Archie Cameron belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Archie Cameron is a member of the Country Party in June 9, 1932.", "Archie Cameron is a member of the Hungarian Justice and Life Party in July, 1943.", "Archie Cameron holds the position of Minister for Defence from March 14, 1940 to October 28, 1940.", "Archie Cameron holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives from February 22, 1950 to August 9, 1956.", "Archie Cameron is a member of the Kuomintang in April 6, 1934.", "Archie Cameron holds the position of Minister for Communications, Urban Infrastructure, Cities and the Arts from November 7, 1938 to April 26, 1939.", "Archie Cameron is a member of the Hatnuah from March, 1946 to December, 1947.", "Archie Cameron is a member of the Action Fran\u00e7aise from 1933 to 1937.", "Archie Cameron is a member of the Liberal and Country League of South Australia in June 9, 1932.", "Archie Cameron holds the position of Australian Minister for Agriculture from March 14, 1940 to October 28, 1940."], "answer": ["Country Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 113, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrice Motsepe was holding the position of chairperson, which position did Patrice Motsepe during the same time span?", "facts": ["Patrice Motsepe holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Hungary from January 2, 2011 to November 3, 2014.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of chairperson in March 12, 2021.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of President of the Community of Madrid from December 1, 2009 to December 20, 2014.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of Minister for Europe and International Development in October, 2005.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of president in 2004.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of vice president in March 12, 2021.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of Minister for Agriculture, Food and the Marine in October 13, 2021.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of Minister of International Trade from 2011 to 2016.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of Leader of the Labour Party in July 15, 2006.", "Patrice Motsepe holds the position of pastor in August 5, 2012."], "answer": ["vice president"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 114, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Roach was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did John Roach simultaneously?", "facts": ["John Roach holds the position of Minister in the Presidency in April, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of inspector general in June, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs in May 10, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of titular bishop in July 12, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of North Dakota Attorney General in January, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of United States Ambassador to the Holy See in November, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 8, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of Chief of the Army Staff in September 21, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of Executive of Baltimore County, Maryland in February 27, 1971.", "John Roach holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 8, 1971."], "answer": ["Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 115, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Antoinette Sandbach was a member of Liberal Democrats, which political party did Antoinette Sandbach belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Liberal Democrats in October 31, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the New Right in January, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Our Home \u2013 Russia in May, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Party of the Revolution in July, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Coalition Movement in February 20, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Conservative Party in October 31, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Eniaion in February, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Priorit\u00e9 Monaco in November, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Rally of the French People in June 25, 2019.", "Antoinette Sandbach is a member of the Republican Nationalist Federal Union in December, 2019."], "answer": ["Conservative Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 116, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez during the same time span?", "facts": ["Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of Leader of the House of Lords in June, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of United States Ambassador to Ivory Coast in November 24, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of Secretary-General to the President, Republic of China in November 12, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills in October 11, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of Minister of Health in October 4, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 1, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of titular bishop in February 1, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 10, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of Chief Secretary to the Treasury in August, 2014.", "Luis Fernando Ramos P\u00e9rez holds the position of High Representative of the Union for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy in April 13, 2014."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 117, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Robert Edward Mulvee was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Robert Edward Mulvee during the same time span?", "facts": ["Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of Lord Warden of the Cinque Ports in May, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 15, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of Minister for Europe and International Development in August 15, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of Secretary of State of Kentucky in October 26, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of Prime Minister of Romania in September, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of High Sheriff in November, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of titular bishop in February 15, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of President of Moldova in July, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of Minister for Resource Management in April 24, 1977.", "Robert Edward Mulvee holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 14, 1977."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 118, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While James McLachlan was a member of Liberal Union, which political party did James McLachlan belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["James McLachlan is a member of the National Trust Party in April 17, 1947.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Industrial Labor Party from 1939 to 1946.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Agreement from November 20, 1937 to February 22, 1943.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Republican Party of the Social Order from 1936 to 1946.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Australian Labor Party (South Australian Branch) from 1943 to 1945.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Progressive Party of Working People from May, 1941 to September, 1944.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Liberal Federation in October 16, 1923.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Golongan Karya Party from May, 1926 to December, 1936.", "James McLachlan holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from July 1, 1935 to June 30, 1947.", "James McLachlan is a member of the Liberal Union in October 16, 1923."], "answer": ["Liberal Federation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 119, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luis Adriano Piedrahita was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Luis Adriano Piedrahita during the same time period?", "facts": ["Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of Minister of Natural Resources and Environment from July, 2002 to August, 2006.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of treasurer general in March, 2002.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of European Commissioner for Climate Action in July 27, 2002.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of titular bishop in July 19, 1999.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 8, 1999.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 19, 1999.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of diocesan bishop in July 3, 2007.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs from February, 2007 to April, 2007.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of Magistrate of Pingtung County in July 23, 2000.", "Luis Adriano Piedrahita holds the position of White House Communications Director from September, 2000 to February, 2003."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 120, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo concurrently?", "facts": ["Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 3, 1983.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of diocesan bishop from April 14, 2000 to April 4, 2012.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of Minister of Agriculture & Farmers Welfare in November 27, 2004.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of titular bishop in November 3, 1983.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of Minister of State for Security in August 4, 2002.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of Prime Minister of Ukraine in September, 2003.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of Mercosur Pro Tempore Presidency in 2004.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of party chair in 2006.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 3, 1983.", "Gonzalo Ramiro del Castillo Crespo holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Science, Research and Innovation from December 15, 2010 to December 26, 2010."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 121, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Eduard Schick was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Eduard Schick simultaneously?", "facts": ["Eduard Schick holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 11, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of acting president in July 18, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of Commendatory abbot in January 9, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 14, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of President of Israel in October, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of Governor of Delaware in May, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of secretary in March, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of titular bishop in April 14, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of Governor of Queensland in August, 1962.", "Eduard Schick holds the position of federal spokesperson of the Austrian Green Party in December 2, 1962."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 122, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Shirley Jeffries was a member of Liberal and Country League of South Australia, which political party did Shirley Jeffries belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Valencian Union in June 15, 1933.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Norwegian Labour Party in 1925.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Coalition Montr\u00e9al in December 15, 1942.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Free Democratic Party in August 3, 1909.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Liberal Federation in June 9, 1932.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Russian Party of Life from April 20, 1942 to September 24, 1942.", "Shirley Jeffries holds the position of Attorney-General of South Australia from April 18, 1933 to May 6, 1944.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the People's Party of Republicans and Conservatives from September, 1908 to September, 1912.", "Shirley Jeffries is a member of the Liberal and Country League of South Australia in June 9, 1932.", "Shirley Jeffries attended University of Adelaide in 1906."], "answer": ["Liberal Federation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 123, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alfred Michael Watson was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Alfred Michael Watson concurrently?", "facts": ["Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of United States Ambassador to Lithuania in February 25, 1977.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of Minister of State for Europe from November 19, 1979 to November 23, 1981.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of Colorado General Assembly from June, 1976 to June, 1981.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 17, 1969 to July 16, 1982.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of Special Assistant to the President in December 10, 1982.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 29, 1965.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of titular bishop in May 17, 1965.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 17, 1965.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of President of D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann in August, 1978.", "Alfred Michael Watson holds the position of press secretary in 1979."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 124, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While H. V. Evatt was holding the position of Attorney-General for Australia, which position did H. V. Evatt within the same time interval?", "facts": ["H. V. Evatt holds the position of Chief Justice of New South Wales from February 15, 1960 to October 24, 1962.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Minister of Transport and Communications from April, 1958 to March, 1960.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of President of Liberia in March, 1954.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Marshal of the Realm from July 23, 1957 to December 24, 1957.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Minister of Employment, Workforce, and Labour in July 5, 1954.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Minister for Foreign Affairs from October 7, 1941 to December 19, 1949.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Attorney-General for Australia from October 7, 1941 to December 19, 1949.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Leader of the Opposition of Australia from June 20, 1951 to February 9, 1960.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of artist-in-residence in 1953.", "H. V. Evatt holds the position of Assistant Secretary of State for Educational and Cultural Affairs in 1960."], "answer": ["Minister for Foreign Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 125, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Nelson J. Perez was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Nelson J. Perez during the same time span?", "facts": ["Nelson J. Perez holds the position of diocesan bishop in July 11, 2017.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of President of Guinea in June 24, 2013.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 8, 2012.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of titular bishop in June 8, 2012.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 25, 2012.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of Minister for Ecclesiastical Affairs of Denmark in 2013.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of Vice-President of the Executive Council in 2015.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of Governor-General of India in 2017.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of Chancellery of the President of the Republic of Poland from 2014 to 2015.", "Nelson J. Perez holds the position of chief financial officer from February 2, 2015 to December 17, 2015."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 126, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Maguire was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did John Maguire within the same time interval?", "facts": ["John Maguire holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 11, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of Finnish Minister for European Affairs in February 15, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of titular bishop in April 6, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of United States Ambassador to Canada in July, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of First Lord of the Treasury in July, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of President of Mexico in October, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of Minister for the Environment, Energy and Climate (Iceland) in March, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of Resident Commissioner of the Philippines in May, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Ely in June, 1894.", "John Maguire holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 6, 1894."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 127, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jens Orback was holding the position of Minister of Democracy, which position did Jens Orback during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Jens Orback holds the position of Minister of the Environment in August 7, 2010.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Exports in November, 2011.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Chief Justice of the United States in June 16, 2011.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Chief Rabbinate of Israel in July, 2009.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Minister of Democracy from October 21, 2004 to October 6, 2006.", "Jens Orback holds the position of chief physician in February, 2010.", "Jens Orback holds the position of general secretary from 2008 to 2016.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Vice President of the United States in November, 2016.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Minister for Gender Equality Affairs from October 21, 2004 to October 6, 2006.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Minister for Integration from October 21, 2004 to October 6, 2006."], "answer": ["Minister for Integration", "Minister for Gender Equality Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 128, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of Mayor of Boston from December, 2004 to July, 2005.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 16, 1982.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 25, 1983.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of council member from 2005 to 2006.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of diocesan bishop from June 6, 1991 to September 1, 2006.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of Governor of Tasmania in November, 2000.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of Prime Minister of Tuvalu in 2005.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of Prime Minister of Ukraine in April 7, 1990.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Ely in November 15, 2003.", "Jos\u00e9 Hugo Garaycoa Hawkins holds the position of titular bishop in December 16, 1982."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 129, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While David Konstant was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did David Konstant during the same time span?", "facts": ["David Konstant holds the position of Bishop of Aston from April 11, 1982 to July 24, 1990.", "David Konstant holds the position of chief administrative officer from December 14, 1984 to October 24, 1999.", "David Konstant holds the position of titular bishop in March 28, 1977.", "David Konstant holds the position of ambassador of Ukraine to Finland from April, 1990 to January, 1997.", "David Konstant holds the position of Governor of Queensland in May, 1986.", "David Konstant holds the position of Members of the Dewan Rakyat, 15th Malaysian Parliament from November 11, 1987 to January 21, 2004.", "David Konstant holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 28, 1977.", "David Konstant holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 25, 1977.", "David Konstant holds the position of diocesan bishop from July 12, 1985 to April 7, 2004.", "David Konstant holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs and Communications from June, 1990 to January, 1999."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 130, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Maximiano Tuazon Cruz was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Maximiano Tuazon Cruz at the same time?", "facts": ["Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of postdoctoral researcher in February 16, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of titular bishop in November 10, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of Lord Mayor of Sheffield in September 22, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of ICAC Commissioner in January, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of Prime Minister of Ghana in May, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of United States Ambassador to Israel in March 8, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 1, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of Minister of Employment, Workforce, and Labour in December 20, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 10, 1987.", "Maximiano Tuazon Cruz holds the position of President of Latvia in August, 1987."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 131, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Dominic Joseph Conway was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Dominic Joseph Conway during the same time period?", "facts": ["Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of Permanent Representative of Israel to the United Nations from November 6, 1973 to February 20, 1982.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 12, 1971 to May 24, 1994.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of titular bishop in October 16, 1970.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of Minister for Solidarity and Health in May 6, 1988.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of Assistant Secretary of Defense for International Security Affairs in 1981.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 16, 1970.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of Minister for Defence from November 23, 1976 to June 27, 1982.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of Governor of Indiana in December 23, 1989.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 8, 1970.", "Dominic Joseph Conway holds the position of senator from May, 1993 to March, 1994."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 132, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of Minister of Labor in April 15, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of United States Ambassador to Czechoslovakia in January, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of Minister in the Presidency in July 7, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 22, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of Chief of Army Staff in May, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of Governor of New Hampshire in May 18, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of titular bishop in July 22, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of Minister of Culture of Denmark in November, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 21, 2000.", "Joaqu\u00edn Mariano Sucunza holds the position of comptroller in October, 2000."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 133, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Joseph McCormick was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Patrick Joseph McCormick concurrently?", "facts": ["Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of member of congress in October 26, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of Federal Department of Defence, Civil Protection and Sports in May, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of Minister of State for European Affairs in January, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of United States federal judge in May, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of Secretary of State for Work and Pensions in October, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of United States Ambassador to Israel in July, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Mauritius in February 25, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of titular bishop in June 14, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 14, 1950.", "Patrick Joseph McCormick holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 21, 1950."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 134, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pralhad Joshi was holding the position of Minister of Parliamentary Affairs, which position did Pralhad Joshi simultaneously?", "facts": ["Pralhad Joshi holds the position of chairperson of the board in January, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Minister of Mines in May 30, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of chief financial officer in July 23, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of secretary-general in September 27, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Liberal Democrat Home Affairs spokesman in September 22, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Minister of Coal in May 30, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Economic Secretary to the Treasury in February 21, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Minister of Parliamentary Affairs in May 30, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of First Sea Lord in July 24, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Vice President of the Republic of China in May 9, 2019."], "answer": ["Minister of Mines", "Minister of Coal"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 135, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Karl Borsch was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Karl Borsch within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Karl Borsch holds the position of sports director in August 4, 2000.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of special prosecutor from April, 2000 to January, 2002.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Leader of the House of Lords from 1986 to 1989.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 17, 2004.", "Karl Borsch attended Sankt Georgen Graduate School of Philosophy and Theology from 1985 to 1990.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs, Turkey from March, 1989 to February, 1998.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of titular bishop in January 17, 2004.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Governor of Maine in June, 1996.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 17, 2004.", "Karl Borsch attended University of Bonn from 1979 to 1985."], "answer": ["Catholic bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 136, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Brian Druker was working for Dana\u2013Farber Cancer Institute, which employer did Brian Druker work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Brian Druker worked for Cambridge Observatory from April, 1997 to February, 2001.", "Brian Druker works for Harvard Medical School from 1987 to 1993.", "Brian Druker works for Dana\u2013Farber Cancer Institute from 1987 to 1993.", "Brian Druker works for Oregon Health & Science University in 2010.", "Brian Druker worked for University of Puerto Rico in January, 2004.", "Brian Druker works for Brigham and Women's Hospital from 1987 to 1993.", "Brian Druker worked for Yerevan Physics Institute from October 14, 2009 to January 17, 2010.", "Brian Druker worked for MSU Faculty of Computational Mathematics and Cybernetics in 2000.", "Brian Druker worked for Brasenose College in November, 1999.", "Brian Druker worked for Yale School of Medicine from March 8, 1996 to September 11, 1998."], "answer": ["Brigham and Women's Hospital", "Harvard Medical School"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 137, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Reginald Delargey was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Reginald Delargey within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Reginald Delargey holds the position of President of Latvia in April 21, 1967.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of Permanent Representative to the United Nations in March, 1970.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 27, 1958.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of diocesan bishop in September 1, 1970.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of cardinal in May 24, 1976.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 25, 1957.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of general in August, 1973.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of Minister for the purposes of the Atlantic Canada Opportunities Agency Act from August 16, 1959 to November 18, 1960.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of titular bishop in November 25, 1957.", "Reginald Delargey holds the position of assessor in March 27, 1969."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 138, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pedro Orozco was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Pedro Orozco during the same time span?", "facts": ["Pedro Orozco holds the position of Bishop of London in 1644.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Minister for Tourism from November 23, 1644 to November 25, 1644.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Chief of Navy in September, 1643.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Lord Chancellor in November 3, 1643.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 14, 1643.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of titular bishop in December 14, 1643.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Salisbury from May, 1644 to October, 1644.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Defence in May 27, 1644.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Minister of Agriculture and Forestry in 1644.", "Pedro Orozco holds the position of Catholic bishop in 1644."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 139, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Adrian Grodecki was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Adrian Grodecki during the same time span?", "facts": ["Adrian Grodecki holds the position of United States Ambassador to Cuba from September 5, 1645 to September 8, 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of titular bishop in December 12, 1644.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 12, 1644.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Catholic bishop in 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office in March, 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Captain of the Honourable Corps of Gentlemen-at-Arms from November, 1645 to December, 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Minister of Defence of Hungary in May, 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Secretary of State for the Environment from August 10, 1645 to November 28, 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Member of Provincial Parliament of Western Cape in 1645.", "Adrian Grodecki holds the position of Mayor of Taoyuan from January, 1645 to April, 1645."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 140, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead was holding the position of Lord Privy Seal, which position did John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead during the identical time period?", "facts": ["John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign Affairs from June 18, 2003 to November 21, 2003.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Federal Minister for Special Affairs of Germany in 1991.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Suffolk from February 11, 1994 to June 30, 2003.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of President of Cuba from February 16, 1998 to January 16, 2003.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of High Commissioner for the Western Pacific in December, 1998.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Resident Commissioner of the Philippines in April, 2002.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Lord Privy Seal from January 10, 1988 to November 28, 1990.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Prime Minister of the Czech Republic in June 20, 2003.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Leader of the House of Lords from January 10, 1988 to November 28, 1990.", "John Ganzoni, 2nd Baron Belstead holds the position of Sterling Professor in 1993."], "answer": ["Leader of the House of Lords"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 141, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Kazimierz Wielikosielec was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Kazimierz Wielikosielec simultaneously?", "facts": ["Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of Governor of Rhode Island in January, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of titular bishop in May 6, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of minority leader in June 14, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of First Secretary of the Georgian Communist Party in June 22, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of alderman in October 15, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of Mayor of Greater Manchester in December 18, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 6, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of Chief Secretary for Ireland in October, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 24, 1999.", "Kazimierz Wielikosielec holds the position of Governor of Baja California in April, 1999."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 142, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Julian Kuo was a member of independent politician, which political party did Julian Kuo belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Julian Kuo is a member of the Non-Partisan Solidarity Union in March 4, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the Democratic Progressive Party in May 19, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the Communist Party of Brazil in September, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the National Resistance Movement in June 2, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the People's Electoral Movement in December 25, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the FRELIMO in January 9, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the New Zealand Liberal Party in October, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the Left Party in September 27, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the independent politician in May 19, 2023.", "Julian Kuo is a member of the Kadima in September 25, 2023."], "answer": ["Democratic Progressive Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 143, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo simultaneously?", "facts": ["Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Riksr\u00e5d in February, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of titular bishop in April 28, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 28, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 28, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Minister for Disabled People in June 22, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Chairperson of the Parliament of Georgia in November, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Military governor of Paris in October, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of First Secretary of the French Socialist Party in July, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Hawaii in December, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Ukrainian Minister of Foreign Affairs in December, 1564."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "diocesan bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 144, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Drago\u0219 Tudorache was a member of Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party, which political party did Drago\u0219 Tudorache belong to during the same time period?", "facts": ["Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the Bulgarian Communist Party from July 16, 2020 to November 28, 2020.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the Ensemble Montr\u00e9al from 2019 to 2020.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the One NL in 2020.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the National Unity of Hope in April 24, 2020.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the Renewing Romania's European Project in May 31, 2022.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the No Pokies in November, 2022.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the Freedom and Direct Democracy from June 14, 2019 to December 22, 2020.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache holds the position of member of the European Parliament in July 2, 2019.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party in May 31, 2022.", "Drago\u0219 Tudorache is a member of the Communist Party of India (Marxist-Leninist) in 2019."], "answer": ["Renewing Romania's European Project"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 145, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While George Christensen was a member of National Party of Australia, which political party did George Christensen belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["George Christensen is a member of the Australian Democrats in October, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the People's Party for Freedom and Democracy in December, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the Union of Democrats for the Republic in August 24, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the Liberal National Party of Queensland in April 7, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the One Nation in April 12, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the Rassemblement Bleu Marine in May 4, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the Freie W\u00e4hler in February, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the Pachakutik Plurinational Unity Movement in September 6, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the National Party of Australia in April 7, 2022.", "George Christensen is a member of the National Alliance Party in June 21, 2022."], "answer": ["Liberal National Party of Queensland"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 146, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While William Hague was a member of Liberal Union, which political party did William Hague belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["William Hague is a member of the Liberal Federation in October 16, 1923.", "William Hague is a member of the Democratic Unionist Party in August 26, 1921.", "William Hague is a member of the Liberal Union in October 16, 1923.", "William Hague is a member of the Change UK from March 4, 1924 to March 6, 1924.", "William Hague is a member of the Independent Democratic Union in November, 1923.", "William Hague is a member of the New Democratic Party from April 19, 1920 to July 25, 1922.", "William Hague holds the position of Treasurer of South Australia from November 3, 1922 to April 16, 1924.", "William Hague holds the position of Minister of Public Works from April 8, 1920 to November 3, 1922.", "William Hague is a member of the Republican People's Party in July 2, 1922.", "William Hague is a member of the Democratic Labour Party from February, 1924 to July, 1924."], "answer": ["Liberal Federation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 147, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Miguel Gatan Purugganan was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Miguel Gatan Purugganan during the same time span?", "facts": ["Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Energy and Climate Change from September, 1994 to March, 1999.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of United States Associate Attorney General from April 13, 1988 to July 18, 1998.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of Archbishop of Uppsala from October 25, 1999 to December 28, 1999.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of Resident Minister in February, 1996.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of diocesan bishop from January 21, 1974 to July 26, 1999.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice and Tackling Illegal Migration from March 1, 1988 to November 17, 1993.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 22, 1971.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of Supreme Court of Ohio in February 10, 1983.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of titular bishop in January 23, 1971.", "Miguel Gatan Purugganan holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 23, 1971."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 148, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Marijan Oblak was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Marijan Oblak during the same time period?", "facts": ["Marijan Oblak holds the position of Permanent Representative of the United Kingdom to the United Nations, New York in January, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 6, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of President of Chile in May 16, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 30, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of Chief Prosecutor of Hungary in March 28, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of Chief of the Naval Staff in March 17, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of Vice President of the Federated States of Micronesia in July, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of titular bishop in April 30, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of Commanding General of the United States Army in September 19, 1958.", "Marijan Oblak holds the position of Chief of the Cabinet of Ministers of Argentina in March 27, 1958."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 149, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Katy Gallagher was holding the position of Attorney-General for Australia, which position did Katy Gallagher simultaneously?", "facts": ["Katy Gallagher holds the position of member of the House of Commons of Canada in 2016.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Minister of Veterans Affairs from January, 2013 to June, 2021.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Minister for the Status of Women in May 23, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of member of the Australian Capital Territory Legislative Assembly from October 20, 2001 to December 23, 2014.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Chief Minister of the Australian Capital Territory from May 16, 2011 to December 11, 2014.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Prime Minister of Haiti in December 5, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Attorney-General for Australia in May 23, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of President of the Congress of Deputies from 2016 to 2021.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Shadow Lord Chancellor from August 5, 2021 to August 18, 2021.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Minister for Finance of Australia in May 23, 2022."], "answer": ["Minister for Finance of Australia", "Minister for the Status of Women"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 150, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Hans van den Broek was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Hans van den Broek belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Hans van den Broek is a member of the Humanist Power Party from October, 1991 to February, 1996.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Musavat Party from 2003 to 2004.", "Hans van den Broek holds the position of Minister of State in February 25, 2005.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Catholic People's Party in October 11, 1980.", "Hans van den Broek holds the position of European Commissioner for External Relations from January 6, 1993 to September 15, 1999.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Silver Republican Party in 1991.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Canadian Alliance in August 4, 1988.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Liberal Democratic Party of Germany in October, 1981.", "Hans van den Broek is a member of the Finnish Rural Party from 1999 to 2003."], "answer": ["Catholic People's Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 151, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Margrethe Vestager was holding the position of Vice-President of the European Commission, which position did Margrethe Vestager simultaneously?", "facts": ["Margrethe Vestager holds the position of Minister for Social Affairs from January 20, 1986 to January 22, 1998.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of Vice-President of the European Commission in December 1, 2019.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of Secretary of the Central Commission for Discipline Inspection from 1992 to 2017.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of Minister for Ecclesiastical Affairs of Denmark from March 23, 1998 to December 21, 2000.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of European Commissioner for A Europe Fit for the Digital Age in December 1, 2019.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of European Commissioner for Competition in November 1, 2014.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of Minister of Education from March 23, 1998 to November 27, 2001.", "Margrethe Vestager holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Denmark from October 3, 2011 to September 2, 2014.", "Margrethe Vestager works for Ministry of Finance of Denmark from 1993 to 1995.", "Margrethe Vestager attended University of Copenhagen from 1986 to 1993."], "answer": ["European Commissioner for A Europe Fit for the Digital Age"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 152, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Carlos Gershenson was working for Massachusetts Institute of Technology, which employer did Carlos Gershenson work for during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Carlos Gershenson worked for Academy of Sciences of the USSR in November, 2003.", "Carlos Gershenson worked for Echo of Moscow from June, 2002 to March, 2007.", "Carlos Gershenson attended Vrije Universiteit Brussel from November 1, 2002 to April, 2007.", "Carlos Gershenson worked for S\u00fcdwestrundfunk in 2009.", "Carlos Gershenson worked for National Science Foundation in February 26, 2015.", "Carlos Gershenson worked for Geeknet from April 12, 2009 to December 21, 2011.", "Carlos Gershenson worked for Telstra in 2014.", "Carlos Gershenson worked for Central Academic Theatre of the Russian Army from October 24, 2011 to January 27, 2013.", "Carlos Gershenson works for Northeastern University from July, 2015 to July, 2016.", "Carlos Gershenson works for Massachusetts Institute of Technology from July, 2015 to July, 2016."], "answer": ["Northeastern University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 153, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Antonio Iannucci was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Antonio Iannucci during the same time period?", "facts": ["Antonio Iannucci holds the position of Financial Secretary in January 18, 1957.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of titular bishop in March 20, 1955.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of Anglican bishop of Lincoln from 1956 to 1957.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 20, 1955.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of diocesan bishop in February 15, 1959.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 8, 1955.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of contributing editor in 1956.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of First Lady in November 2, 1956.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of assessor from July, 1959 to September, 1959.", "Antonio Iannucci holds the position of Minister of Justice of Hungary in December 19, 1959."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 154, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Theodor Innitzer was holding the position of Catholic bishop, which position did Theodor Innitzer simultaneously?", "facts": ["Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Chair of the Chamber of Deputies of the Parliament of the Czech Republic in June 17, 1933.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of President of South Korea in February 7, 1933.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Archbishop of Vienna in October 16, 1932.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Chief Justice of the Common Pleas in June, 1933.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Ireland in November, 1933.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Under-Secretary of State for the Home Department in January, 1932.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of cardinal in March 13, 1933.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for International Development in 1933.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 16, 1932.", "Theodor Innitzer holds the position of Minister for Infrastructure and Transport from September, 1933 to October, 1933."], "answer": ["Archbishop of Vienna"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 155, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Kostas Lapavitsas was a member of SYRIZA, which political party did Kostas Lapavitsas belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Kostas Lapavitsas works for School of Oriental and African Studies, University of London in 1999.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Brothers of Italy from July 6, 2004 to December 24, 2004.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Nasjonal Samling in November 18, 2001.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the SYRIZA in August 21, 2015.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Popular Unity in August 21, 2015.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Hungarian Social Democratic Party from November, 2012 to February, 2013.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Congress for Democracy and Progress from August 28, 2005 to June 28, 2009.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Vlaams Blok from 2009 to 2012.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Janata Dal from April 6, 2003 to December 26, 2006.", "Kostas Lapavitsas is a member of the Christian People's Party in February 2, 2006."], "answer": ["Popular Unity"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 156, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Timothy Edward Freyer was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Timothy Edward Freyer within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of Privy Council of the United Kingdom in June 23, 2016.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of Minister of Immigration from April, 2017 to May, 2017.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of titular bishop in November 23, 2016.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of Massachusetts Attorney General in 2017.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 17, 2017.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 23, 2016.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of Vice President of Peru in February 14, 2016.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of mayor of a place in France in October 7, 2017.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of Head of the Security Service of Ukraine from June 4, 2017 to July 20, 2017.", "Timothy Edward Freyer holds the position of minister in December 3, 2017."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 157, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Bruno Maldaner was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Bruno Maldaner within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Bruno Maldaner holds the position of United States Ambassador to Azerbaijan from March 26, 2001 to December 26, 2001.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 29, 1966.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of titular bishop in April 15, 1966.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of United States Ambassador to Ivory Coast in 1978.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of deacon in 1990.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Development in 1968.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of conductor in June, 1979.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of diocesan bishop from May 27, 1971 to December 12, 2001.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 15, 1966.", "Bruno Maldaner holds the position of Hofmarschall from November, 1968 to January, 1981."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 158, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Joseph Paul was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did John Joseph Paul simultaneously?", "facts": ["John Joseph Paul holds the position of Lowndean Professor of Astronomy and Geometry from April 4, 1979 to July 25, 1982.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of Privy Council of the United Kingdom from 1991 to 1994.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 4, 1977.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of diocesan bishop from October 14, 1983 to December 10, 1994.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 17, 1977.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of titular bishop in May 17, 1977.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from May, 1994 to October, 1994.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of Minister of State for Policing and the Fire Service in 1993.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of minister-president in May 12, 1985.", "John Joseph Paul holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Exports in 1983."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 159, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Britt Bager was a member of Venstre, which political party did Britt Bager belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Britt Bager is a member of the Yisrael Beiteinu from 2003 to 2015.", "Britt Bager works for Codan A/S from 1997 to 2000.", "Britt Bager is a member of the Venstre in March 23, 2021.", "Britt Bager attended University of Southern Denmark from 2010 to 2011.", "Britt Bager is a member of the National Alliance for Reconstruction in 2008.", "Britt Bager is a member of the Centre Party in May 23, 2019.", "Britt Bager holds the position of member of the Folketing from March 23, 2021 to March 22, 2021.", "Britt Bager is a member of the Comprom\u00eds from May, 2008 to November, 2009.", "Britt Bager is a member of the Conservative People's Party in March 23, 2021.", "Britt Bager attended Copenhagen Business School from 2010 to 2013."], "answer": ["Conservative People's Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 160, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Reslow was a member of Sweden Democrats, which political party did Patrick Reslow belong to concurrently?", "facts": ["Patrick Reslow is a member of the Moderate Party in May 7, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Sweden Democrats in May 7, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Red in February 19, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Russian People's Democratic Union in August 22, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Democratic Socialist Party in January, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Labour and Social Justice \u2013 The Electoral Alternative in December 13, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Catalunya en Com\u00fa in June, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Danish Social Liberal Party in October, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Politics Can Be Different in April, 2017.", "Patrick Reslow is a member of the Hungarian Socialist Workers' Party in November 4, 2017."], "answer": ["Moderate Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 161, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Gregor Helfenstein was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Gregor Helfenstein during the same time span?", "facts": ["Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of governor in April 22, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of Minister of Tourism in May 19, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of Chairman of the Council of Ministers of Bosnia and Herzegovina in August 13, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of titular bishop in October 29, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 29, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of Bishop of Grimsby in July 14, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of UNICEF Goodwill Ambassador in February, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of President of Cuba in December, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of Majority Leader of the Illinois House of Representatives in April 2, 1599.", "Gregor Helfenstein holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 1, 1599."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 162, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Francis Lodonu was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Francis Lodonu at the same time?", "facts": ["Francis Lodonu holds the position of Mayor of Christchurch in July, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of State Auditor of Mississippi in February 28, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of Minister for Youth in February 26, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of chef de cabinet in March 25, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of Chief Justice of Canada in February, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 17, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of naval officer in May 7, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of titular bishop in May 17, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of Minister of Defense in March, 1973.", "Francis Lodonu holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 29, 1973."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 163, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Paolo Piccione was working for University of S\u00e3o Paulo, which employer did Paolo Piccione work for during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Paolo Piccione attended Sapienza University of Rome in 1987.", "Paolo Piccione attended University of Florence in 1987.", "Paolo Piccione attended Scuola Normale Superiore in 2001.", "Paolo Piccione works for Institute of Mathematics and Statistics, University of S\u00e3o Paulo in March 1, 1996.", "Paolo Piccione attended Kyushu University from 2013 to 2014.", "Paolo Piccione attended Pennsylvania State University from 1987 to 1994.", "Paolo Piccione worked for University of Birmingham in 1995.", "Paolo Piccione works for University of S\u00e3o Paulo in March 1, 1996.", "Paolo Piccione attended University of Copenhagen in 1988.", "Paolo Piccione attended University of Notre Dame in 2016."], "answer": ["Institute of Mathematics and Statistics, University of S\u00e3o Paulo"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 164, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ben Nighthorse Campbell was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Ben Nighthorse Campbell belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the Janata Party in October, 1981.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the New Flemish Alliance from May, 1976 to April, 1986.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell attended Meiji University from 1960 to 1964.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the Democratic Party in March 3, 1995.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell attended San Jos\u00e9 State University in 1957.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the Libertarian Party from May 13, 1978 to May 20, 1994.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the Communist Party of Austria from March, 1961 to February, 1986.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the Red Electoral Alliance in 1964.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the People and Justice in 1959.", "Ben Nighthorse Campbell is a member of the Republican Party in March 3, 1995."], "answer": ["Republican Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 165, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Christopher Glancy was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Christopher Glancy during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Christopher Glancy holds the position of United States Secretary of Veterans Affairs in May 18, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of Minister for Consumer Affairs in October 23, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of titular bishop in February 18, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of Chief of the Naval Staff in June 26, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of Secretary of State for Health and Social Services in November 11, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 18, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 5, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of Empress of Japan in April, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of President of Turkey in April, 2012.", "Christopher Glancy holds the position of Prime Minister of Malta in May, 2012."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 166, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks at the same time?", "facts": ["Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Prime Minister of the Czech Republic in August 28, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of urban planner in January 15, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Downing Street Chief of Staff in September 19, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of titular bishop in October 25, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 10, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Secretary of State for India in August 25, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Minister-President of Saxony-Anhalt in May, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of coadjutor bishop in October 25, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Governor of \u0130stanbul in March 5, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 25, 2011."], "answer": ["coadjutor bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 167, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Michael Andrew Gielen was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Michael Andrew Gielen during the same time span?", "facts": ["Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 6, 2020.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of diocesan bishop in May 21, 2022.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of Minister of Public Works and Transport of Hungary from December 3, 2021 to December 14, 2021.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of Italian Minister of the Environment from April 16, 2022 to November 28, 2022.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 7, 2020.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of Governor of British Mauritius in 2021.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of United States Ambassador to South Africa in March, 2022.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of United States Secretary of Education from September 17, 2022 to December 19, 2022.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of United States Ambassador to Turkey in April, 2021.", "Michael Andrew Gielen holds the position of titular bishop in January 6, 2020."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 168, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Peter John Uglietto was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Peter John Uglietto at the same time?", "facts": ["Peter John Uglietto holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 14, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of United States Ambassador to Georgia in January 13, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Ely in September 25, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of Attorney General of New South Wales in July, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of President of the Republic of Lithuania in October, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of Pennsylvania Treasurer in September, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of titular bishop in June 30, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of President of Harvard University in February, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of Dean of the College of Cardinals in October 22, 2010.", "Peter John Uglietto holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 30, 2010."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 169, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Joseph Kaising was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did John Joseph Kaising within the same time interval?", "facts": ["John Joseph Kaising holds the position of mayor of Novi Sad in January 24, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Lincolnshire in March 25, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 11, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of titular bishop in February 21, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 21, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of conductor in November, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of Minister for Food, Agriculture and Fisheries in March, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of visiting scholar in April, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Finland in September 9, 2000.", "John Joseph Kaising holds the position of Regius Professor of Botany in November, 2000."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 170, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Andrew Peter Wypych was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Andrew Peter Wypych within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of Prime Minister of Egypt in October, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of Secretary of State of Maryland in May 23, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 13, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of titular bishop in June 13, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 10, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of Vice Chief of Army Staff in July 7, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of designated survivor in May 8, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of President of Italy in November 28, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of Minister for Nordic Cooperation in March, 2011.", "Andrew Peter Wypych holds the position of archpriest in February 22, 2011."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 171, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Leon Dubrawski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Leon Dubrawski concurrently?", "facts": ["Leon Dubrawski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 7, 1998.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Minister of Culture in May, 2000.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Indian state governor from June 27, 2001 to June 28, 2002.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 27, 1998.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of diocesan bishop in May 4, 2002.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of titular bishop in April 7, 1998.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Minister of Culture of Denmark in April 13, 2002.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Speaker of the Parliament of Sri Lanka from September 12, 2002 to October 20, 2002.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Cloistered Emperor from 1999 to 2000.", "Leon Dubrawski holds the position of Sadaijin from July 6, 2001 to December 28, 2001."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 172, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jeremy Thorpe was a member of Liberal Democrats, which political party did Jeremy Thorpe belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the Liberal Democrats in March 2, 1988.", "Jeremy Thorpe attended Trinity College, Oxford from October, 1948 to 1952.", "Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the Socialist People's Party of Montenegro from 1962 to 1963.", "Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the Force of the Right from November 8, 1969 to September 12, 1982.", "Jeremy Thorpe attended Eton College from 1943 to 1947.", "Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the United Socialist Party of Venezuela from May 12, 1986 to August 28, 1987.", "Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the Nationalist People's Coalition in 1974.", "Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the Liberal Party in March 2, 1988.", "Jeremy Thorpe holds the position of leader of the Liberal Party from January 18, 1967 to May 10, 1976.", "Jeremy Thorpe is a member of the Yisrael Beiteinu in 1963."], "answer": ["Liberal Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 173, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Nadine Proven\u00e7al was working for Simon Fraser University, which employer did Nadine Proven\u00e7al work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Nadine Proven\u00e7al attended McGill University from September 1, 2005 to February 1, 2013.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al worked for Metropolitan Police Department of the District of Columbia in September 18, 2003.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al worked for Great Southern and Western Railway in April, 2012.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al worked for The Lego Group in October, 2011.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al worked for Meta Platforms in 2015.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al works for Simon Fraser University in March 1, 2017.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al worked for University of Salerno in 2006.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al attended Laval University from September 1, 2001 to June 1, 2004.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al works for British Columbia's Children's Hospital in March 1, 2017.", "Nadine Proven\u00e7al worked for Great Eastern Railway from March 21, 2007 to May 22, 2014."], "answer": ["British Columbia's Children's Hospital"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 174, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Edward William Clark was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Edward William Clark during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Edward William Clark holds the position of Minister of Finance of Sri Lanka in April 18, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 26, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Minister-President of Lower Saxony in May, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 16, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Minister of State for Middle East and North Africa in October 18, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Financial Secretary in May 22, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Director-General of the World Health Organization in July, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of titular bishop in January 16, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Prime Minister of the Czech Republic in February 9, 2001.", "Edward William Clark holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of the People's Republic of China in February 18, 2001."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 175, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Huang Kuo-shu was a member of independent politician, which political party did Huang Kuo-shu belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the independent politician in October 17, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Socialist Party of Chile in November 22, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Momentum Movement in August 2, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Liberal Democrats in August, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Socialist Party of Ukraine in May 16, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Democratic Progressive Party in October 17, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Reform Progressive Party in May 23, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Austrian Freedom Party in September 23, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the MeRA25 in December 13, 2021.", "Huang Kuo-shu is a member of the Independent Greens in October 22, 2021."], "answer": ["Democratic Progressive Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 176, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Idit Silman was a member of The Jewish Home, which political party did Idit Silman belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Idit Silman is a member of the Hungarian Justice and Life Party in April, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the New Right in January 15, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the Democratic Progressive Party in August 2, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the Social Democratic Party of Switzerland in August 11, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the Ensemble Montr\u00e9al in September, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the Reiwa Shinsengumi in June 14, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the Social Liberal Party in April 21, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the African National Congress in July 10, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the Liberal and Country League of South Australia in April, 2020.", "Idit Silman is a member of the The Jewish Home in January 15, 2020."], "answer": ["New Right"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 177, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa concurrently?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of Minister of Munitions in July 1, 1989.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of charg\u00e9 d'affaires from October 16, 1987 to January 24, 1995.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 21, 1986.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 3, 1986.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of Vice-Chancellor of Germany in October 1, 1990.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of Camerlengo of the Sacred College of Cardinals in 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of emir from August, 1992 to April, 1994.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of diocesan bishop from May 8, 1991 to July 21, 1999.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of Arizona Attorney General from October 10, 1997 to December 10, 1997.", "Jos\u00e9 Alves da Costa holds the position of titular bishop in January 3, 1986."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 178, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque during the same time period?", "facts": ["Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of General Secretary of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union in June, 1990.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 6, 1969.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of High Commissioner on National Minorities from 2000 to 2003.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of European Ombudsman from 1992 to 2003.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of titular bishop in November 11, 1968.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of finance minister in March 9, 1989.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of Governor of the Banca d'Italia in September 18, 2003.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 11, 1968.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of Colorado General Assembly from May, 2000 to June, 2004.", "Adhemar Esquivel Kohenque holds the position of diocesan bishop from October 20, 1995 to June 2, 2004."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 179, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Arthur J. Serratelli was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Arthur J. Serratelli during the same time period?", "facts": ["Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of President of the Board of Trade in 2016.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 3, 2000.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Westmorland from October 11, 2018 to December 25, 2018.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of titular bishop in July 3, 2000.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 8, 2000.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of Bishop of Willesden in March 27, 2000.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of diocesan bishop from June 1, 2004 to April 15, 2020.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of Bishop of Barking in April 20, 2016.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of Second Deputy Prime Minister in October 12, 2016.", "Arthur J. Serratelli holds the position of Minister for Sport from August, 2020 to October, 2020."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 180, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Edward Kmiec was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Edward Kmiec at the same time?", "facts": ["Edward Kmiec holds the position of recorder in September, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 26, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of titular bishop in August 26, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of secretary of state in April, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of Lord Chancellor in October, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of Secretary of State for Work and Pensions in February 7, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 3, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of Attorney-General of South Australia in April 19, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of Member of the Parliament of Bangladesh in June, 1982.", "Edward Kmiec holds the position of Dean of in July, 1982."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 181, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Martin Hamilton-Smith was a member of Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division), which political party did Martin Hamilton-Smith belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Verdes Equo in 2011.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Civic Forum in 2011.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Ontario New Democratic Party from 2007 to 2009.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Liberal Democratic Congress in January, 2014.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Social Democracy Party (Turkey) in October 8, 2011.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith holds the position of Leader of the Opposition from April 12, 2007 to July 8, 2009.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia in May 27, 2014.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Forza Italia in October, 2007.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Brothers of Italy from January 2, 2013 to July 16, 2013.", "Martin Hamilton-Smith is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division) in May 27, 2014."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Australia"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 182, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Walter Nash was holding the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand, which position did Walter Nash concurrently?", "facts": ["Walter Nash holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development from December 12, 1957 to December 12, 1960.", "Walter Nash holds the position of minister of culture from June 20, 1943 to June 20, 1946.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Speaker of the Massachusetts House of Representatives from December 5, 1950 to December 17, 1951.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Nevada from September, 1935 to December, 1953.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of South Dakota in May, 1943.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs from December 12, 1957 to December 12, 1960.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of Finance from December 6, 1935 to December 13, 1949.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Supreme Allied Commander Atlantic in 1952.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of Social Development from December 13, 1938 to April 30, 1940.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand from December 12, 1957 to December 12, 1960."], "answer": ["Minister for M\u0101ori Development", "Minister of Foreign Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 183, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pierre B\u00fcrcher was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Pierre B\u00fcrcher within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of titular bishop in January 29, 1994.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of Vice President of Egypt in September 19, 2001.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of Prime Minister of Belgium from 2001 to 2010.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of Chief Secretary of New South Wales from 2007 to 2015.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 12, 1994.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 29, 1994.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of tax collector in December, 1994.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of Roman Catholic Bishop of Reykjav\u00edk from October 30, 2007 to September 18, 2015.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Energy from 2004 to 2009.", "Pierre B\u00fcrcher holds the position of Liberal Democrat Home Affairs spokesman in 2009."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 184, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pedro Xague was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Pedro Xague at the same time?", "facts": ["Pedro Xague holds the position of Minister for Veterans' Affairs in July, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Member of the Parliament of Bangladesh in August, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Minister for Defence Materiel in May 18, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Ohio Secretary of State in November 10, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of wissenschaftlicher Assistent in May 22, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of titular bishop in September 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of European Commissioner for External Relations in November, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of diocesan bishop in September 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of professor in August 1, 1560."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "diocesan bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 185, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Todd Martinez was working for Stanford University, which employer did Todd Martinez work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Todd Martinez worked for Nestl\u00e9 from October, 2003 to December, 2003.", "Todd Martinez attended Calvin University from August 1, 1985 to August 1, 1989.", "Todd Martinez attended University of California, Los Angeles from September 1, 1989 to September 1, 1994.", "Todd Martinez worked for Arkansas State University in June, 1987.", "Todd Martinez worked for Yeshiva University in March, 1987.", "Todd Martinez works for SLAC National Accelerator Laboratory in January 1, 2009.", "Todd Martinez worked for Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology from 2003 to 2008.", "Todd Martinez worked for University of Reims in June 13, 1995.", "Todd Martinez works for Stanford University in January 1, 2009.", "Todd Martinez worked for Radcliffe College from May, 2003 to February, 2005."], "answer": ["SLAC National Accelerator Laboratory"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 186, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Flores was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Patrick Flores during the same time period?", "facts": ["Patrick Flores holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Exports in 1977.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of titular bishop in March 9, 1970.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of High Commissioner of the Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands from May, 1974 to February, 1978.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of Minister for Skills and Training in 1978.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 5, 1970.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of Minister of Information in November 19, 1973.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of Conservative Chief Whip from November, 1977 to December, 1977.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of Minister for the Climate (Sweden) in December 2, 1975.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 4, 1978.", "Patrick Flores holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 9, 1970."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 187, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn during the same time period?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 19, 2002.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of diocesan bishop from January 31, 2008 to December 14, 2020.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of Controller-General of Finances in 2016.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of titular bishop in June 19, 2002.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of bishop in 2018.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Justice from 2009 to 2013.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of United States Ambassador to Nepal in 2014.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of Confederate States Secretary of War from April, 2011 to June, 2012.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Georgia from 2013 to 2015.", "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda de la Torre Mart\u00edn holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 16, 2002."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 188, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia simultaneously?", "facts": ["Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of President of Kenya from August 6, 1974 to September 27, 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of Minister for Sport and Civil Society in 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of justice of the peace in June 9, 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of United States Ambassador to Czechoslovakia in January 5, 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of Commandant of the Marine Corps in February, 1973.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of Commissioner of Health of the City of New York in 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of Commonwealth's Attorney in November 3, 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 13, 1974.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of titular bishop in November 26, 1973.", "Maur\u00edlio Jorge Quintal de Gouveia holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 26, 1973."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 189, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez at the same time?", "facts": ["Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of European Commissioner for Enlargement and European Neighbourhood Policy in April 2, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of President of the Balearic Islands in January, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of titular bishop in March 15, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of Speaker of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives in May, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of list of Bishops of Pozna\u0144 in December, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 7, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 15, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of Prime Minister of Luxembourg in May, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of New York State Engineer and Surveyor in February, 1997.", "Juan Garc\u00eda Rodr\u00edguez holds the position of Head of the Minister of Defence's military cabinet in December 11, 1997."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 190, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jean-Baptiste Gourion was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jean-Baptiste Gourion concurrently?", "facts": ["Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Under-Secretary of State for the Home Department in June 11, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 14, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 9, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Secretary for Security in December, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Chairperson of the Democratic Progressive Party in April 13, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Justice Minister of Denmark in January 14, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of titular bishop in August 14, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Chief of the General Staff in April, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of Minister for Social Protection in May, 2003.", "Jean-Baptiste Gourion holds the position of President of the Bundesrat of Germany in November 4, 2003."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 191, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pedro Xague was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Pedro Xague during the same time span?", "facts": ["Pedro Xague holds the position of Minister of Local Government and Regional Development in August, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of titular bishop in September 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of diocesan bishop in September 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Physician to the President in August 6, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Wales in May, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Minister-President of the French Community in May, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Speaker of the Landsting in May 11, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of President of the Supreme Court of the United Kingdom in April 4, 1560.", "Pedro Xague holds the position of Superintendent of Finances in June 7, 1560."], "answer": ["diocesan bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 192, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo concurrently?", "facts": ["Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 28, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Undersecretary of State in December, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Justice of the Common Pleas in February, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Minister of Education in July 16, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of president of Germany in July, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Cabinet Secretary for Education and Lifelong Learning in October 24, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 28, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of Deputy Lieutenant in August 23, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of United States Ambassador to Nigeria in October, 1564.", "Jer\u00f3nimo Clavijo holds the position of titular bishop in April 28, 1564."], "answer": ["diocesan bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 193, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of Paymaster General in October, 2007.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of diocesan bishop from June 3, 1999 to February 2, 2010.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of titular bishop in October 24, 1997.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of Postmaster General of the United Kingdom in May 24, 2001.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 8, 1998.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 24, 1997.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of Mayor of Budapest from October 20, 2000 to March 20, 2004.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of Minister for Housing from June, 2000 to September, 2009.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of President of Italy from February, 2008 to June, 2009.", "Joseph Ignace Randrianasolo holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice and Tackling Illegal Migration in July 4, 1999."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 194, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Piet Bukman was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Piet Bukman belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Piet Bukman is a member of the Green Party of Canada in August 10, 1997.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the From Five from 1989 to 1993.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the Indonesian Democratic Party \u2013 Struggle in November, 1990.", "Piet Bukman holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives from December 3, 1996 to May 19, 1998.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the Anti-Revolutionary Party in October 11, 1980.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the Communist Party of Poland in 1991.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the Bulgarian Socialist Party in 1981.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the Communist Party of Germany in May 11, 1993.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Piet Bukman is a member of the UK Independence Party from 1985 to 1986."], "answer": ["Anti-Revolutionary Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 195, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Mette Bock was holding the position of Minister of Culture of Denmark, which position did Mette Bock during the same time span?", "facts": ["Mette Bock holds the position of Minister of Culture of Denmark from November 28, 2016 to June 27, 2019.", "Mette Bock holds the position of member of the Folketing in September 15, 2011.", "Mette Bock holds the position of Princess Royal from 2009 to 2012.", "Mette Bock holds the position of Minister of Economy, Trade and Industry from 2008 to 2009.", "Mette Bock holds the position of Minister for Ecclesiastical Affairs of Denmark from November 28, 2016 to June 27, 2019.", "Mette Bock works for DR from 2008 to 2010.", "Mette Bock holds the position of United States Ambassador to Israel in January, 2007.", "Mette Bock holds the position of Groom in Waiting in 2011.", "Mette Bock holds the position of Minister for Foreign Affairs of Finland in 2007.", "Mette Bock works for Aarhus University in 2007."], "answer": ["Minister for Ecclesiastical Affairs of Denmark"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 196, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Dominik Malachowski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Dominik Malachowski concurrently?", "facts": ["Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Under-Secretary-General for Humanitarian Affairs and Emergency Relief Coordinator from January, 1528 to July, 1528.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of President of the Community of Madrid in 1528.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Minister for Health from June, 1528 to August, 1528.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Minister of Seniors in September, 1527.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 20, 1528.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Prime Minister of Tuvalu in October 27, 1527.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Chief Secretary in August 7, 1528.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of titular bishop in April 3, 1527.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of Postmaster-General of New South Wales in October 8, 1528.", "Dominik Malachowski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 3, 1527."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 197, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Giovanni Battista Businski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Giovanni Battista Businski at the same time?", "facts": ["Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of California State Controller in February 2, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of Governor of Vermont in January, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 7, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of Minister for Nordic Cooperation in May 17, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 11, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of titular bishop in March 7, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of United States Ambassador to Afghanistan in September 4, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of President of Romania in November 17, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of secretary-general in July, 1667.", "Giovanni Battista Businski holds the position of Shadow Foreign Secretary in October, 1667."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 198, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Olle Felten was a member of Sweden Democrats, which political party did Olle Felten belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Olle Felten is a member of the League of Communists of Yugoslavia in January, 2018.", "Olle Felten holds the position of member of the Swedish Riksdag from March 16, 2018 to September 24, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Alternative for Sweden in March 15, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Revolutionary Communist League in February, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Fine Gael in August, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Australian Conservatives in May 2, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Asturias Forum in June, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Centre Party in September 19, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Sweden Democrats in March 15, 2018.", "Olle Felten is a member of the Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf in June 18, 2018."], "answer": ["Alternative for Sweden"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 199, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Reg Wright was a member of independent politician, which political party did Reg Wright belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Reg Wright is a member of the independent politician in June 2, 1978.", "Reg Wright is a member of the Land and People from July, 1959 to January, 1972.", "Reg Wright is a member of the Liberal Democrats from October 13, 1962 to April 13, 1969.", "Reg Wright holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from February 22, 1950 to June 30, 1978.", "Reg Wright is a member of the Citizen and Republican Movement in 1958.", "Reg Wright is a member of the United Socialist Party of Venezuela from 1965 to 1973.", "Reg Wright is a member of the Hungarian Democratic Forum from September, 1957 to October, 1968.", "Reg Wright is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia in June 2, 1978.", "Reg Wright is a member of the Nye Borgerlige from 1962 to 1963.", "Reg Wright is a member of the National Fascist Party from 1975 to 1977."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Australia"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 200, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Michael Forbes was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did Michael Forbes belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Michael Forbes is a member of the Possible in July, 1987.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the Christian Union from May, 1993 to July, 1993.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the Republican Party in July 17, 1999.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the Change UK from December 25, 1985 to October 25, 1990.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the Democratic Party in July 17, 1999.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the Tories from February, 1994 to March, 1996.", "Michael Forbes attended State University of New York in 1983.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the The Greens in 1992.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the National Salvation Front from January, 1989 to March, 1994.", "Michael Forbes is a member of the Catalunya en Com\u00fa from April 8, 1987 to May 11, 1988."], "answer": ["Republican Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 201, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Paul Loverde was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Paul Loverde during the same time period?", "facts": ["Paul Loverde holds the position of titular bishop in February 3, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Prime Minister of North Macedonia in September 17, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Minister for Social Affairs in July, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Duke of Kent in May, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Chief Prosecutor of Hungary in August 14, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 12, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of president of Bolivia in August, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Vice-Chairperson of the National Committee of the Chinese People's Political Consultative Conference in July 2, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 3, 1988.", "Paul Loverde holds the position of Lord Speaker in June 2, 1988."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 202, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Kurt von Schleicher was holding the position of Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic, which position did Kurt von Schleicher concurrently?", "facts": ["Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Vice President of Iran in June 7, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Shadow Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster in October, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Minister in the Presidency in December, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Chancellor of Germany from December 3, 1932 to January 28, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Minister President of Prussia from December 3, 1932 to January 28, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Leader of the New Zealand Labour Party in February 4, 1932.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Bishop of Liverpool in June, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Bangladesh in July, 1932.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic from December 3, 1932 to January 28, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Minister of Defence of Hungary in June, 1932."], "answer": ["Minister President of Prussia", "Chancellor of Germany"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 203, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alberto Dahik was working for University of Guayaquil, which employer did Alberto Dahik work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Alberto Dahik works for National Congress of Ecuador from August 10, 1988 to August 9, 1992.", "Alberto Dahik works for University of Guayaquil from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik works for Escuela Superior Polit\u00e9cnica del Litoral from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik works for The Coca-Cola Company from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Morehouse College from 2014 to 2015.", "Alberto Dahik works for Universidad de Especialidades Esp\u00edritu Santo in 2015.", "Alberto Dahik is a member of the Conservative Party in July 17, 1987.", "Alberto Dahik worked for University of the District of Columbia in 2008.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Desert Research Institute in March 2, 2000.", "Alberto Dahik works for El Universo from 1981 to 1984."], "answer": ["El Universo", "The Coca-Cola Company", "Escuela Superior Polit\u00e9cnica del Litoral"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 204, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Louise Schack Elholm was holding the position of Minister for Ecclesiastical Affairs of Denmark, which position did Louise Schack Elholm during the same time span?", "facts": ["Louise Schack Elholm works for Confederation of Danish Industries from 2001 to 2005.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of Minister of Indigenous Services in March 27, 2014.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of finance minister from 2005 to 2013.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of speaker from April, 2012 to October, 2019.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of United States Secretary of Education in September, 2007.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of Minister for Nordic Co-operation in December 15, 2022.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of Italian Minister for the South and Territorial Cohesion from November, 2006 to July, 2007.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of Vice President of India from February, 2008 to January, 2018.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of Minister for Ecclesiastical Affairs of Denmark in December 15, 2022.", "Louise Schack Elholm holds the position of member of the Folketing in November 13, 2007."], "answer": ["Minister for Nordic Co-operation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 205, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Thomas Ruscher was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Thomas Ruscher during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Thomas Ruscher holds the position of High Sheriff of Berkshire from October 17, 1503 to October 25, 1503.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of Minister of Defence and Military Veterans from January, 1503 to April, 1503.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Pennsylvania in October 7, 1503.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of Administrator of the Environmental Protection Agency in December 4, 1502.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of Premier of the Western Cape in June, 1502.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of dean of Westminster in December, 1503.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of titular bishop in December 19, 1502.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of Defence Minister of Denmark in 1503.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 19, 1502.", "Thomas Ruscher holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 19, 1503."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 206, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Filippo Santoro was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Filippo Santoro at the same time?", "facts": ["Filippo Santoro holds the position of diocesan bishop in May 12, 2004.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 10, 1996.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of Minister for Community Safety and Legal Affairs from July 10, 1998 to August 22, 2000.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of Commendatory abbot from 1999 to 2002.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of First Lord of the Admiralty in November 9, 1999.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of titular bishop in April 10, 1996.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 29, 1996.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of minister-president from July 27, 2002 to July 28, 2002.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of Minister of State for Trade in May, 1998.", "Filippo Santoro holds the position of bishop in 2004."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 207, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While J. Terry Steib was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did J. Terry Steib concurrently?", "facts": ["J. Terry Steib holds the position of Mayor of New York City from May, 2007 to February, 2016.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of Assistant Secretary of Defense for International Security Affairs in 2001.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of Director of Immigration from July 25, 1995 to January 26, 2003.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 6, 1983.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of Governor of Rhode Island in November 19, 2002.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of Deputy Premier of Victoria from 2012 to 2015.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of titular bishop in December 6, 1983.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 24, 1993 to August 23, 2016.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 10, 1984.", "J. Terry Steib holds the position of King of Albania in November 7, 2004."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 208, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Silvano Piovanelli was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Silvano Piovanelli during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 24, 1982.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Employment in 1983.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of President of Finland in September, 1982.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of cardinal in May 25, 1985.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of Liberal Democrat Frontbench Team in April 20, 1985.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of Minister for the Cabinet Office from May 12, 1983 to January 18, 1985.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of Minister for Health of Denmark in 1985.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 28, 1982.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of city manager in September, 1984.", "Silvano Piovanelli holds the position of titular bishop in May 28, 1982."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 209, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Ontario New Democratic Party in December 14, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Anti-Revolutionary Party in October 11, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Green Italy in April 8, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Freedom Movement in August, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Christian Historical Union in April 1, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the La France insoumise in April, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Social Democratic Party of Germany in June 10, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Ecologist Green Party of Mexico in August 2, 1980.", "Isa\u00e4c Arend Diepenhorst is a member of the Cidadania in September, 1980."], "answer": ["Anti-Revolutionary Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 210, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Julio Parise Loro was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Julio Parise Loro simultaneously?", "facts": ["Julio Parise Loro holds the position of Master-General of the Ordnance in January, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of Federal Chancellor of Germany in September, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of Speaker of the United States House of Representatives in April 18, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of volunteer in August, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of titular bishop in October 5, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 8, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of music director in January 10, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of Vice President of Venezuela in February 4, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 5, 1974.", "Julio Parise Loro holds the position of Minister of Education and Research in March, 1974."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 211, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Bob Such was a member of independent politician, which political party did Bob Such belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Bob Such is a member of the Country Liberal Party in November, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the The Olive Tree in December, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia in October 12, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the independent politician in October 12, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the National Salvation Party in July 22, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the One NL in November 2, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Hungarian Working People's Party in November 6, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Democratic Party \u2013 demokraci.pl in September 15, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division) in October 12, 2000.", "Bob Such is a member of the Italian Socialist Party in July, 2000."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division)", "Liberal Party of Australia"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 212, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Andrzej Iwanecki was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Andrzej Iwanecki simultaneously?", "facts": ["Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Special Rapporteur on human rights in Iran in August, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of titular bishop in January 7, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 7, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Secretary of State of Texas in December, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Mayor of San Francisco in November, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 7, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Prime Minister of Serbia in November 15, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Deputy President of the Supreme Court of the United Kingdom in March, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Attorney General of Sri Lanka in April 5, 2018.", "Andrzej Iwanecki holds the position of Vice President of the Comoros in August, 2018."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 213, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Peter Binsfeld was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Peter Binsfeld simultaneously?", "facts": ["Peter Binsfeld holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Delaware from October 1, 1581 to November 26, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Transportation in May 23, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of titular bishop in February 12, 1580.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 2, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of Magistrate of Taipei County from April, 1581 to July, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of counsel in February, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of Metropolitan Police Department of the District of Columbia Chief in February 8, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives of the Philippines from July 7, 1581 to August 23, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of United States Ambassador to Venezuela from May, 1581 to August, 1581.", "Peter Binsfeld holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 12, 1580."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 214, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Dante Bernini was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Dante Bernini during the same time span?", "facts": ["Dante Bernini holds the position of Commonwealth Chairperson-in-Office in September, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 8, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of Minister of State for Children in July 1, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of titular bishop in October 30, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of Governor of Hawaii in January, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Ohio in September, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of Mayor of Budapest in July, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 30, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of Deputy First Minister of Scotland in April 16, 1971.", "Dante Bernini holds the position of puisne judge in November 1, 1971."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 215, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Governor of Massachusetts in December 10, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Prime Minister of Laos in May 17, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs of Georgia in October 25, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 9, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Lord Chancellor of France in December, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Bishop of Dover in August 8, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Minister for Social Services in August, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of titular bishop in September 18, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 18, 2019.", "Aleksander Jaz\u0142owiecki holds the position of Deputy Lieutenant in November, 2019."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 216, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jens Orback was holding the position of Minister for Gender Equality Affairs, which position did Jens Orback during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jens Orback holds the position of President of the South Australian Legislative Council from 2012 to 2013.", "Jens Orback holds the position of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party from July, 2014 to December, 2015.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Minister of Democracy from October 21, 2004 to October 6, 2006.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Sterling Professor in 2015.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Chairman of the National Public Safety Commission in November, 2016.", "Jens Orback holds the position of general secretary from 2008 to 2016.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Minister for Gender Equality Affairs from October 21, 2004 to October 6, 2006.", "Jens Orback holds the position of prime minister in January 15, 2011.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Secretary of State for Scotland from December, 2012 to February, 2014.", "Jens Orback holds the position of Minister for Integration from October 21, 2004 to October 6, 2006."], "answer": ["Minister for Integration", "Minister of Democracy"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 217, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Barry Urban was a member of independent politician, which political party did Barry Urban belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Barry Urban is a member of the Democratic Left in December, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Czech Social Democratic Party in September 15, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Swedish Social Democratic Party in May 1, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Ahora Madrid in April, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Eniaion in February 18, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the independent politician in November 29, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Communist Refoundation Party in May, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Russian People's Democratic Union in April 3, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Western Australian Labor Party in November 29, 2017.", "Barry Urban is a member of the Khmer Renovation in January 8, 2017."], "answer": ["Western Australian Labor Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 218, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Matteo Maria Zuppi was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Matteo Maria Zuppi during the same time span?", "facts": ["Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of President pro tempore of the Union of South American Nations in December, 2016.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 14, 2012.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of auxiliary bishop of Rome in January 31, 2012.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of Minister of State for Overseas Development in December, 2013.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of Lord Chief Justice of Ireland in September, 2014.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of Minister for Sport and Civil Society from May 9, 2017 to November 13, 2019.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of engineer in June 20, 2015.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of cardinal in October 5, 2019.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of titular bishop in January 31, 2012.", "Matteo Maria Zuppi holds the position of Vice President of the Federated States of Micronesia in May 1, 2017."], "answer": ["auxiliary bishop of Rome"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 219, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Vincenzo Savio was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Vincenzo Savio at the same time?", "facts": ["Vincenzo Savio holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Singapore from September 1, 1998 to October 8, 1998.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of titular bishop in April 14, 1993.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of diocesan bishop in December 9, 2000.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of patriarch from November 7, 1994 to August 12, 1995.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of Plumian Professor of Astronomy and Experimental Philosophy from September 13, 1998 to October 26, 1998.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 14, 1993.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of the Netherlands in May, 1997.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of Vice President of the People's Republic of China from July, 1996 to January, 1999.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of Vice Chief of Naval Operations from September, 1997 to September, 1999.", "Vincenzo Savio holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 30, 1993."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 220, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jean Tulard was working for Sciences Po, which employer did Jean Tulard work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Jean Tulard worked for Mus\u00e9um national d'histoire naturelle in 1980.", "Jean Tulard worked for New Economic School in May 20, 1976.", "Jean Tulard worked for Writers Union of Armenia in December 24, 1980.", "Jean Tulard worked for Sofia University in 1974.", "Jean Tulard holds the position of president from 1973 to 1977.", "Jean Tulard holds the position of president from 1974 to 1999.", "Jean Tulard works for Paris-Sorbonne University - Paris IV from 1981 to 2001.", "Jean Tulard works for Sciences Po from 1981 to 2001.", "Jean Tulard worked for Freie Universit\u00e4t Berlin in September, 1980.", "Jean Tulard worked for Duke University School of Law in April, 1976."], "answer": ["Paris-Sorbonne University - Paris IV"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 221, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Miguel Avell\u00e1n was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Miguel Avell\u00e1n within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Minister for Aboriginal Affairs in March, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Captain of the Honourable Corps of Gentlemen-at-Arms in December 14, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Commonwealth Secretary-General in December 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Bishop of London in October, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Vice-Chancellor of the Crown in August, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Governor of New Hampshire in January 18, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of titular bishop in June 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of President of Nauru in August, 1633."], "answer": ["Catholic bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 222, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Shuli Mualem was a member of The Jewish Home, which political party did Shuli Mualem belong to during the same time period?", "facts": ["Shuli Mualem is a member of the Progress Party in April 15, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the Party of Hope in August, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the Alliance 90 in November, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the Fine Gael in March, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the United Socialist Party of Venezuela in February 1, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the New Right in December 29, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the The Jewish Home in December 29, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the Ensemble Montr\u00e9al in December 23, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the Congress of the New Right in February, 2018.", "Shuli Mualem is a member of the National Advancement Party in May, 2018."], "answer": ["New Right"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 223, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Tjerk Westerterp was a member of Christian Democratic Appeal, which political party did Tjerk Westerterp belong to concurrently?", "facts": ["Tjerk Westerterp holds the position of member of the European Parliament from May 8, 1967 to August 17, 1971.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Jubilee Party of Kenya in 1985.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Catholic People's Party in October 11, 1980.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Les Centristes in March, 1997.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Humanist Power Party in 1982.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal in October 11, 1980.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Samajwadi Janata Party in January 9, 1970.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Free-minded Liberal Party from September 24, 1990 to July 24, 2000.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Hummat in November, 1982.", "Tjerk Westerterp is a member of the Livable Netherlands in 2002."], "answer": ["Catholic People's Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 224, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Timothy C. Senior was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Timothy C. Senior at the same time?", "facts": ["Timothy C. Senior holds the position of European Commissioner for Transport in February, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of Minister of State for Security in April 14, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of Marshal of the Sejm in April, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 31, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of preacher in July, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of Metropolitan Police Department of the District of Columbia Chief in December, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of Minister for Veterans' Affairs in February, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 8, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of Secretary for Relations with States in November, 2009.", "Timothy C. Senior holds the position of titular bishop in June 8, 2009."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 225, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez simultaneously?", "facts": ["Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 20, 1968.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 19, 1942.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of Attorney General of Kentucky from September 25, 1957 to March 27, 1966.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of President of El Salvador from 1947 to 1963.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of Minister for Fair Trading in November 20, 1968.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Cornwall in November, 1961.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of patriarch in May 9, 1943.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of Co-ordinating Minister for National Security in June 21, 1957.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of titular bishop in May 20, 1968.", "Jorge Manuel L\u00f3pez holds the position of Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia from 1963 to 1967."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 226, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Zurek was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Patrick Zurek during the same time span?", "facts": ["Patrick Zurek holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 5, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Minister of State for Energy in June, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Member of the Legislative Yuan in May 2, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of titular bishop in January 5, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Minister of State for Transport in June 14, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Coordinator for Counterterrorism in April, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Archdeacon of London in September, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 16, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Governor of Kaluga Oblast in June, 1998.", "Patrick Zurek holds the position of Keeper of the Seals of France in August, 1998."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 227, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Karl Borsch was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Karl Borsch during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Karl Borsch holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 17, 2004.", "Karl Borsch attended University of Bonn from 1979 to 1985.", "Karl Borsch attended Sankt Georgen Graduate School of Philosophy and Theology from 1985 to 1990.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Home Secretary from March 20, 1995 to February 26, 2003.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Shadow Leader of the House of Commons in December, 1996.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of heir presumptive from June, 1979 to March, 1994.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of wing commander from December 23, 1991 to December 23, 2001.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Commanding General of the United States Army from April, 1982 to October, 1995.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of titular bishop in January 17, 2004.", "Karl Borsch holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 17, 2004."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 228, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Francisco Cases Andreu was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Francisco Cases Andreu within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 22, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of United States Secretary of State in November, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of Confederate States Secretary of War in August, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of First Secretary of the Communist Party of Cuba in March, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of titular bishop in February 22, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of Chief Rabbinate of Israel in August 2, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of President of Italy in April 12, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 10, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of Lord Commissioner of the Treasury in July 28, 1994.", "Francisco Cases Andreu holds the position of minister of Families, Children and Social Development in October, 1994."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 229, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Scott Andrews was a member of independent politician, which political party did Scott Andrews belong to during the same time period?", "facts": ["Scott Andrews is a member of the Christian Social Party in January, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the independent politician in November 5, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Cidadania in May, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Tahya Tounes in February, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Socialist Movement of Catalonia in September 21, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Progress Party in October, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Liberal Party of Canada in November 5, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Our Land in February, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Peoples Democratic Party in August, 2014.", "Scott Andrews is a member of the Polska Razem in June, 2014."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Canada"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 230, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Martin Luluga was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Martin Luluga within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Martin Luluga holds the position of President of India in June 18, 1986.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of Minister responsible for the Federal Economic Development Initiative for Northern Ontario in January 11, 1986.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of titular bishop in October 17, 1986.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 11, 1987.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 17, 1986.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of Member of Provincial Parliament of Western Cape in February, 1987.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of Mayor of Dallas, Texas in 1987.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of Treasurer of Western Australia in August, 1987.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of general in May 19, 1986.", "Martin Luluga holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Energy and Climate Change in June, 1987."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 231, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas concurrently?", "facts": ["Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of Minister-President of Saxony-Anhalt in 1990.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of titular bishop in April 26, 1979.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of pr\u00e9sident-directeur g\u00e9n\u00e9ral from 1981 to 1992.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of United States Ambassador to Sudan from 2011 to 2014.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 1, 1989 to January 15, 2014.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs of Georgia from 1997 to 2004.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 27, 1979.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of First Lady of the United States in 1991.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of Member of the National Assembly of Pakistan in June 11, 2003.", "Ram\u00f3n L\u00f3pez Carrozas holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 26, 1979."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 232, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Madhav Kumar Nepal was holding the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Nepal, which position did Madhav Kumar Nepal at the same time?", "facts": ["Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Deputy Leader of the Conservative Party from May, 2000 to September, 2008.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs from November 30, 1994 to September 12, 1995.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Prime Minister of Nepal from May 25, 2009 to February 6, 2011.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Deputy National Security Advisor in 2010.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Ministry of the Overseas from January, 2006 to January, 2008.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of President of Fiji in June 16, 2011.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Nepal from November 30, 1994 to September 12, 1995.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Lord Marshal (Sweden) in September, 2006.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of President of Vietnam from July, 1998 to May, 2008.", "Madhav Kumar Nepal holds the position of Minister for Lands from June 26, 2001 to March 26, 2007."], "answer": ["Minister of Foreign Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 233, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Thomas J. Paprocki was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Thomas J. Paprocki concurrently?", "facts": ["Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of Chairman of the Chiefs of Staff Committee from October 4, 2004 to December 17, 2004.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 19, 2003.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of Lord Marshal (Sweden) from October 16, 2004 to December 20, 2004.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Scotland in May, 2004.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of Minister for the purposes of the Atlantic Canada Opportunities Agency Act in June, 2010.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 24, 2003.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of President of Ireland in April, 2003.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of titular bishop in January 24, 2003.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 20, 2010.", "Thomas J. Paprocki holds the position of Bishop of Mauritius in November, 2004."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 234, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Henryk Tomasik was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Henryk Tomasik within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Henryk Tomasik holds the position of diocesan bishop from October 16, 2009 to January 4, 2021.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 21, 1992.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Resident Commissioner of the Philippines in November, 2008.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Chancellery of the President of the Republic of Poland in April 19, 2000.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of titular bishop in November 21, 1992.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of United States Secretary of Labor from May, 2016 to September, 2018.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 21, 1992.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of sub-prefect from August 3, 2012 to September 6, 2017.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of public prosecutor general in 2008.", "Henryk Tomasik holds the position of Mayor of Taoyuan in July, 1996."], "answer": ["Catholic bishop", "auxiliary bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 235, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Rosendo Huesca Pacheco was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Rosendo Huesca Pacheco within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of titular bishop in May 30, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of Bishop of South Tokyo in December, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of United States Ambassador to Cuba in December, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 24, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of Permanent representative of Spain to the European Union in July, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of Bishop of Grimsby in March 11, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 30, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of state's attorney in June 16, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of Prince-Elector in December 15, 1970.", "Rosendo Huesca Pacheco holds the position of Regius Professor of History in January, 1970."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 236, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While John Yanta was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did John Yanta within the same time interval?", "facts": ["John Yanta holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Defence in March 19, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 27, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of Prince-Elector in December 17, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of artist-in-residence in August 28, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 30, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of titular bishop in October 27, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of monarch of Scotland in September, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of Colonial Secretary in September, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of Deputy Attorney General in March, 1994.", "John Yanta holds the position of Bishop of Liverpool in May 4, 1994."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 237, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Wincenty Lipski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Wincenty Lipski during the same time span?", "facts": ["Wincenty Lipski holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Veterans Affairs in October 14, 1857.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of foreign minister from January, 1857 to July, 1857.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of list of Governors of Natal from August, 1857 to December, 1857.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of Downing Street Chief of Staff from February 1, 1857 to December 28, 1857.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of titular bishop in September 18, 1856.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of Director of Central Intelligence in April, 1856.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 9, 1857.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of Prime Minister of Laos in November 7, 1856.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of President of Zimbabwe in January, 1856.", "Wincenty Lipski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 18, 1856."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 238, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Antonio Moreno Casamitjana was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Antonio Moreno Casamitjana during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of Supreme Commander of the Swedish Armed Forces in March 4, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of speaker in September, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of Chief of Army in May 18, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of Grand Master of the Teutonic Knights in July 16, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of Governor of Oklahoma in February, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of titular bishop in April 22, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 9, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of the Treasury in February, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 22, 1986.", "Antonio Moreno Casamitjana holds the position of Secretary of State of West Virginia in May, 1986."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 239, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joseph Oliver Bowers was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Joseph Oliver Bowers during the same time period?", "facts": ["Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 27, 1952.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of Minister of Petroleum and Energy in January 15, 1953.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of Leader of the Conservative Party in 1953.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of Prime Minister of Laos in May 10, 1952.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of United States Ambassador to Vietnam in January 10, 1953.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of titular bishop in November 27, 1952.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of Assistant Secretary of State for Legislative Affairs in March, 1953.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of Minister of Home Affairs (Bangladesh) in December, 1953.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of President pro tempore of the Senate of the Philippines in November 6, 1953.", "Joseph Oliver Bowers holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 22, 1953."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 240, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ladislau Biernaski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Ladislau Biernaski during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of mayor of Tallinn in April, 1982.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 19, 1979.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of Prime Minister of Yemen in September 21, 1997.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of court painter from October 2, 1999 to October 12, 1999.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of titular bishop in April 19, 1979.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of Warsaw City Council in December 16, 1995.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 27, 1979.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of Minister of Natural Resources in November, 1994.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of Norway in September, 2005.", "Ladislau Biernaski holds the position of diocesan bishop in December 6, 2006."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 241, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Brendan Comiskey was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Brendan Comiskey concurrently?", "facts": ["Brendan Comiskey holds the position of State Auditor of Missouri from 2000 to 2002.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of Ministry of Public Administration and Home Affairs in 1997.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of Minister of State for Schools and Childhood from October, 1993 to April, 1998.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of Governor of Colorado from May 1, 1980 to May 17, 1990.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 3, 1979.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of titular bishop in December 3, 1979.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of Cabinet Secretary for Justice from 1988 to 1994.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic in February, 1995.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 20, 1980.", "Brendan Comiskey holds the position of diocesan bishop from April 4, 1984 to April 6, 2002."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 242, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy was holding the position of Prime Minister of Pakistan, which position did Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy concurrently?", "facts": ["Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of Defence Minister of Pakistan from September 12, 1956 to October 17, 1957.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of Prime Minister of Bengal from July 3, 1946 to August 14, 1947.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of dean in 1931.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of President of Russia from 1923 to 1945.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of Secretary for the Civil Service in June, 1938.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of Prime Minister of Pakistan from September 12, 1956 to October 17, 1957.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of High Sheriff of Berkshire from July 10, 1949 to February 24, 1954.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of Mayor of Manila in December 6, 1944.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy is a member of the All India Muslim League from 1920 to 1947.", "Huseyn Shaheed Suhrawardy holds the position of charg\u00e9 d'affaires in 1929."], "answer": ["Defence Minister of Pakistan"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 243, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pralhad Joshi was holding the position of Minister of Coal, which position did Pralhad Joshi concurrently?", "facts": ["Pralhad Joshi holds the position of b\u00e2tonnier in March 7, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Minister of Coal in May 30, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of President of the Xunta of Galicia in December 6, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of President of the French Republic in October 3, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Minister of Parliamentary Affairs in May 30, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Minister of Mines in May 30, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Chief Minister of Malacca in August 1, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of United States Ambassador to the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development in November 27, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Governor-General of the Philippines in January, 2019.", "Pralhad Joshi holds the position of Premier of the Free State in January, 2019."], "answer": ["Minister of Parliamentary Affairs", "Minister of Mines"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 244, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Archie Norman was holding the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which position did Archie Norman concurrently?", "facts": ["Archie Norman holds the position of president of Lazio in November, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Holy Roman Emperor in December, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of colonel in December, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Transport from February 2, 2000 to September 18, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Daij\u014d Tenn\u014d in October 5, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government from February 2, 2000 to September 18, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Minister of Munitions in October, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for International Development in November 6, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Minister for Migration in October, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs from February 2, 2000 to September 18, 2001."], "answer": ["Shadow Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government", "Shadow Secretary of State for Transport"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 245, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Micha\u0142 Kalecki was working for University of Warsaw, which employer did Micha\u0142 Kalecki work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for University of Adelaide in 1946.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki works for University of Warsaw from 1956 to 1968.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for University of Burgundy in March, 1943.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for United States Environmental Protection Agency in January, 1943.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for Mshak from May, 1947 to August, 1951.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki works for SGH Warsaw School of Economics from 1956 to 1968.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for Politehnica University of Bucharest in August 7, 1947.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for Barnard College in January 8, 1951.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki worked for Swansea University in 1944.", "Micha\u0142 Kalecki works for University of Oxford from 1940 to 1945."], "answer": ["SGH Warsaw School of Economics"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 246, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Romina Pourmokhtari was holding the position of Minister for the Environment, which position did Romina Pourmokhtari at the same time?", "facts": ["Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of President of the National Council of Austria in July, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of minister in January 2, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Minister for the Climate (Sweden) in October 18, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Regius Professor of History in October 17, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Minister of Fisheries and Oceans in August 2, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Minister for the Environment in October 18, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Defence Minister of Denmark in March 24, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Minister for Immigration and Border Protection of Australia in April, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of Chief Minister of France in August 22, 2022.", "Romina Pourmokhtari holds the position of member of the Swedish Riksdag from September 26, 2022 to October 18, 2022."], "answer": ["Minister for the Climate (Sweden)"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 247, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luca Regli was working for University of Zurich, which employer did Luca Regli work for during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Luca Regli worked for MIT Lincoln Laboratory from December 2, 2010 to January 5, 2011.", "Luca Regli worked for Pennsylvania Railroad from December 27, 2008 to July 27, 2011.", "Luca Regli worked for Ministry of Works in 2010.", "Luca Regli worked for University of Puerto Rico from August, 2008 to April, 2011.", "Luca Regli works for University Medical Center Utrecht from April 1, 2008 to September 30, 2012.", "Luca Regli worked for Maryland Institute College of Art in January, 2011.", "Luca Regli worked for The Royal Conservatory of Music in February 7, 2012.", "Luca Regli works for University Hospital Zurich in October 1, 2012.", "Luca Regli worked for Hampton University in 2010.", "Luca Regli works for University of Zurich in October 1, 2012."], "answer": ["University Hospital Zurich"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 248, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks during the same time period?", "facts": ["Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of coadjutor bishop in October 25, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 10, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Amir al-Mu'minin in January, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of duke in September, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 25, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of President of Cyprus in December, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Prime Minister of Belarus in October 26, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of project manager in February, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of titular bishop in October 25, 2011.", "Johannes Willibrordus Maria Hendriks holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of the People's Republic of China in January, 2011."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "coadjutor bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 249, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Robert Ling Kui Ee was a member of independent politician, which political party did Robert Ling Kui Ee belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the National Renaissance Front in July 11, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the People's Movement Party in July, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the independent politician in May 12, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the Rashtriya Janata Dal in June, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the Australian Conservatives in July, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the Real Politics Union in November, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the People's National Congress Party in February 4, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the Swedish Social Democratic Party in November, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the People's Justice Party in May 12, 2020.", "Robert Ling Kui Ee is a member of the Reform Party in March 24, 2020."], "answer": ["People's Justice Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 250, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Johannes Bluyssen was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Johannes Bluyssen during the same time span?", "facts": ["Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 27, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of Secretary of State for the Northern Department in March 9, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of Supreme Allied Commander Europe in December, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of antipope in March, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of titular bishop in October 28, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of executive officer in May 1, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of Attorney General of Kentucky in April 23, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of Leader of the Christian Democratic Union in June, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of Minister of Human Settlements in September, 1961.", "Johannes Bluyssen holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 28, 1961."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 251, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s during the same time period?", "facts": ["Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of President of the Senate of Romania from March 14, 2000 to November 21, 2000.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of National Congress of Ecuador from July, 1998 to December, 2004.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of Lord Chamberlain from May 13, 1994 to June 28, 2000.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of Chief Whip from February, 2002 to July, 2002.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Wales in January, 1992.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 5, 1992.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of diocesan bishop from January 24, 1998 to December 13, 2006.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of dean from November 22, 1996 to February 23, 1997.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 16, 1991.", "Carlos Jes\u00fas Patricio Baladr\u00f3n Vald\u00e9s holds the position of titular bishop in November 16, 1991."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 252, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Katy Gallagher was holding the position of Minister for Finance of Australia, which position did Katy Gallagher during the same time period?", "facts": ["Katy Gallagher holds the position of Minister for Finance of Australia in May 23, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Archdeacon of Canterbury in August 14, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives of the Philippines in October, 2017.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Montana from 2003 to 2009.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs from September 1, 2012 to July 11, 2013.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Minister for the Status of Women in May 23, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Attorney-General for Australia in May 23, 2022.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Bishop of Clogher in 2011.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of member of the Australian Capital Territory Legislative Assembly from October 20, 2001 to December 23, 2014.", "Katy Gallagher holds the position of Chief Minister of the Australian Capital Territory from May 16, 2011 to December 11, 2014."], "answer": ["Attorney-General for Australia", "Minister for the Status of Women"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 253, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While William G. Curlin was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did William G. Curlin within the same time interval?", "facts": ["William G. Curlin holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 2, 1988.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of titular bishop in November 2, 1988.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of Minister of Transport and Communications from December 16, 2002 to December 23, 2002.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of United States Ambassador to Ivory Coast from December, 1996 to April, 2002.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 20, 1988.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of parliamentary group leader in October, 2001.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Labor in November 7, 1988.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of diocesan bishop from February 22, 1994 to September 10, 2002.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of Chief of the Romanian General Staff from June, 2001 to December, 2002.", "William G. Curlin holds the position of Minister of Road Transport and Highways in August 2, 1993."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 254, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Archie Norman was holding the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Transport, which position did Archie Norman during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Archie Norman holds the position of Counselor to the President in October, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Minister of State for Housing in September 20, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Northern Ireland in January 11, 2000.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Newfoundland and Labrador in January 13, 2000.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Intendant des finances in December 23, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs from February 2, 2000 to September 18, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Hungary in December 5, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of United States Ambassador to Benin in November, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Transport from February 2, 2000 to September 18, 2001.", "Archie Norman holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government from February 2, 2000 to September 18, 2001."], "answer": ["Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "Shadow Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 255, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Adrian van Walenburch was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Adrian van Walenburch within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of Minister for Communications, Urban Infrastructure, Cities and the Arts in April, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of President of Hungary in March 20, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of titular bishop in August 8, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of President of Romania in May 12, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of President pro tempore of the Union of South American Nations in September 21, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of ambassador of Ukraine to Finland in September, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of Secretary of State for Scotland in May, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Defence in March, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 30, 1661.", "Adrian van Walenburch holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 8, 1661."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 256, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luigi Barlassina was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Luigi Barlassina during the same time span?", "facts": ["Luigi Barlassina holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 9, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of United States Deputy Attorney General in December, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of Prime Minister of Afghanistan in January, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of United States representative in September 12, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of non-voting member of the U.S. House of Representatives in December, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of Prime Minister of Malta in November 1, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of titular bishop in August 9, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of Magistrate of Miaoli County in September 1, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 8, 1918.", "Luigi Barlassina holds the position of Minister for Agriculture in January 1, 1918."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 257, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Philip Joseph Philbin was holding the position of campaign manager, which position did Philip Joseph Philbin at the same time?", "facts": ["Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of secretary from 1921 to 1940.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Slovenia in August, 1920.", "Philip Joseph Philbin attended Harvard University in 1920.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of Minister of Agriculture of Hungary from March 12, 1920 to June 19, 1920.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of monarch of the United Kingdom in August 9, 1920.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of Chairperson of the Democratic Progressive Party in July, 1920.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of consul in June 6, 1920.", "Philip Joseph Philbin attended Columbia Law School in 1924.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of campaign manager from 1921 to 1940.", "Philip Joseph Philbin holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Nottinghamshire in January 20, 1920."], "answer": ["secretary"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 258, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Reginald Weaver was holding the position of Minister for Forests, which position did Reginald Weaver simultaneously?", "facts": ["Reginald Weaver holds the position of Minister for Forests from April 16, 1929 to November 3, 1930.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the Liberal Reform Party in 1913.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Minister for Mines from April 16, 1929 to November 3, 1930.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Secretary for Public Works from May 16, 1932 to February 10, 1935.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the Nationalist Party of Australia from 1917 to 1931.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Speaker of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly from August 4, 1937 to May 27, 1941.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the United Australia Party from 1931 to 1943.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Minister for Health from May 16, 1932 to February 10, 1935.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia (New South Wales Division) in 1945.", "Reginald Weaver holds the position of Leader of the Opposition from February 10, 1944 to November 12, 1945.", "Reginald Weaver is a member of the National Party of Australia \u2013 NSW from 1913 to 1917."], "answer": ["Minister for Mines"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 259, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Robert William Muench was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Robert William Muench within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Robert William Muench holds the position of titular bishop in May 8, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Minister for Home Affairs in July, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Secretary of the Central Military Commission of the Communist Party of Vietnam in November, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Chairman of the Senate of Pakistan in August, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Treasurer of Arkansas in January 13, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 29, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Postmaster General of the United Kingdom in October 14, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of Lord High Steward of Sweden in January, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 8, 1990.", "Robert William Muench holds the position of deputy head teacher in April 28, 1990."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 260, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Tulsi Gabbard was a member of independent politician, which political party did Tulsi Gabbard belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the Falange Nacional in March, 2018.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the Fasci Italiani di Combattimento from March, 2020 to November, 2020.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the Democratic Party in October 11, 2022.", "Tulsi Gabbard holds the position of council member from 2010 to 2012.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the independent politician in October 11, 2022.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the Europe Ecology \u2013 The Greens in May 26, 2017.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the People Power Party in March 18, 2013.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the Democratic Alliance in October, 2020.", "Tulsi Gabbard is a member of the Revolutionary Left Front in February 8, 2021.", "Tulsi Gabbard attended Hawaii Pacific University in 2009."], "answer": ["Democratic Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 261, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Seiji Maehara was a member of independent politician, which political party did Seiji Maehara belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Seiji Maehara holds the position of Minister for Foreign Affairs from September 17, 2010 to March 7, 2011.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the Democratic Party (Japan, 2016) in November 2, 2017.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the Democratic Union in August 21, 2010.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the Samajwadi Janata Party from 2010 to 2011.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the Japan Restoration Party in 2010.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the United Left in February, 2015.", "Seiji Maehara holds the position of Minister of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism from September 16, 2009 to September 17, 2010.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the Italian Social Movement - National Right from June 2, 2012 to March 12, 2016.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the independent politician in November 2, 2017.", "Seiji Maehara is a member of the Falange Espa\u00f1ola Tradicionalista y de las JONS in 2011."], "answer": ["Democratic Party (Japan, 2016)"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 262, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Francesco Maria Macchiavelli was holding the position of Catholic bishop, which position did Francesco Maria Macchiavelli during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of state attorney general in August 19, 1640.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of Speaker of the Knesset from March, 1640 to August, 1640.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of cardinal in December 16, 1641.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of High Commissioner from July 20, 1639 to November 24, 1640.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 11, 1638.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Hungary in April, 1640.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of diocesan bishop in October 11, 1638.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of First Lady of Bangladesh in January, 1640.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of United States senator in November, 1639.", "Francesco Maria Macchiavelli holds the position of President of the European Commission in 1641."], "answer": ["diocesan bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 263, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Lucy Gichuhi was a member of Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division), which political party did Lucy Gichuhi belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the Occident from February 22, 2019 to September 24, 2019.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the Family First Party in May 3, 2017.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the New Democratic Party in October, 2018.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the Democratic Liberal Party in 2019.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the New Party in November 18, 2018.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the Catalan Solidarity in December, 2017.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia in February 2, 2018.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the Liberal Party of Australia (South Australian Division) in February 2, 2018.", "Lucy Gichuhi is a member of the New Azerbaijan Party in May, 2018.", "Lucy Gichuhi holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from April 19, 2017 to June 30, 2019."], "answer": ["Liberal Party of Australia"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 264, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Aloysius John Wycislo was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Aloysius John Wycislo during the same time span?", "facts": ["Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 21, 1960.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 7, 1960.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of Minister of Veterans Affairs from August 10, 1981 to January 20, 1982.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of Prime Minister of the Faroe Islands from 1961 to 1980.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of titular bishop in October 7, 1960.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of President of Honduras in March 27, 1960.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of Executive Secretary of the United States Department of State from October 24, 1973 to June 27, 1979.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of Minister of Consumer Affairs, Food and Public Distribution from May 3, 1966 to February 8, 1980.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of diocesan bishop from March 4, 1968 to May 10, 1983.", "Aloysius John Wycislo holds the position of mayor of Novi Sad in May, 1976."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 265, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva during the same time period?", "facts": ["M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 9, 2010.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of Minister for Information Technology in April 23, 2016.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of diocesan bishop in June 22, 2016.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of member of congress in August, 2011.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of writer in November 3, 2010.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of Lord Chancellor of France in 2012.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of chairperson of the board in March 10, 2016.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of titular bishop in June 9, 2010.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of chef de cabinet from 2012 to 2016.", "M\u00e1rio Ant\u00f4nio da Silva holds the position of Catholic bishop in August 20, 2010."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 266, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba at the same time?", "facts": ["Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of diocesan bishop in July 16, 1991.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of titular bishop in October 20, 1984.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of President pro tempore of the United States Senate from March 2, 1990 to December 15, 2009.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of district attorney in November, 2008.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 20, 1984.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of President of the Council of Ministers of Peru from July 12, 1991 to March 23, 2011.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of cardinal in February 14, 2015.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 22, 1984.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Enterprise, Trade and Employment from December 18, 1994 to December 26, 2007.", "Luis H\u00e9ctor Villalba holds the position of Administrator of the Environmental Protection Agency from January 7, 2008 to January 22, 2013."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 267, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi during the same time span?", "facts": ["Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of Secretary of the Central Commission for Discipline Inspection in April 7, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 22, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of Dean of Windsor in April 24, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of Department for International Development in September, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of Governor of Jalisco in June, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of auxiliary bishop in May 22, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of mayor of Rome in December, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of Marshal of the Realm in May 10, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of naval officer in September 26, 2019.", "Alberto Lorenzelli Rossi holds the position of titular bishop in May 22, 2019."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 268, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Christopher Butler was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Christopher Butler during the same time span?", "facts": ["Christopher Butler holds the position of naval officer in December 15, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of Minister of Education, Science and Culture in September 2, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of Oberpr\u00e4sident in June, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of auxiliary bishop in November 29, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of titular bishop in November 29, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of Governor of Vermont in June, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 21, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of Minister of Crown-Indigenous Relations in October 11, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of United States Ambassador to the United Nations Agencies for Food and Agriculture in September 16, 1966.", "Christopher Butler holds the position of President of the National Assembly of Ecuador in October 11, 1966."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 269, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim during the same time period?", "facts": ["Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of military officer in September, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of Chief Medical Advisor to the President in August, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 20, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of Prime Minister of Portugal in December, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of President of Iraq in June 28, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of auxiliary bishop in February 24, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of Deputy Chairman of the Planning Commission in March, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of titular bishop in February 24, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of lecturer in October 18, 1832.", "Johann Nepomuk von Tschiderer zu Gleifheim holds the position of Federal Election Commission in December, 1832."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 270, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jan Dekert was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jan Dekert during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jan Dekert holds the position of Lord Mayor of Dublin in 1859.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Exeter in June 9, 1858.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of Secretary of Foreign Affairs of Mexico in February 16, 1859.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of Catholic bishop in January 16, 1859.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Arkansas from August 14, 1859 to December 17, 1859.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of President of the Liberal Democratic Party from August, 1859 to December, 1859.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of Election Commissioner of India in September 4, 1858.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of President of the People's Republic of China from November 14, 1859 to December 22, 1859.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of titular bishop in September 27, 1858.", "Jan Dekert holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 27, 1858."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 271, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Kurt von Schleicher was holding the position of Minister President of Prussia, which position did Kurt von Schleicher during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Catholic bishop in April 19, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic from December 3, 1932 to January 28, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Bishop of Leicester in April 15, 1932.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Minister President of Prussia from December 3, 1932 to January 28, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Vice-Chamberlain of the Household in May 14, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Bath and Wells in August, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Attorney General of California in January 8, 1932.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Attorney-General of South Australia in August, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of board of supervisors in May, 1933.", "Kurt von Schleicher holds the position of Chancellor of Germany from December 3, 1932 to January 28, 1933."], "answer": ["Chancellor of Germany", "Reich Chancellor in the Weimar Republic"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 272, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Joseph Parecattil was holding the position of titular bishop, which position did Joseph Parecattil simultaneously?", "facts": ["Joseph Parecattil holds the position of Minister of the Interior of Denmark from May 3, 1963 to October 3, 1966.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of titular bishop in April 28, 1969.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of Catholic bishop in November 30, 1953.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of President of Peru in July 3, 1969.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of Second Lady or Gentleman of the United States in April, 1964.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of cardinal in April 28, 1969.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 28, 1953.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of circuit judge in January, 1967.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of diocesan administrator in 1962.", "Joseph Parecattil holds the position of Chief Cabinet Secretary in November, 1968."], "answer": ["cardinal"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 273, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Miguel Avell\u00e1n was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Miguel Avell\u00e1n concurrently?", "facts": ["Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of United States Ambassador to Vietnam in March 28, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Minister of Cooperative Governance and Traditional Affairs in September, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of President of Liberia in January 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of chief economist in October 1, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of Florida Commissioner of Agriculture in January 25, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of consultant in August, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of United States Ambassador to Canada in September 2, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 20, 1633.", "Miguel Avell\u00e1n holds the position of titular bishop in June 20, 1633."], "answer": ["titular bishop", "Catholic bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 274, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski concurrently?", "facts": ["Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of India in 1684.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Minister of the Environment in December 2, 1683.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Catholic bishop in February 6, 1684.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Federal Minister for Foreign Affairs in 1684.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in September 27, 1683.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Ministry of the Overseas from April, 1684 to December, 1684.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Lord Steward in October, 1684.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of engineer in November, 1684.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of titular bishop in September 27, 1683.", "Stanis\u0142aw Bedli\u0144ski holds the position of Secretary of State for Wales in November, 1683."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 275, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Giovanni Businski was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Giovanni Businski simultaneously?", "facts": ["Giovanni Businski holds the position of antipope in January 9, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of Catholic bishop in February, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of metropolitan in December 28, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of auxiliary bishop in January 11, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice and Tackling Illegal Migration in July 17, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of Minister for Social Security in December, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of Solicitor-General for Ireland in December, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of Minister for Culture of Sweden in March, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of titular bishop in January 11, 1527.", "Giovanni Businski holds the position of Minister for Foreign Affairs of Finland in November 26, 1527."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 276, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Charles Salatka was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Charles Salatka during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Charles Salatka holds the position of Bishop of South Tokyo in July, 1968.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of diocesan bishop in January 5, 1968.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of Catholic bishop in March 6, 1962.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of canon from December 16, 1962 to October 19, 1967.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of titular bishop in December 11, 1961.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of President of Serbia and Montenegro from 1967 to 1968.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of auxiliary bishop in December 11, 1961.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of United States Under Secretary of the Army in October, 1964.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of Chief Whip in April 11, 1965.", "Charles Salatka holds the position of Mayor of San Salvador from December 21, 1966 to December 28, 1966."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 277, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Venedykt Aleksiichuk was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Venedykt Aleksiichuk during the same time period?", "facts": ["Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of member of the Folketing in October, 2013.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of titular bishop in August 3, 2010.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of Minister of Trade and Industry in June, 2015.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 5, 2010.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of diocesan bishop in April 20, 2017.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of town supervisor from 2016 to 2017.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of Minister of State in 2011.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of Speaker of the Landsting in September, 2013.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of auxiliary bishop in August 3, 2010.", "Venedykt Aleksiichuk holds the position of President of the Generalitat of Catalonia in February, 2014."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 278, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Walter Francis Sullivan was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Walter Francis Sullivan within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Malaysia in 1989.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of diocesan bishop from June 4, 1974 to September 16, 2003.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of Secretary of State for Scotland in April, 1994.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of Secretary for Mines in September, 2003.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 1, 1970.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of Prime Minister of Malaysia in December, 1997.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of President of Nauru from August 13, 2002 to June 16, 2003.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of Minister of Economic and Business Affairs in August, 1979.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 15, 1970.", "Walter Francis Sullivan holds the position of titular bishop in October 15, 1970."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 279, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques at the same time?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of Vice President of Iran in April, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of Federal Minister of Justice in May 10, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of \u00e4kim of Astana in November 22, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of Magistrate of Miaoli County in April, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of President of Moldova in May, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of Catholic bishop in September 20, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Sri Lanka in July 23, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of protonotary apostolic in August 18, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 10, 1991.", "Jos\u00e9 Ant\u00f4nio Aparecido Tosi Marques holds the position of titular bishop in July 10, 1991."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 280, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Michael Joseph Savage was holding the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand, which position did Michael Joseph Savage within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of High Sheriff of Herefordshire in October 22, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Governor of Bombay in March 22, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of heir presumptive in March, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development from December 6, 1935 to March 27, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs from December 6, 1935 to March 27, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand from December 6, 1935 to March 27, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Permanent Representative of Russia to the United Nations in October, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of mayor of a place in France in September, 1940.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of Governor of Texas in October 18, 1935.", "Michael Joseph Savage holds the position of chief financial officer in June 15, 1935."], "answer": ["Minister for M\u0101ori Development", "Minister of Foreign Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 281, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Ciar\u00e1n Cannon was a member of Fine Gael, which political party did Ciar\u00e1n Cannon belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Latvian Farmers' Union in April 7, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Group of Independents in November, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Progressive Democrats in March 24, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Australian Greens in January 25, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Kurdistan Democratic Party in September, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Ulster Unionist Party in April, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Fine Gael in March 24, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Progressive Republican Party in August 9, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the New Zealand National Party in February, 2009.", "Ciar\u00e1n Cannon is a member of the Freedom and Direct Democracy in August, 2009."], "answer": ["Progressive Democrats"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 282, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Petro Loza was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Petro Loza at the same time?", "facts": ["Petro Loza holds the position of Catholic bishop in July 12, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives in July, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 12, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of European Commissioner for External Relations in November, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of Minnesota Attorney General in July 16, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of Clerk of the Closet in April 25, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of titular bishop in April 12, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of equerry in February 16, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of Chairman of Committees of the New South Wales Legislative Council in August, 2018.", "Petro Loza holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Defence in August 18, 2018."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 283, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pierre Pettigrew was holding the position of Minister responsible for Official Languages, which position did Pierre Pettigrew within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of State for Defence Procurement in July, 1997.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister responsible for Official Languages from December 12, 2003 to July 19, 2004.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister responsible for the Francophonie from January 25, 1996 to October 3, 1996.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Culture and Education from April, 1999 to January, 2000.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister for International Development from January 25, 1996 to October 3, 1996.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Health from December 12, 2003 to July 19, 2004.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Canada from July 20, 2004 to February 5, 2006.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of International Trade from August 3, 1999 to December 11, 2003.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Innovation in November, 2002.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Intergovernmental Affairs from December 12, 2003 to July 19, 2004."], "answer": ["Minister of Health", "Minister of Intergovernmental Affairs"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 284, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Javier Azagra Labiano was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Javier Azagra Labiano concurrently?", "facts": ["Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of preacher in September 25, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia in July 19, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of superior general in August 27, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of Minister of Population and Ethnic Affairs in April 27, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of Leader of the Opposition in the House of Lords in December 3, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of Attorney General of Ireland in December, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of general manager in November, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 7, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 17, 1970.", "Javier Azagra Labiano holds the position of titular bishop in July 17, 1970."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 285, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Peter Anthony Libasci was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Peter Anthony Libasci concurrently?", "facts": ["Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of Prime Minister of Dominica from 2008 to 2009.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of judge from June, 2009 to June, 2011.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of Vice President of Ecuador in June, 2010.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of diocesan bishop in September 19, 2011.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of Governor of Tennessee from November 3, 2009 to October 6, 2010.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 1, 2007.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of titular bishop in April 3, 2007.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of Secretary General of NATO in November 10, 2007.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of United States Ambassador to Poland in 2008.", "Peter Anthony Libasci holds the position of auxiliary bishop in April 3, 2007."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 286, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington was holding the position of Minister for Women and Equalities, which position did Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Governor of the Banque de France in July, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Chief Justice of Ireland in December 25, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of President of Serbia in May, 1998.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of President of Harvard University in July, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of High Commissioner for the Western Pacific in November, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Lord Privy Seal from July 27, 1998 to June 8, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Minister of Crown-Indigenous Relations in September 3, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Leader of the House of Lords from July 27, 1998 to June 8, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Minister for Women and Equalities from July 27, 1998 to June 8, 2001.", "Margaret Jay, Baroness Jay of Paddington holds the position of Governor of Texas in October, 2001."], "answer": ["Lord Privy Seal", "Leader of the House of Lords"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 287, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford was a member of Labour Party, which political party did Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Taiwan People's Party in August 24, 2003.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Civic Democratic Party in August, 2001.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Conservative Party in June 26, 2007.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Labour Party in June 26, 2007.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford holds the position of Minister of State for Defence Procurement from October 5, 2008 to May 11, 2010.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Italian People's Party in March 7, 2009.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Liberal Conservative Reformers from January 18, 2002 to July 27, 2004.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Workers\u2019 Party of Korea from October 10, 2010 to October 11, 2010.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Northern Ireland from September 14, 2001 to November 11, 2003.", "Quentin Davies, Baron Davies of Stamford is a member of the Khmer Renovation from February 12, 2006 to November 14, 2006."], "answer": ["Conservative Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 288, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Park Byeong-seug was a member of independent politician, which political party did Park Byeong-seug belong to at the same time?", "facts": ["Park Byeong-seug holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of South Korea from June 5, 2020 to May 29, 2022.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the independent politician in June 6, 2020.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Our Land in 2022.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Party for the Animals from August, 2022 to October, 2022.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Authenticity and Modernity Party in January 21, 2020.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Neo Destour from July, 2021 to September, 2022.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Democratic Party of Korea in June 6, 2020.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Alliance of Liberals and Democrats Party in November 5, 2021.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Social Democratic Party of Lithuania in August, 2022.", "Park Byeong-seug is a member of the Spanish Communist Workers' Party in April, 2022."], "answer": ["Democratic Party of Korea"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 289, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Eduardo Monteiro was working for University of S\u00e3o Paulo, which employer did Eduardo Monteiro work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Eduardo Monteiro worked for University of Hawai\u02bbi at M\u0101noa in 2001.", "Eduardo Monteiro worked for Wehrmacht from September, 1995 to July, 1997.", "Eduardo Monteiro worked for P.L. Kapitza Institute for Physical Problems RAS from March 9, 1995 to December 26, 2000.", "Eduardo Monteiro worked for Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars in May 20, 2001.", "Eduardo Monteiro worked for University of Bucharest in September 4, 1997.", "Eduardo Monteiro worked for Hochschule f\u00fcr Musik Freiburg in April 17, 1995.", "Eduardo Monteiro works for University of S\u00e3o Paulo in August 5, 2002.", "Eduardo Monteiro attended Paris-Sorbonne University - Paris IV from 1995 to 2000.", "Eduardo Monteiro works for School of Communications and Arts of the University of S\u00e3o Paulo in August 5, 2002.", "Eduardo Monteiro worked for Apple in June, 2002."], "answer": ["School of Communications and Arts of the University of S\u00e3o Paulo"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 290, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While George Beluso Rimando was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did George Beluso Rimando at the same time?", "facts": ["George Beluso Rimando holds the position of Commissioner of the British Antarctic Territory in August, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of Catholic bishop in May 25, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of United States Ambassador to Vietnam in May, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of Minister responsible for the Federal Economic Development Initiative for Northern Ontario in March 15, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of Governor of Yap in May 22, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Ireland in October 18, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of High Commissioner for Palestine and Transjordan in March 27, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of auxiliary bishop in March 4, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of Secretary for Public Works in May 27, 2006.", "George Beluso Rimando holds the position of titular bishop in March 4, 2006."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 291, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Henry Barwell was a member of Liberal Union, which political party did Henry Barwell belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Henry Barwell holds the position of member of the Australian Senate from December 18, 1925 to March 22, 1928.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the National Liberal Party in October, 1924.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the Nippon Ishin no Kai in November 18, 1928.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the Liberal Federation in October 16, 1923.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the Liberal Union in October 16, 1923.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the The Jewish Home in May 2, 1923.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the Self-Defence of the Republic of Poland in May 13, 1926.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party from 1924 to 1925.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the Ecuadorian Socialist Party in February 24, 1925.", "Henry Barwell is a member of the New Party Daichi in May 18, 1924."], "answer": ["Liberal Federation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 292, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Nicolai Dubinin was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Nicolai Dubinin concurrently?", "facts": ["Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Minister of Natural Resources in April 19, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of titular bishop in July 30, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Oxfordshire in May, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Prime Minister of North Macedonia in April 8, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Chancellor of Germany in July 23, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of auxiliary bishop in July 30, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Dean of Canterbury in March, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Page of Honour in November, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of Catholic bishop in October 4, 2020.", "Nicolai Dubinin holds the position of constitutional bishop in April 27, 2020."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 293, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Brian Druker was working for Brigham and Women's Hospital, which employer did Brian Druker work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Brian Druker worked for GSI Helmholtz Centre for Heavy Ion Research in February 1, 2009.", "Brian Druker works for Brigham and Women's Hospital from 1987 to 1993.", "Brian Druker worked for University of Pittsburgh School of Law from October 19, 2001 to April 24, 2008.", "Brian Druker worked for Goddard Space Flight Center from April 20, 2008 to December 25, 2009.", "Brian Druker worked for Austrian Academy of Sciences from January 23, 2005 to December 26, 2010.", "Brian Druker works for Oregon Health & Science University in 2010.", "Brian Druker works for Dana\u2013Farber Cancer Institute from 1987 to 1993.", "Brian Druker worked for Royal Danish Academy of Fine Arts in August 17, 1998.", "Brian Druker worked for Bucknell University from July, 2006 to July, 2007.", "Brian Druker works for Harvard Medical School from 1987 to 1993."], "answer": ["Harvard Medical School", "Dana\u2013Farber Cancer Institute"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 294, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While William Marsh was a member of Democratic Party, which political party did William Marsh belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["William Marsh is a member of the Social Democratic Federation from May 24, 2004 to March 28, 2013.", "William Marsh is a member of the Anti-Parliamentary Communist Federation from April 8, 1989 to September 15, 2013.", "William Marsh is a member of the Democratic Party in September 14, 2021.", "William Marsh attended Geisel School of Medicine from 1979 to 1982.", "William Marsh is a member of the British Socialist Party in December 10, 1994.", "William Marsh is a member of the Rafi in 1978.", "William Marsh is a member of the Agir in June, 2007.", "William Marsh attended Dartmouth College from 1975 to 1979.", "William Marsh is a member of the Cap \u00c9cologie from May 17, 2007 to January 19, 2018.", "William Marsh is a member of the Republican Party in September 14, 2021."], "answer": ["Republican Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 295, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Anca Dragu was a member of Save Romania Union, which political party did Anca Dragu belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Anca Dragu is a member of the Isamaa in August 17, 2010.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party in August 15, 2020.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the Finns Party in November, 2015.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the People's Party for Freedom and Democracy from 2007 to 2016.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the Christian Democratic Party in February, 2007.", "Anca Dragu attended National School of Political and Administrative Studies in 2007.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the RENAMO in January, 2018.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the Party of the Communists of Catalonia from 2009 to 2016.", "Anca Dragu is a member of the Save Romania Union in August 15, 2020.", "Anca Dragu holds the position of President of the Senate of Romania from December 21, 2020 to November 23, 2021."], "answer": ["Liberty, Unity and Solidarity Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 296, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Walter Nash was holding the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs, which position did Walter Nash during the same time period?", "facts": ["Walter Nash holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand from December 12, 1957 to December 12, 1960.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Azerbaijan from 1935 to 1944.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of National Defence in November, 1955.", "Walter Nash holds the position of White House Press Secretary in 1950.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of Social Development from December 13, 1938 to April 30, 1940.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Administrator of Veterans Affairs from November, 1947 to May, 1951.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister for M\u0101ori Development from December 12, 1957 to December 12, 1960.", "Walter Nash holds the position of United States Special Representative for North Korea Policy in October 3, 1944.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of Finance from December 6, 1935 to December 13, 1949.", "Walter Nash holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs from December 12, 1957 to December 12, 1960."], "answer": ["Minister for M\u0101ori Development", "Prime Minister of New Zealand"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 297, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alberto Dahik was working for El Universo, which employer did Alberto Dahik work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Alberto Dahik works for The Coca-Cola Company from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik works for National Congress of Ecuador from August 10, 1988 to August 9, 1992.", "Alberto Dahik works for University of Guayaquil from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik is a member of the Conservative Party in July 17, 1987.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Bilka from April 11, 1989 to January 15, 2012.", "Alberto Dahik works for Escuela Superior Polit\u00e9cnica del Litoral from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik works for El Universo from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Roosevelt University in October 24, 2015.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Winchester College from December 15, 1995 to January 24, 2011.", "Alberto Dahik works for Universidad de Especialidades Esp\u00edritu Santo in 2015."], "answer": ["Escuela Superior Polit\u00e9cnica del Litoral", "The Coca-Cola Company", "University of Guayaquil"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 298, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pietro Maffi was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Pietro Maffi during the same time span?", "facts": ["Pietro Maffi holds the position of Vice-Chancellor of Germany from August, 1903 to September, 1905.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of titular bishop in June 9, 1902.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of Catholic bishop in June 11, 1902.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of auxiliary bishop in June 9, 1902.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of President of the Board of Control in 1906.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of cardinal in April 15, 1907.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of President of East Timor in 1903.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of Minister for Employment in February, 1902.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of President of the Xunta of Galicia in 1906.", "Pietro Maffi holds the position of Minister of Economic Affairs and Infrastructure in April 6, 1902."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 299, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pierre Pettigrew was holding the position of Minister of Intergovernmental Affairs, which position did Pierre Pettigrew during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of International Trade from August 3, 1999 to December 11, 2003.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Canada from July 20, 2004 to February 5, 2006.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Defence and Military Veterans in January 23, 1996.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Chief Secretary for Ireland in October, 1998.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of United States Ambassador to Jordan from October 26, 2006 to December 27, 2006.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister for International Development from January 25, 1996 to October 3, 1996.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister responsible for Official Languages from December 12, 2003 to July 19, 2004.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Intergovernmental Affairs from December 12, 2003 to July 19, 2004.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister responsible for the Francophonie from January 25, 1996 to October 3, 1996.", "Pierre Pettigrew holds the position of Minister of Health from December 12, 2003 to July 19, 2004."], "answer": ["Minister responsible for Official Languages", "Minister of Health"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 300, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Dougherty was holding the position of auxiliary bishop, which position did Patrick Dougherty during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Patrick Dougherty holds the position of diocesan bishop from September 1, 1983 to November 11, 2008.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of Minister of Natural Resources and Environment in July, 1986.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign Affairs from December, 2002 to July, 2004.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of auxiliary bishop in October 15, 1976.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of Minister for Defence Materiel in March 6, 1999.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of Catholic bishop in December 8, 1976.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of Lord Chief Justice of Northern Ireland from February, 1995 to June, 1996.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of President of Comoros in April 22, 1978.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of Italian Minister of Public Administration from 1988 to 1996.", "Patrick Dougherty holds the position of titular bishop in October 15, 1976."], "answer": ["titular bishop"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 301, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Alberto Dahik was working for Escuela Superior Polit\u00e9cnica del Litoral, which employer did Alberto Dahik work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Alberto Dahik worked for H\u00f4pital de la Charit\u00e9 in September 16, 1989.", "Alberto Dahik works for Universidad de Especialidades Esp\u00edritu Santo in 2015.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Hanna-Barbera in 2012.", "Alberto Dahik works for University of Guayaquil from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik is a member of the Conservative Party in July 17, 1987.", "Alberto Dahik worked for Tongji University from 1996 to 1998.", "Alberto Dahik works for Escuela Superior Polit\u00e9cnica del Litoral from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik works for National Congress of Ecuador from August 10, 1988 to August 9, 1992.", "Alberto Dahik works for El Universo from 1981 to 1984.", "Alberto Dahik works for The Coca-Cola Company from 1981 to 1984."], "answer": ["El Universo", "The Coca-Cola Company", "University of Guayaquil"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 302, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Bob Rae was a member of New Democratic Party, which political party did Bob Rae belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Bob Rae is a member of the New Democratic Party from 1974 to 1998.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Movement for Defence of the Land from 2002 to 2006.", "Bob Rae is a member of the People's National Movement from December 26, 2001 to June 27, 2006.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Libertarian Party in 2006.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Ontario New Democratic Party from 1974 to 1998.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Forza Italia in June, 2005.", "Bob Rae holds the position of Premier of Ontario from October 1, 1990 to June 26, 1995.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Liberal Party of Canada in 2006.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Alliance '90/The Greens from December, 2001 to July, 2006.", "Bob Rae is a member of the Polska Razem in 2003."], "answer": ["Ontario New Democratic Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 303, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Panfilo Lacson was a member of independent politician, which political party did Panfilo Lacson belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Panfilo Lacson is a member of the Chinese Youth Party in 1982.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the independent politician in March 24, 2022.", "Panfilo Lacson holds the position of Chief of the Philippine National Police from November 16, 1999 to February 16, 2001.", "Panfilo Lacson attended Philippine Military Academy from 1967 to 1971.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the New Democratic Party of Serbia in August, 1982.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the Communist Party of Czechoslovakia from May, 1969 to February, 1980.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the No Pokies in September, 1985.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the People's Radical Party in April 24, 1976.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the Partido para sa Demokratikong Reporma in March 24, 2022.", "Panfilo Lacson is a member of the Telem in 1969."], "answer": ["Partido para sa Demokratikong Reporma"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 304, "triple_element": "S1_R1_O2", "question": "While Pantaleon Alvarez was a member of Partido Demokratiko Pilipino\u2013Lakas ng Bayan, which political party did Pantaleon Alvarez belong to during the same time span?", "facts": ["Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Independent Democratic Union from June 10, 2017 to January 10, 2018.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the The Olive Tree in September, 2018.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Christian Democratic Appeal from May 4, 2016 to August 10, 2019.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Partido Demokratiko Pilipino\u2013Lakas ng Bayan in November 15, 2020.", "Pantaleon Alvarez holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives of the Philippines in July 25, 2016.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Janata Dal (United) in February, 2019.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Liberal Party of Canada in December 15, 2019.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Partido para sa Demokratikong Reporma in November 15, 2020.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Direction Italy in 2018.", "Pantaleon Alvarez is a member of the Communist Party of India (Marxist) in November 14, 2020."], "answer": ["Partido para sa Demokratikong Reporma"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 305, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Tracey DeKeyser was playing for Cornell Big Red women's ice hockey, which school did Tracey DeKeyser attend during the same time span?", "facts": ["Tracey DeKeyser plays for Alexia Alluminio in 1999.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended Hobart College from May, 2000 to February, 2005.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended University of Tennessee College of Law from 2003 to 2004.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended Helmut Schmidt University in March, 2001.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for AS Police in July 13, 2000.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for Cornell Big Red women's ice hockey from 1993 to 1997.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended Technical University of Madrid from June, 1998 to March, 1999.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for A.C. Doukas Basketball in 2000.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for Pallokissat from November, 2004 to March, 2005.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for Winslow United F.C. from June, 2002 to November, 2002.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for F.C. Ashdod from 2003 to 2006.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for Pakistan A cricket team from March 20, 2001 to December 21, 2007.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for Harburger TB 1865 in June, 2005.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended University of Wisconsin\u2013Madison in 2007.", "Tracey DeKeyser plays for Weston-super-Mare A.F.C. in March, 2006.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended St. Lawrence University in 2003.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff in June, 2002.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended University of Toronto Scarborough in May 23, 2002.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended Asti Leku Ikastola in June, 2004.", "Tracey DeKeyser attended Cornell University from 1993 to 1997."], "answer": ["Cornell University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 306, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jimmer Fredette was playing for BYU Cougars men's basketball, which school did Jimmer Fredette attend during the same time period?", "facts": ["Jimmer Fredette attended Suffolk University Law School from 2012 to 2018.", "Jimmer Fredette attended St. Xavier High School in December 13, 2018.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Portugal national under-18 football team in January 1, 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Fazekas Mih\u00e1ly Gimn\u00e1zium from May, 2017 to December, 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for BYU Cougars men's basketball from 2007 to 2011.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Skt. J\u00f8rgens Gymnasium from April, 2019 to December, 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Air Command and Staff College in 2017.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for WVC Dynamo Moscow from March 12, 2018 to August 24, 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for I-Shou University FC from January, 2015 to September, 2017.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Loyola Marymount University from 2014 to 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Partizan in July 15, 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Lotto Dstny Development Team in 2016.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Fudan University from June 3, 2014 to June 18, 2018.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Baltimore Blast in January, 2017.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Dayton Dutch Lions in September, 2015.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Belarusian State Economic University in 2019.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Horndean F.C. from November, 2015 to September, 2016.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Gelehrtenschule des Johanneums in September, 2018.", "Jimmer Fredette plays for Uni\u00f3 Esportiva Vic from January 22, 2016 to November 28, 2018.", "Jimmer Fredette attended Brigham Young University from 2007 to 2011."], "answer": ["Brigham Young University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 307, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Tim Couch was playing for Kentucky Wildcats football, which school did Tim Couch attend during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Tim Couch attended University of Limoges in November, 2003.", "Tim Couch plays for FC Bayern Alzenau in December 5, 2007.", "Tim Couch plays for Laval Comets from May, 2007 to September, 2007.", "Tim Couch attended Suffolk University in March, 2004.", "Tim Couch plays for Cleveland Browns from 1999 to 2003.", "Tim Couch attended University of Kentucky from 1996 to 1998.", "Tim Couch plays for Moscow Stars from December, 2003 to January, 2007.", "Tim Couch plays for Jacksonville Jaguars in 2007.", "Tim Couch plays for Green Bay Packers in 2004.", "Tim Couch plays for Leigh Genesis F.C. from May, 2005 to June, 2005.", "Tim Couch plays for Buda\u00f6rs Handball in March, 1999.", "Tim Couch attended Mississippi College from April 9, 1999 to December 16, 2005.", "Tim Couch attended Stetson University College of Law in January, 2007.", "Tim Couch plays for Kentucky Wildcats football from 1996 to 1998.", "Tim Couch attended Fuqua School of Business in August, 2003.", "Tim Couch plays for Western Bulldogs from July, 2006 to May, 2007.", "Tim Couch attended Bilkent University in July, 2005.", "Tim Couch attended Forman Christian College from October 14, 2001 to July 22, 2004.", "Tim Couch attended University of Montpellier 1 in May 19, 2000.", "Tim Couch attended Western College for Women in July, 2005."], "answer": ["University of Kentucky"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 308, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Lenox Hewitt was holding the position of chairperson, which employer did Lenox Hewitt work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Lenox Hewitt holds the position of president of Lombardy in November 18, 1972.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of Secretary of State for Education in May 14, 1974.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Lancing College in 1973.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Hamilton College in July, 1972.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Danfoss in 1969.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Qantas from 1975 to 1980.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of vicar general in 1970.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of minister from 1968 to 1971.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Central State University in October, 1973.", "Lenox Hewitt works for UCSF Medical Center in April 3, 1968.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of bureaucrat in September 20, 1968.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of president of Bolivia in July, 1970.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Televisi\u00f3n Espa\u00f1ola in June 11, 1968.", "Lenox Hewitt works for National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration in December, 1974.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Saint Petersburg Conservatory from September, 1969 to March, 1971.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of Governor of Bermuda from December, 1971 to March, 1972.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of Premier of the Republic of China in 1971.", "Lenox Hewitt works for Queen's University in February 5, 1974.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of intendant in January, 1970.", "Lenox Hewitt holds the position of chairperson from 1975 to 1980."], "answer": ["Qantas"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 309, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Blake Sims was playing for Alabama Crimson Tide football, which school did Blake Sims attend during the same time span?", "facts": ["Blake Sims attended Goethe-Institut in June 13, 2018.", "Blake Sims plays for Birmingham Iron in 2018.", "Blake Sims attended Woodrow Wilson High School from 2015 to 2017.", "Blake Sims plays for FC Karpaty-2 Lviv from 2015 to 2017.", "Blake Sims attended Medical College of Georgia in 2015.", "Blake Sims attended Southeast Missouri State University from 2017 to 2018.", "Blake Sims plays for Alabama Crimson Tide football from 2010 to 2014.", "Blake Sims plays for FK Zvijezda 09 in 2018.", "Blake Sims attended Fairfield University in 2018.", "Blake Sims plays for BIIK Kazygurt in 2015.", "Blake Sims attended Solvay Brussels School of Economics and Management in June 9, 2017.", "Blake Sims attended St Patrick's High School, Karachi in November, 2018.", "Blake Sims attended Marischal College from May, 2015 to November, 2015.", "Blake Sims plays for Belarus national under-17 football team from November 15, 2017 to September 20, 2018.", "Blake Sims plays for Toronto Six from February, 2016 to September, 2017.", "Blake Sims plays for Mets de Guaynabo in 2015.", "Blake Sims attended University of Alabama from 2010 to 2014.", "Blake Sims plays for SC Bonifika in November, 2017.", "Blake Sims plays for S.S. Real Montecchio from April, 2015 to February, 2016.", "Blake Sims attended Wofford College from October 26, 2017 to November 28, 2017."], "answer": ["University of Alabama"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 310, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Tyree Wilson was playing for Texas Tech Red Raiders football, which school did Tyree Wilson attend at the same time?", "facts": ["Tyree Wilson plays for Texas Tech Red Raiders football from 2020 to 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for FK Famos Hrasnica in 2019.", "Tyree Wilson attended University of Coimbra in 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Campinense Clube in 2019.", "Tyree Wilson attended Brooklyn Law School in January 1, 2019.", "Tyree Wilson attended Bankura Zilla School in November, 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Club Tijuana in April, 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for KIF Kolding in August, 2018.", "Tyree Wilson attended Tulane University Law School in November 3, 2018.", "Tyree Wilson attended Royal Swedish Academy of Fine Arts in December, 2018.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Senegal women's national handball team in 2019.", "Tyree Wilson attended California School of Professional Psychology in 2018.", "Tyree Wilson attended South Kent School in 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Alicante CF B in 2018.", "Tyree Wilson attended Texas A&M University from 2018 to 2019.", "Tyree Wilson attended Columbia University School of Social Work in March 25, 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Leeds Tykes in December 15, 2018.", "Tyree Wilson attended Texas Tech University from 2020 to 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Texas A&M Aggies football from 2018 to 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for NK Radomlje in January, 2018."], "answer": ["Texas Tech University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 311, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Josh Allen was playing for Wyoming Cowboys football, which school did Josh Allen attend within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Josh Allen attended Imperial Academy of Arts in May, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended Eszterh\u00e1zy K\u00e1roly Catholic University from January, 2018 to April, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Sydney Stars in July 28, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Toronto Inferno in September 9, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended University of Wyoming from 2015 to 2017.", "Josh Allen attended University of Hertfordshire from April, 2018 to September, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended Manchester University from March, 2018 to July, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended Baker University in October 17, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Buffalo Bills in 2018.", "Josh Allen attended St Catherine's College in August 11, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended Crossroads School from July 20, 2018 to July 26, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Serbia national under-20 football team in September, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended Lyc\u00e9e militaire de Saint-Cyr from August 2, 2018 to November 22, 2018.", "Josh Allen attended United States Naval Test Pilot School in 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Madhya Pradesh cricket team in November, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Ethnikos Katerini F.C. from January, 2018 to August, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for FC Sulori Vani in November 7, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Wyoming Cowboys football from 2015 to 2017.", "Josh Allen plays for FFC Zuchwil 05 from August, 2018 to December, 2018.", "Josh Allen plays for Yeclano Deportivo in 2018."], "answer": ["University of Wyoming"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 312, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Mher Grigoryan was holding the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Armenia, which employer did Mher Grigoryan work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Mher Grigoryan works for Georgian Technical University in May 6, 1996.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of visiting scholar in May 25, 2011.", "Mher Grigoryan works for Government of Armenia in May 12, 2018.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of conductor from February 14, 2013 to August 19, 2015.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of Prime Minister of East Timor in May 13, 2005.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of Minister of Natural Resources from April, 2006 to November, 2008.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of Apostolic King of Hungary from February, 1998 to May, 2004.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of United States Deputy Secretary of Homeland Security in November 22, 2016.", "Mher Grigoryan attended Yerevan State University in 1994.", "Mher Grigoryan works for HK Danmark from 1997 to 2000.", "Mher Grigoryan works for Pacific Northwest National Laboratory from August, 2003 to October, 2011.", "Mher Grigoryan works for NKT in February 23, 1998.", "Mher Grigoryan works for SGH Warsaw School of Economics from 2005 to 2010.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Scotland in 2016.", "Mher Grigoryan works for Jet Propulsion Laboratory in April, 2008.", "Mher Grigoryan works for Harvard Medical School in 1994.", "Mher Grigoryan works for Johns Hopkins University in 2001.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of President of the Swiss Confederation from June, 1998 to June, 2017.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of Armenia in May 12, 2018.", "Mher Grigoryan holds the position of advisor from August 17, 2006 to October 23, 2006.", "Mher Grigoryan works for The King's College in November, 1996."], "answer": ["Government of Armenia"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 313, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Tyree Wilson was playing for Texas A&M Aggies football, which school did Tyree Wilson attend within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Tyree Wilson plays for CB Islas Canarias in February 10, 2020.", "Tyree Wilson plays for New Jersey Stallions in June 11, 2020.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Greve Fodbold from June, 2020 to April, 2021.", "Tyree Wilson attended Stonyhurst College from September 9, 2021 to October 20, 2021.", "Tyree Wilson attended Lady Shri Ram College for Women in September, 2022.", "Tyree Wilson attended Sint-Jan Berchmanscollege from August, 2020 to August, 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Texas Tech Red Raiders football from 2020 to 2022.", "Tyree Wilson attended Notre Dame Law School in October, 2021.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Texas A&M Aggies football from 2018 to 2019.", "Tyree Wilson plays for South China AA in April 10, 2021.", "Tyree Wilson attended Texas A&M University from 2018 to 2019.", "Tyree Wilson attended University of Northern Iowa from September 9, 2022 to October 23, 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Port Adelaide Pirates from 2021 to 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for Oklahoma Sooners men's basketball from September, 2022 to October, 2022.", "Tyree Wilson attended Texas Tech University from 2020 to 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for CSO Filia\u0219i in June 6, 2021.", "Tyree Wilson attended University of Connecticut School of Law from 2020 to 2022.", "Tyree Wilson attended St. Andrew's College in September 23, 2022.", "Tyree Wilson plays for A.S.D. Fidelis Andria 1928 from April 4, 2020 to June 7, 2022.", "Tyree Wilson attended Assumption University in August, 2022."], "answer": ["Texas A&M University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 314, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jae Crowder was playing for Marquette Golden Eagles men's basketball, which school did Jae Crowder attend within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Jae Crowder plays for Oxford University Cricket Club in July, 2016.", "Jae Crowder plays for Miami Heat in February 6, 2020.", "Jae Crowder plays for New South Wales cricket team in 2016.", "Jae Crowder attended Interregional Academy of Personnel Management from 2016 to 2018.", "Jae Crowder plays for North Dakota State Bison football in November, 2016.", "Jae Crowder attended West Virginia Wesleyan College in May 13, 2019.", "Jae Crowder plays for Marquette Golden Eagles men's basketball from 2010 to 2012.", "Jae Crowder plays for Beykoz 1908 S.K.D. in January, 2016.", "Jae Crowder plays for Morpeth Town A.F.C. in 2016.", "Jae Crowder attended University of Limoges from October, 2015 to December, 2020.", "Jae Crowder plays for Bermuda Hogges from February 14, 2020 to September 23, 2020.", "Jae Crowder attended St. Albans School in December 27, 2013.", "Jae Crowder attended Aston University in October 12, 2019.", "Jae Crowder attended Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences in 2016.", "Jae Crowder attended Marquette University from 2010 to 2012.", "Jae Crowder attended William Mitchell College of Law from February 16, 2017 to December 26, 2018.", "Jae Crowder attended All-Russian Academy of Foreign Trade from July, 2017 to October, 2017.", "Jae Crowder plays for FC Metallurg Vyksa from April 26, 2015 to March 26, 2019.", "Jae Crowder attended Yale College in 2019.", "Jae Crowder plays for FC Nart Cherkessk in September, 2017."], "answer": ["Marquette University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 315, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Gilles P\u00e9lisson was working for Soci\u00e9t\u00e9 G\u00e9n\u00e9rale, which school did Gilles P\u00e9lisson attend during the same time period?", "facts": ["Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for ARTE from July, 1995 to March, 2016.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Gonzaga University School of Law in April, 2003.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Harvard Business School in 2014.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for Auckland University of Technology from March, 2003 to February, 2023.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for Phoenix Police Department in July 14, 2010.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for Soci\u00e9t\u00e9 G\u00e9n\u00e9rale from 1981 to 1983.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Royal Swedish Academy of Fine Arts from 2004 to 2021.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended King Juan Carlos University from July, 1994 to September, 1995.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Chicago State University from April 21, 1997 to April 27, 2001.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Grand S\u00e9minaire de Montr\u00e9al from 2009 to 2023.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for University of Montana in January, 1987.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for TF1 Group from 2016 to 2023.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for Leiden University Medical Center in 2018.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Edinburgh Academy from 2020 to 2022.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for Cadena SER in January, 2013.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Anoka High School in February, 2018.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for DADES in June, 1989.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended Harvard University from 1981 to 1983.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson works for University of North Carolina at Greensboro in 1994.", "Gilles P\u00e9lisson attended ESSEC Business School from 1976 to 1979."], "answer": ["Harvard University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 316, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Albert Dou was holding the position of rector, which employer did Albert Dou work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Albert Dou attended University of Innsbruck from 1951 to 1952.", "Albert Dou holds the position of rector from 1975 to 1977.", "Albert Dou holds the position of Prime Minister of Japan in September, 1970.", "Albert Dou holds the position of Speaker of the Parliament of Nauru in 1956.", "Albert Dou works for Autonomous University of Barcelona in 1984.", "Albert Dou works for Sheffield Hallam University from January, 1957 to June, 1967.", "Albert Dou works for Bureau des Longitudes from July, 1966 to October, 1973.", "Albert Dou holds the position of Leader of the Christian Democratic Union in October 22, 1955.", "Albert Dou works for University of the Sunshine Coast in April 2, 1980.", "Albert Dou works for University of Twente from October 7, 1983 to May 12, 1984.", "Albert Dou holds the position of President of the Generalitat of Catalonia in May 24, 1978.", "Albert Dou works for Southern Illinois University Carbondale in March, 1952.", "Albert Dou attended University of Barcelona from 1943 to 1950.", "Albert Dou attended University of Hamburg from 1950 to 1951.", "Albert Dou holds the position of commander-in-chief from January, 1956 to July, 1970.", "Albert Dou works for Schlumberger in January, 1979.", "Albert Dou holds the position of president from 1961 to 1963.", "Albert Dou holds the position of city treasurer in July, 1946.", "Albert Dou works for University of Deusto from 1975 to 1977.", "Albert Dou works for Mercedes-Benz Group in April 6, 1959.", "Albert Dou holds the position of Member of Provincial Parliament of Western Cape in 1981.", "Albert Dou holds the position of Foreign Service officer in April, 1979.", "Albert Dou works for Ministry of Energy in September 12, 1960."], "answer": ["University of Deusto"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 317, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Paul George was playing for Fresno State Bulldogs men's basketball, which school did Paul George attend simultaneously?", "facts": ["Paul George attended University of Central Arkansas from July 8, 2018 to December 17, 2018.", "Paul George attended Tashkent Suvorov Military School from September 4, 2018 to June 18, 2019.", "Paul George plays for Frederikshavn fI from September, 2013 to August, 2015.", "Paul George attended Davidson Day School from September 18, 2011 to January 24, 2017.", "Paul George plays for US Quevilly in 2013.", "Paul George plays for HC Dinamo Minsk from March 2, 2014 to March 8, 2018.", "Paul George plays for Los Angeles Clippers in 2019.", "Paul George attended Hartwick College from 2015 to 2019.", "Paul George plays for Fresno State Bulldogs men's basketball from 2008 to 2010.", "Paul George plays for Bryn\u00e4s IF in March, 2011.", "Paul George plays for AS Ot\u00f4ho from 2015 to 2017.", "Paul George attended University of Angers from February, 2012 to January, 2018.", "Paul George attended Grenoble School of Management from 2014 to 2017.", "Paul George attended California State University, Fresno from 2008 to 2010.", "Paul George plays for Melbourne University Football Club in August, 2017.", "Paul George attended Allen Academy from 2015 to 2017.", "Paul George attended Stern Conservatory in 2013.", "Paul George plays for FC Idel Kazan in 2012.", "Paul George attended Squadron Officer School in 2017.", "Paul George plays for Tampa Bay Storm in May 28, 2017."], "answer": ["California State University, Fresno"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 318, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Mathieu Gallet was holding the position of pr\u00e9sident-directeur g\u00e9n\u00e9ral, which employer did Mathieu Gallet work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Mathieu Gallet holds the position of Prime Minister of Tanzania from December 15, 2012 to May 22, 2013.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Federation University Australia in 2012.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Brookhaven National Laboratory in September 8, 2010.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Radio France from May 12, 2014 to March 1, 2018.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Corvinus University of Budapest in September, 2010.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Clausthal University of Technology in 2013.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Southwest Airlines in September, 2010.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of President of Venezuela in 2010.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of President of Tunisia from 2010 to 2012.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Westmorland in March 24, 2012.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of administrative law judge in June, 2018.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of president from May 26, 2010 to February 27, 2014.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Carnegie Mellon University in 2010.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of Prime Minister of Bengal in February, 2014.", "Mathieu Gallet works for B Verkin Institute for Low Temperature Physics and Engineering from April 5, 2010 to July 7, 2012.", "Mathieu Gallet works for Free University of Brussels in April, 2014.", "Mathieu Gallet works for University of Perpignan in December 7, 2011.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of Leader of the House in Lok Sabha in 2010.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of Secretary for Lands and Works in December 20, 2012.", "Mathieu Gallet holds the position of pr\u00e9sident-directeur g\u00e9n\u00e9ral from May 12, 2014 to March 1, 2018."], "answer": ["Radio France"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 319, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Brittney Griner was playing for Baylor Bears women's basketball, which school did Brittney Griner attend during the same time period?", "facts": ["Brittney Griner plays for UMMC Ekaterinburg from 2015 to 2022.", "Brittney Griner attended Baylor University from 2009 to 2013.", "Brittney Griner attended Vystrel course in 2020.", "Brittney Griner attended Olmsted Falls High School from September, 2021 to October, 2022.", "Brittney Griner plays for Badureliya Sports Club in February 3, 2017.", "Brittney Griner attended Indian Institutes of Technology from May 5, 2017 to April 22, 2020.", "Brittney Griner plays for Red Star F.C. from 2015 to 2020.", "Brittney Griner attended Maine East High School from April, 2015 to March, 2020.", "Brittney Griner attended Manchester University in November, 2014.", "Brittney Griner plays for Faemino-Faema in January, 2021.", "Brittney Griner attended University of Tennessee College of Law in November, 2018.", "Brittney Griner plays for Castelo Futebol Clube in March, 2015.", "Brittney Griner plays for VfL Leverkusen from September 11, 2014 to February 19, 2017.", "Brittney Griner attended London School of Business and Finance in March 21, 2014.", "Brittney Griner plays for Baylor Bears women's basketball from 2009 to 2013.", "Brittney Griner plays for Beijing Great Wall from 2014 to 2015.", "Brittney Griner attended Saint Petersburg State Electrotechnical University in January, 2014.", "Brittney Griner attended University of Wisconsin\u2013Eau Claire in March, 2022.", "Brittney Griner plays for Boston United F.C. in January, 2014.", "Brittney Griner plays for FK Slovan Pardubice in 2022."], "answer": ["Baylor University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 320, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Chris Nanco was playing for Syracuse Orange men's soccer, which school did Chris Nanco attend concurrently?", "facts": ["Chris Nanco plays for VK Karlovarsko from July, 2019 to October, 2019.", "Chris Nanco plays for Timor-Leste national futsal team in January 1, 2017.", "Chris Nanco attended Harris\u2013Stowe State University from January, 2017 to October, 2018.", "Chris Nanco attended University of Illinois Chicago School of Law from May 1, 2018 to September 5, 2019.", "Chris Nanco attended Military University of the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation from January, 2019 to March, 2019.", "Chris Nanco attended Antonin Scalia Law School from October, 2019 to December, 2019.", "Chris Nanco plays for Syracuse Orange men's soccer from 2013 to 2016.", "Chris Nanco plays for Philadelphia Union II from 2017 to 2018.", "Chris Nanco attended Marischal College in February 1, 2017.", "Chris Nanco plays for CD Oper\u00e1rio from May, 2018 to December, 2018.", "Chris Nanco plays for St. George's SC in 2018.", "Chris Nanco attended Albion College in March 3, 2019.", "Chris Nanco plays for Forge FC in 2019.", "Chris Nanco attended Jewish Theological Seminary of Breslau in 2018.", "Chris Nanco plays for FC Oshmyany in July, 2019.", "Chris Nanco plays for Steel City Sparks in January 14, 2018.", "Chris Nanco attended Trenton Central High School in April, 2019.", "Chris Nanco attended Louis Pasteur University in February, 2018.", "Chris Nanco plays for Sichuan Longfor F.C. from October 2, 2017 to December 23, 2017.", "Chris Nanco attended Syracuse University from 2013 to 2016."], "answer": ["Syracuse University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 321, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jalen Hurts was playing for Alabama Crimson Tide football, which school did Jalen Hurts attend concurrently?", "facts": ["Jalen Hurts attended Birmingham\u2013Southern College from July 14, 2019 to November 17, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended Marylhurst University in February, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for Alabama Crimson Tide football from 2016 to 2018.", "Jalen Hurts plays for Helmond Sport from June 18, 2019 to September 27, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended University of Oklahoma in 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for Italy under-21 Serie B representative team in 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended Wells Theological College from July 22, 2019 to July 28, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for FC Bataysk-2007 from January 1, 2019 to October 3, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for CS P\u00e9tange in September 24, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for NK Bela Krajina in May, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended University of Alabama from 2016 to 2018.", "Jalen Hurts attended \u00c9cole militaire interarmes from July, 2019 to November, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended Twyford School from July, 2019 to November, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended Vanderbilt University School of Medicine in 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for France military national football team from April, 2019 to September, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for SK Austria K\u00e4rnten in 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended Royal College of Surgeons of Edinburgh in July, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts attended Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul from January, 2019 to September, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for Churchill Brothers S.C. in January 15, 2019.", "Jalen Hurts plays for FC Dinamo-93 Minsk in October, 2019."], "answer": ["University of Alabama"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 322, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Mark Zuckerberg was holding the position of chief executive officer, which employer did Mark Zuckerberg work for concurrently?", "facts": ["Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of commander in May, 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of Under Secretary of State for Political Affairs in 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of Minister of State for Immigration in September, 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for St. Petersburg State Transport University in June 8, 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for Wilmer Cutler Pickering Hale and Dorr in 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of Master of the Mint in April 15, 2004.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of director general in November, 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for University of G\u00f6ttingen in 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of Minister of Public Works and Transport of Hungary in June 12, 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine in February 24, 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for Meta Platforms in February 4, 2004.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for History Museum of Armenia in February 6, 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg attended Harvard University in September, 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for University of Nigeria in March 4, 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for Texas Southern University in March, 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of chief executive officer in February 4, 2004.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of Labour Party Chair in 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of General Secretary of the Workers' Party of Korea from July 23, 2002 to July 23, 2003.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for General Atomics in July, 2004.", "Mark Zuckerberg holds the position of Daij\u014d-daijin in 2002.", "Mark Zuckerberg works for Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution from February, 2002 to June, 2002."], "answer": ["Meta Platforms"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 323, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jens Lehmann was holding the position of full professor, which employer did Jens Lehmann work for at the same time?", "facts": ["Jens Lehmann holds the position of full professor from December, 2015 to May, 2022.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of Leader of the New Zealand Labour Party in December 19, 2009.", "Jens Lehmann works for University of Bonn from December, 2015 to May, 2022.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of President of Singapore in August 7, 2011.", "Jens Lehmann works for Stanford University in June 9, 2011.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of municipal clerk in 2012.", "Jens Lehmann works for Maxim Tank Belarusian State Pedagogical University in October, 2007.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of Minister for Economic Affairs in 2009.", "Jens Lehmann works for Durham School in 2013.", "Jens Lehmann works for Amazon in June, 2022.", "Jens Lehmann works for University of Nantes in June, 2014.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of deputy mayor in 2012.", "Jens Lehmann works for University of East Anglia in June 27, 2015.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of tax collector in July, 2011.", "Jens Lehmann works for Santa Fe Institute in 2009.", "Jens Lehmann works for Leipzig University from October, 2006 to November, 2015.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of Ministry of Budget, Public Accounts and Civil Administration in February 2, 2012.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of Minister of State for Foreign Affairs from July 12, 2008 to September 24, 2013.", "Jens Lehmann works for Satbayev University in 2006.", "Jens Lehmann holds the position of vicar general in 2014."], "answer": ["University of Bonn"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 324, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Robert P. Knight was holding the position of medical director, which employer did Robert P. Knight work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Robert P. Knight works for Atlantic Council in April, 1945.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of lieutenant general in May 11, 1945.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of Minister for the Status of Women in 1946.", "Robert P. Knight works for Radio Televisi\u00f3n Madrid in 1946.", "Robert P. Knight works for Vanemuine Theatre in April 15, 1946.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of President of the Australian Senate from September, 1945 to October, 1946.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of charg\u00e9 d'affaires in 1946.", "Robert P. Knight works for The Heritage Foundation in June, 1966.", "Robert P. Knight works for Duke Divinity School in May 14, 1945.", "Robert P. Knight works for Argonne National Laboratory in October 17, 1946.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of medical director from 1947 to April 30, 1966.", "Robert P. Knight works for Heriot-Watt University in October 14, 1945.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of chairperson from 1945 to 1946.", "Robert P. Knight works for Henschel & Sohn in March, 1946.", "Robert P. Knight works for University of Westminster in February, 1945.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of Chancellor of Poland in December, 1966.", "Robert P. Knight works for Austen Riggs Center from 1947 to April 30, 1966.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of President of Italy in January, 1945.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of Minister of Supply in August 16, 1966.", "Robert P. Knight holds the position of grand master in July 8, 1946."], "answer": ["Austen Riggs Center"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 325, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Michel Parisse was holding the position of professor, which employer did Michel Parisse work for at the same time?", "facts": ["Michel Parisse works for St. Augustine's University in 1990.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of director from 1985 to 1991.", "Michel Parisse works for Kazan Federal University in December 12, 1986.", "Michel Parisse works for municipality of Paris in 1990.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Solicitor General for New South Wales in October 23, 1991.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Prime Minister of Azerbaijan from 1988 to 1990.", "Michel Parisse works for University of Paris 1 Pantheon-Sorbonne from 1993 to 2002.", "Michel Parisse works for Food and Drug Administration in July, 1990.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of King of Albania in October 24, 1988.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of professor from 1993 to 2002.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Northamptonshire from December 10, 1988 to December 27, 1988.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Indiana from April, 1985 to November, 1990.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Minister for Sport, Health Improvement and Mental Health in September, 1991.", "Michel Parisse works for Visva-Bharati University in October 14, 1989.", "Michel Parisse works for University of Benin in March, 1992.", "Michel Parisse works for Paul H. Nitze School of Advanced International Studies in March, 1986.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Minister of Democratic Institutions in 1990.", "Michel Parisse works for Ministry of the Economy, Finance and the Recovery Finansdepartementet in September, 1989.", "Michel Parisse works for National University of Singapore in July, 1990.", "Michel Parisse holds the position of Minister of Road Transport and Highways in August, 1991."], "answer": ["University of Paris 1 Pantheon-Sorbonne"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 326, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Maria Berger was holding the position of Federal Minister of Justice, which employer did Maria Berger work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Maria Berger works for Salling Group in December 26, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Georgia in December 19, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for University of Guayaquil in December 19, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of Chief Minister of Maharashtra in January 9, 2007.", "Maria Berger works for Andover Newton Theological School in December 9, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for Office de Radiodiffusion T\u00e9l\u00e9vision Fran\u00e7aise in January 3, 2007.", "Maria Berger holds the position of Federal Minister of Justice from January 11, 2007 to December 2, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of Secretary of State for War in December 3, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for Institute of Ecosystem Studies in January 1, 2007.", "Maria Berger holds the position of senior lecturer in December 11, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for American University of Paris in December 13, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of mayor of Novi Sad in December 19, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for Breitbart News in December 15, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of Cabinet Secretary for Justice in December 4, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of Chief of Navy in December 14, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of hegumen in December 19, 2008.", "Maria Berger holds the position of High Sheriff of Suffolk in December 17, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for Austrian Federal Government from January 11, 2007 to December 2, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for University of the West Indies in December 18, 2008.", "Maria Berger works for University of Dhaka in December 18, 2008."], "answer": ["Austrian Federal Government"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 327, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jamal Abu-Shamala was playing for Minnesota Golden Gophers men's basketball, which school did Jamal Abu-Shamala attend concurrently?", "facts": ["Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Prussian Academy of Arts in August 7, 2010.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended University of Minnesota from 2005 to 2009.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended University of St. Thomas in 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Hapoel Afula F.C. in June, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Brown College from July 19, 2011 to December 20, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Saint Mary's College from February 22, 2010 to November 28, 2010.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Ey\u00fcpspor in July 21, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Minnesota Golden Gophers men's basketball from 2005 to 2009.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Robert Schumann Hochschule in July 8, 2010.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Bic in November, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Minnehaha Academy in August 9, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Mughan FK from December 15, 2011 to December 16, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for La William-Duvel from September, 2010 to November, 2010.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Stonyhurst College from 2010 to 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended Perth Academy in September 17, 2010.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Portsmouth F.C. in February 3, 2010.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Acad\u00e9mica Petr\u00f3leos do Lobito in November, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala attended West Virginia Wesleyan College in January 26, 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Sioux Falls Skyforce from 2010 to 2011.", "Jamal Abu-Shamala plays for Nordsj\u00e6lland H\u00e5ndbold in 2011."], "answer": ["University of Minnesota"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 328, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Steve Nash was playing for Santa Clara Broncos men's basketball, which school did Steve Nash attend during the same time period?", "facts": ["Steve Nash attended Marquette University Law School from March 6, 2010 to December 21, 2011.", "Steve Nash plays for Newport (IOW) F.C. from 2008 to 2010.", "Steve Nash attended South Hampstead High School in 2006.", "Steve Nash attended Katharineum in 1998.", "Steve Nash plays for Dallas Mavericks from 1998 to 2004.", "Steve Nash attended INSEAD from January 7, 2000 to December 24, 2008.", "Steve Nash plays for F.C. Givat Olga from June 2, 2006 to February 6, 2007.", "Steve Nash plays for Santa Clara Broncos men's basketball from 1992 to 1996.", "Steve Nash plays for Wellington Olympic AFC in October, 1999.", "Steve Nash attended Ravensburg University of Cooperative Education in May 8, 2006.", "Steve Nash plays for Clube Desportivo dos Olivais e Moscavide in 2009.", "Steve Nash attended University of the Western Cape in 2009.", "Steve Nash plays for Nottinghamshire Cricket Board from 2000 to 2002.", "Steve Nash plays for Los Angeles Lakers in July 11, 2012.", "Steve Nash attended V. I. Lenin Military-Political Academy from May 21, 1998 to January 26, 2008.", "Steve Nash attended Canterbury School from August, 1999 to March, 2011.", "Steve Nash attended West Virginia University College of Law from 2007 to 2008.", "Steve Nash attended Santa Clara University from 1992 to 1996.", "Steve Nash plays for Riffa S.C. in 2000.", "Steve Nash plays for MFK Viz-Sinara Yekaterinburg in January 25, 2007."], "answer": ["Santa Clara University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 329, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Abraham Alikhanov was holding the position of director, which employer did Abraham Alikhanov work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Abraham Alikhanov works for Ioffe Institute from 1927 to 1941.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of Gresham Professor of Geometry in July, 1931.", "Abraham Alikhanov attended Saint Petersburg State Polytechnical University in 1929.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of Minister of Democracy from December 20, 1929 to February 20, 1931.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of full professor from 1928 to 1938.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for Istituto per le Applicazioni del Calcolo Mauro Picone in January, 1936.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for CBS News from October 17, 1936 to December 25, 1943.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for John Paul II Catholic University of Lublin in 1931.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of Labor Minister of Israel in 1940.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of monarch of the United Kingdom in June, 1934.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for Minnesota State University, Mankato in November 5, 1937.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for MSNBC in 1937.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for Queensland University of Technology in December, 1944.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of pope from May, 1932 to February, 1934.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of director from 1945 to 1968.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for Westminster Theological Seminary from 1935 to 1938.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of President of the Republic of Lithuania in December 19, 1943.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of vicar in June, 1933.", "Abraham Alikhanov holds the position of Secretary for Security in 1939.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for Institute for Theoretical and Experimental Physics from 1945 to 1968.", "Abraham Alikhanov works for King Edward's School in September, 1930."], "answer": ["Institute for Theoretical and Experimental Physics"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 330, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While \u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius was playing for Maryland Terrapins men's basketball, which school did \u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attend during the identical time period?", "facts": ["\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Birmingham City University in November, 2009.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for KK Union Olimpija from 1999 to 2000.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Golden State Warriors in 2007.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for BC \u017dalgiris from 2013 to 2014.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Fenerbah\u00e7e Men's Basketball in 2011.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Berklee College of Music from August 16, 2007 to January 19, 2013.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Peugeot in 2001.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Punahou School in 2000.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Goethe-Institut in October, 2004.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Ressu Upper Secondary School in December, 2007.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Toray Arrows from May 10, 2005 to January 11, 2011.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Maryland Terrapins men's basketball from 1994 to 1998.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Maccabi Tel Aviv B.C. from 2003 to 2005.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Indiana Pacers from 2005 to 2007.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius plays for Mashonaland cricket team in July, 2010.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Washburn University from October, 2006 to September, 2008.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended Hugo Treffner Gymnasium from 2009 to 2010.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended University of Maryland from 1994 to 1998.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended \u00c9cole Libre des Sciences Politiques from 1999 to 2003.", "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius attended The First High School of Changsha, Hunan from May 21, 2001 to February 22, 2010."], "answer": ["University of Maryland"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 331, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Christine Sinclair was playing for Portland Pilots women's soccer, which school did Christine Sinclair attend during the same time period?", "facts": ["Christine Sinclair plays for Portland Pilots women's soccer from 2001 to 2005.", "Christine Sinclair plays for OFK Grbalj from February, 2008 to November, 2010.", "Christine Sinclair attended University of Kentucky College of Law in 2008.", "Christine Sinclair attended University of Portland from 2001 to 2005.", "Christine Sinclair plays for SG Germania Wiesbaden in August 17, 2012.", "Christine Sinclair plays for Canada women's national under-20 association football team from 2001 to 2002.", "Christine Sinclair plays for FC Lukhovitsy in July 14, 2009.", "Christine Sinclair plays for Portland Thorns FC in January 11, 2013.", "Christine Sinclair plays for FC Gold Pride from 2009 to 2010.", "Christine Sinclair plays for CD Illescas from October 18, 2007 to February 20, 2013.", "Christine Sinclair attended Ghana School of Law from March 19, 2010 to September 20, 2013.", "Christine Sinclair plays for Western New York Flash from 2011 to 2012.", "Christine Sinclair attended Kyiv Suvorov Military School from January 1, 2012 to March 5, 2012.", "Christine Sinclair attended University of Texas School of Law in March 14, 2000.", "Christine Sinclair attended University of West Florida in February, 2011.", "Christine Sinclair plays for Canada women's national association football team in 2000.", "Christine Sinclair attended McGeorge School of Law in June, 2009.", "Christine Sinclair attended Antonin Scalia Law School from December 24, 2009 to December 27, 2009.", "Christine Sinclair attended William Penn Charter School from September, 2007 to March, 2009.", "Christine Sinclair attended State and National Law School in April 12, 2013."], "answer": ["University of Portland"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 332, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jess S\u00f8derberg was holding the position of board member, which employer did Jess S\u00f8derberg work for concurrently?", "facts": ["Jess S\u00f8derberg works for University of Cape Town from 1916 to 1947.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Odense Steel Shipyard from June 30, 1944 to September 7, 2001.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Mosque-Cathedral of Cordoba from June 24, 1931 to July 26, 1973.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Columbia Business School in August, 2002.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Danske Bank in March 23, 1999.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Carlsberg Group from March 12, 2009 to March 26, 2015.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of Mayor of Keelung from 1940 to 1981.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of campaign manager in January 6, 2005.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for \u00c9cole du Louvre from 1965 to 2000.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of President of El Salvador in July, 1989.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Bilka from March 11, 1980 to September 19, 2005.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of Anglican Bishop of Lichfield in 1997.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of Minister of Foreign Affairs of Jordan from November 14, 1969 to March 22, 1989.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of board member from March 12, 2009 to March 26, 2015.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of Minister for Women and Equalities in 1993.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Maersk from April 16, 1904 to April 30, 2007.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg works for Salling Group from May 22, 2006 to November 5, 2007.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of Speaker of the National Parliament of Papua New Guinea in 1918.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of full professor in May, 1983.", "Jess S\u00f8derberg holds the position of Governor of California from 1950 to 1958."], "answer": ["Carlsberg Group"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 333, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Dan Nwaelele was playing for Air Force Falcons men's basketball, which school did Dan Nwaelele attend simultaneously?", "facts": ["Dan Nwaelele plays for Air Force Falcons men's basketball from 2003 to 2007.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for Austin Spurs from 2016 to 2017.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Winona State University from 2015 to 2017.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Obafemi Awolowo University from 2013 to 2017.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for Santa Cruz Warriors from 2012 to 2016.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for KK Sloga in September 27, 2008.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for Lithuania national football team in November, 2015.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Royal University of Ireland from April 4, 2014 to June 11, 2016.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for F.C. Sporting Genzano in 2011.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for Metropolitans 92 in 2017.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for IF Ready in 2009.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Grenoble Institute of Political Studies from October 6, 2013 to April 22, 2015.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for SK Gaming from October, 2013 to April, 2017.", "Dan Nwaelele attended North Dakota State University from May, 2011 to September, 2013.", "Dan Nwaelele plays for Nybergsund IL-Trysil from January, 2011 to November, 2011.", "Dan Nwaelele attended United States Air Force Academy from 2003 to 2007.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Oslo Commerce School in 2016.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Regis High School from June, 2010 to August, 2014.", "Dan Nwaelele attended Sturm College of Law from 2008 to 2017.", "Dan Nwaelele attended University of Maryland Francis King Carey School of Law in 2011."], "answer": ["United States Air Force Academy"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 334, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jalen Rose was playing for Michigan Wolverines men's basketball, which school did Jalen Rose attend during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jalen Rose attended \u00c9cole sup\u00e9rieure de guerre from 2004 to 2005.", "Jalen Rose plays for NK Kr\u0161ko from February 6, 1998 to August 10, 2003.", "Jalen Rose attended United States Naval Academy in October, 2000.", "Jalen Rose plays for Michigan Wolverines men's basketball from 1991 to 1994.", "Jalen Rose attended University of Michigan from 1991 to 1994.", "Jalen Rose attended Enskilda Gymnasiet in 2004.", "Jalen Rose plays for Baltimore Bays from September 5, 1998 to January 10, 2005.", "Jalen Rose plays for Cruzeiro E.C. in March 3, 2005.", "Jalen Rose attended Brewster Academy in March, 1997.", "Jalen Rose attended Krasnodar Higher Military Aviation School of Pilots named after Hero of the Soviet Union A.K. Serov from 1998 to 2003.", "Jalen Rose plays for Mutual FC in February, 1995.", "Jalen Rose attended La Salle Academy, Providence in July 1, 1998.", "Jalen Rose plays for Indiana Pacers from 1996 to 2002.", "Jalen Rose plays for SV Schwechat in 1998.", "Jalen Rose plays for U.S. Fiumana in 1997.", "Jalen Rose attended East Central Community College from October, 2000 to May, 2004.", "Jalen Rose attended INSEEC Business School in July, 2005.", "Jalen Rose plays for Alakhdhar S.C. in 2001.", "Jalen Rose plays for FK Ra\u010da in November 5, 2004.", "Jalen Rose attended University of Maryland Global Campus in 2005."], "answer": ["University of Michigan"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 335, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Charles University, which political party did Jan Ml\u00e1dek belong to during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the The Blue Party in December 8, 1985.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Prague University of Economics and Business from 1979 to 1983.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Ball State University from April, 1992 to October, 1994.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the National Resistance Movement from 1980 to 1984.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the Estonian Coalition Party from May 3, 1990 to August 7, 1994.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the Czech Social Democratic Party in 1995.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the No Pokies in 1980.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the Law and Justice in August, 1995.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Manchester University in 1980.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the Group of Independents from August 8, 1991 to November 10, 1992.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Charles University from 1987 to 1989.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the Welfare Party in 1984.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the Communist Party of Czechoslovakia from 1987 to 1989.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Universidad de Panam\u00e1 from December, 1990 to August, 1991.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek is a member of the SYRIZA in 1985.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul in 1992.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Crossroads School from May 15, 1979 to May 20, 1984.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended University of Fort Hare in 1981.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Gray's Inn in 1982.", "Jan Ml\u00e1dek attended Military Academy of the General Staff of the Armed Forces of Russia in February, 1986."], "answer": ["Communist Party of Czechoslovakia"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 336, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Kimeshan Naidoo was holding the position of engineer, which employer did Kimeshan Naidoo work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of Keeper of the Seals of France from February 9, 2019 to August 24, 2019.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of engineer from 2013 to 2015.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of President of the Republic of Lithuania from September, 2016 to April, 2019.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Citro\u00ebn in April 6, 2020.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of President-elect of the United States from June, 2021 to July, 2022.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of chief technology officer from 2016 to 2023.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for University of Turin in March, 2020.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Schlumberger from 2013 to 2015.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of Administrator of NASA from November 19, 2019 to March 28, 2023.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Gallaudet University in 2018.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Colorado College in 2019.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Corvinus University of Budapest in June 28, 2022.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Auckland University of Technology from April 27, 2019 to April 27, 2022.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of Vice-President of the Executive Council from 2018 to 2022.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of master of novices from January 3, 2018 to April 19, 2019.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for United Nations in 2017.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for Sovremennik Theatre in 2023.", "Kimeshan Naidoo works for National and Kapodistrian University of Athens in 2020.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of High Sheriff of Suffolk in 2017.", "Kimeshan Naidoo holds the position of Governor of Delaware in 2020."], "answer": ["Schlumberger"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 337, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Susanna Gideonsson was holding the position of chairperson, which employer did Susanna Gideonsson work for at the same time?", "facts": ["Susanna Gideonsson works for Francis Crick Institute in August, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of chairperson in June 15, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for University of Hohenheim in October 2, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for Toms International in August, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of President of the Liberal Democratic Party in November 10, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of United States Ambassador to Nicaragua in October 7, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of Vice President of Indonesia in January, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for Ara in September, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for Swedish Trade Union Confederation in June 15, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of Mayor of Yerevan in August 1, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for Nottingham Trent University in November 17, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of Minister for Economic Affairs in May 25, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of Minister of Transport and Communications in February 26, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of Labor Minister of Israel in August, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of partner in September, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for NRC Handelsblad in March, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson holds the position of United States senator in July 3, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for Louisiana State University in March, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for West Chester University of Pennsylvania in July 28, 2020.", "Susanna Gideonsson works for London and South Western Railway in November 24, 2020."], "answer": ["Swedish Trade Union Confederation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 338, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Derek Anderson was playing for Ohio State Buckeyes men's basketball, which school did Derek Anderson attend during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Derek Anderson attended Pembroke College from January, 1996 to August, 1996.", "Derek Anderson attended University of Guadalajara in March, 1997.", "Derek Anderson attended Slade School of Fine Art in April 21, 1997.", "Derek Anderson plays for Alemannia Aachen from January, 1997 to February, 1997.", "Derek Anderson attended Ohio State University from 1992 to 1994.", "Derek Anderson plays for FC Mglebi Zugdidi in June 27, 1997.", "Derek Anderson plays for Balestier Khalsa FC in October 27, 1995.", "Derek Anderson attended Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism in April 6, 1997.", "Derek Anderson attended Corcoran College of Art and Design in October 27, 1996.", "Derek Anderson attended Victoria College in December 10, 1995.", "Derek Anderson plays for Ohio State Buckeyes men's basketball from 1992 to 1994.", "Derek Anderson plays for Arna-Bj\u00f8rnar in December, 1997.", "Derek Anderson attended Royal College of Music in Stockholm in June, 1995.", "Derek Anderson plays for St Blazey A.F.C. from January, 1997 to September, 1997.", "Derek Anderson attended Tashkent Suvorov Military School in March 8, 1995.", "Derek Anderson plays for Energetyk ROW Rybnik in January, 1996.", "Derek Anderson plays for Harimau Muda A in March, 1997.", "Derek Anderson plays for Kentucky Wildcats men's basketball from 1995 to 1997.", "Derek Anderson attended Bengaluru University in 1997.", "Derek Anderson plays for Shahin Ahvaz F.C. from September, 1995 to October, 1996."], "answer": ["Ohio State University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 339, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Demian Saffer was holding the position of director, which employer did Demian Saffer work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Demian Saffer holds the position of State Counsellor of Kazakhstan in January 13, 2014.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of campaign manager in December 5, 2002.", "Demian Saffer works for Georgetown University from May, 2004 to February, 2012.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of President of the Generalitat Valenciana from May, 1999 to October, 2007.", "Demian Saffer works for Starwood from June 5, 2015 to January 25, 2016.", "Demian Saffer attended Williams College in 1995.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of director in January 1, 2020.", "Demian Saffer works for NewYork\u2013Presbyterian Hospital in February, 1997.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of Minister of Communications and Multimedia in October, 2017.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of Speaker of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly from May, 1998 to October, 2017.", "Demian Saffer works for University of Texas at Austin in January 1, 2020.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of Vice President of Palau from January, 2016 to March, 2016.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of wissenschaftlicher Assistent in October, 2008.", "Demian Saffer works for City of Basel Music Academy in April, 2017.", "Demian Saffer works for Ernst & Young in 2017.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of adjutant general from December 4, 2001 to April 17, 2018.", "Demian Saffer holds the position of Minister for Tourism in 2006.", "Demian Saffer attended University of California, Santa Cruz in 1999.", "Demian Saffer works for Pacific Northwest National Laboratory in 2015.", "Demian Saffer works for Tilburg University from February, 2000 to May, 2015.", "Demian Saffer works for University of Alabama in Huntsville from February, 2009 to October, 2011.", "Demian Saffer works for Pennsylvania State University from 2005 to 2019."], "answer": ["University of Texas at Austin"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 340, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Steve Alford was playing for Indiana Hoosiers men's basketball, which school did Steve Alford attend within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Steve Alford plays for Oklahoma City Blue in August, 2012.", "Steve Alford works for Missouri State University from 1991 to 1995.", "Steve Alford attended Athens School of Fine Arts in October 27, 1997.", "Steve Alford attended University of Redlands from July, 2010 to July, 2015.", "Steve Alford works for University of California, Los Angeles from 2013 to 2018.", "Steve Alford plays for Tigres de San Luis in January 25, 2005.", "Steve Alford works for University of Iowa from 1995 to 1999.", "Steve Alford plays for Tampa Bay Hellenic in March 6, 2009.", "Steve Alford attended University of Chicago Graduate Library School from 1992 to 2005.", "Steve Alford plays for Sevilla Atl\u00e9tico from March 2, 2017 to March 9, 2017.", "Steve Alford plays for Rubin Kazan from August, 2018 to December, 2018.", "Steve Alford attended Wycliffe Hall in November, 2007.", "Steve Alford plays for Southampton F.C. in October 4, 1989.", "Steve Alford attended Helena High School in December, 1989.", "Steve Alford attended Indiana University Bloomington from 1983 to 1987.", "Steve Alford plays for Brazil national football team from February 14, 2017 to September 17, 2019.", "Steve Alford works for University of Nevada, Reno in 2019.", "Steve Alford works for University of New Mexico from 2007 to 2013.", "Steve Alford plays for VV Alkmaar Vrouwen from 2010 to 2014.", "Steve Alford attended Austin Peay State University in July, 1993.", "Steve Alford attended Lyc\u00e9e Kl\u00e9ber from January, 1997 to February, 2014.", "Steve Alford attended Danish Design School from June 28, 2016 to December 28, 2016.", "Steve Alford attended University of Seville from July 21, 2002 to August 21, 2008.", "Steve Alford plays for Indiana Hoosiers men's basketball from 1983 to 1987.", "Steve Alford plays for TSV Schilksee in 2019."], "answer": ["Indiana University Bloomington"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 341, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Matt Howard was playing for Butler Bulldogs men's basketball, which school did Matt Howard attend during the same time span?", "facts": ["Matt Howard attended East Ukrainian Volodymyr Dahl National University in May 14, 2012.", "Matt Howard attended University of California, Davis, School of Law from May 1, 2014 to August 15, 2015.", "Matt Howard plays for TSV 1860 Rosenheim in September 8, 2015.", "Matt Howard plays for Hapoel Tel Aviv B.C. in 2017.", "Matt Howard plays for Defensores de Cambaceres from December, 2014 to June, 2016.", "Matt Howard plays for Washington Warthogs in November 21, 2014.", "Matt Howard plays for Butler Bulldogs men's basketball from 2007 to 2011.", "Matt Howard attended Butler University from 2007 to 2011.", "Matt Howard attended New Mexico Highlands University in May, 2015.", "Matt Howard plays for G.S. Niki Volou (men's association football) from 2015 to 2016.", "Matt Howard plays for Seattle SuperSonics from June, 2014 to November, 2015.", "Matt Howard attended Christ's Hospital in 2015.", "Matt Howard plays for Armenia national under-17 football team in 2013.", "Matt Howard attended Deerfield Academy in 2017.", "Matt Howard plays for FC Costuleni in May 13, 2015.", "Matt Howard attended Arsakeio in May 27, 2015.", "Matt Howard attended Higher Scientific Institute for Diocesan Priests at St. Augustine's in May 24, 2015.", "Matt Howard plays for Cultural y Deportiva Leonesa from March, 2015 to November, 2017.", "Matt Howard attended Dwight D. Eisenhower School for National Security and Resource Strategy from June, 2012 to November, 2013.", "Matt Howard attended Tokyo University of the Arts in December, 2016."], "answer": ["Butler University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 342, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Daniel Jutras was holding the position of rector, which employer did Daniel Jutras work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Daniel Jutras works for University of Montreal in June 1, 2020.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of Brazilian federal deputy in July 19, 2010.", "Daniel Jutras works for Business Insider from July 3, 1985 to October 6, 1992.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of rector in June 1, 2020.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of Vice-President of the European Commission from April 3, 1998 to August 15, 2007.", "Daniel Jutras attended Harvard Law School in 1985.", "Daniel Jutras works for University of California, Riverside in January, 2009.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of Governor of Balochistan from March 18, 2011 to December 18, 2012.", "Daniel Jutras works for Texas A&M University\u2013Commerce from June 22, 2003 to September 23, 2003.", "Daniel Jutras works for Hellenic Military Academy in April, 2018.", "Daniel Jutras works for Amtrak in June, 2013.", "Daniel Jutras works for Stellantis from July, 1997 to May, 1998.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of chairperson in February 3, 1987.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of minister of information from June, 2006 to February, 2009.", "Daniel Jutras works for Montefiore Medical Center in December, 2016.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of Minister of State for Europe in 1993.", "Daniel Jutras works for Sports Illustrated in 1989.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice and Tackling Illegal Migration in April, 2012.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of b\u00e2tonnier in April 9, 2006.", "Daniel Jutras works for University of British Columbia from October, 2014 to November, 2014.", "Daniel Jutras holds the position of United States Ambassador to South Africa in 1995."], "answer": ["University of Montreal"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 343, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Martin Mayhew was playing for Florida State Seminoles football, which school did Martin Mayhew attend within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Martin Mayhew attended Kungsholmens gymnasium in 2020.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Florida State Seminoles football from 1983 to 1987.", "Martin Mayhew attended Western Reserve Academy from 2009 to 2013.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Lehigh Valley IronPigs from February, 1996 to July, 2015.", "Martin Mayhew plays for FC Arsenal Tula in May 9, 2007.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Tampa Bay Buccaneers from 1993 to 1996.", "Martin Mayhew works for New York Giants from February 11, 2016 to February 9, 2017.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Buffalo Bills in 1988.", "Martin Mayhew attended Florida State University from 1983 to 1987.", "Martin Mayhew works for Detroit Lions from September 24, 2008 to November 5, 2015.", "Martin Mayhew attended Lyc\u00e9e Kl\u00e9ber in February, 1989.", "Martin Mayhew attended Georgetown University Law Center from 1997 to 2000.", "Martin Mayhew attended Upsala College in June 5, 2021.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Inner Mongolia Caoshangfei F.C. from June, 2013 to August, 2019.", "Martin Mayhew attended University of Sopron in 2009.", "Martin Mayhew attended Coker College from April 20, 1995 to August 20, 2014.", "Martin Mayhew attended King Juan Carlos University from July, 1991 to November, 1997.", "Martin Mayhew works for San Francisco 49ers from February 9, 2017 to January 22, 2021.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Australia national rugby union team from December, 1995 to March, 2018.", "Martin Mayhew attended Technical University of Sofia in 2006.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Gallitos de Isabela in 2019.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Iran B national football team in July 14, 1989.", "Martin Mayhew plays for Colorado Caribous from April 2, 1993 to July 19, 2008."], "answer": ["Florida State University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 344, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 was playing for BYU Cougars men's basketball, which school did Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attend within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Brigham Young University from 1970 to 1973.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Monrovia Black Star F.C. from March, 1982 to March, 1983.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Virtus Pallacanestro Bologna from 1978 to 1980.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Suffolk University Law School from September 2, 1976 to December 6, 1976.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Beylerbeyi S.K. in May 13, 1978.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for KK Union Olimpija from 1976 to 1978.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Club Necaxa from October 6, 1978 to October 20, 1980.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for BYU Cougars men's basketball from 1970 to 1973.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for KK Cibona from 1980 to 1983.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Hurac\u00e1n Buceo in November 14, 1978.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Baku Higher Combined Arms Command School in March, 1974.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended The Manchester Grammar School in March, 1980.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Adama City F.C. in 1981.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Asti Leku Ikastola in September 18, 1980.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 plays for Mazara Calcio A.S.D. in August, 1976.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended McGill University Faculty of Medicine and Health Sciences from February 7, 1978 to November 22, 1980.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Woodrow Wilson High School from July, 1980 to August, 1980.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Varvakeio from April 6, 1982 to August 14, 1982.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Benedictine High School of Pannonhalma from April 17, 1983 to December 24, 1983.", "Kre\u0161imir \u0106osi\u0107 attended Sherborne School from 1974 to 1983."], "answer": ["Brigham Young University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 345, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Tatyana Lysova was holding the position of correspondent, which employer did Tatyana Lysova work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Tatyana Lysova works for University of Cincinnati in January, 1993.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of King of Saudi Arabia from September 11, 2009 to January 27, 2019.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of Minister of Rural and Regional Development from October, 2003 to November, 2003.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of Governor of Maine in May 13, 2021.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of Bishop of Grimsby in February 17, 2007.", "Tatyana Lysova attended Moscow State Institute of Radio-engineering Electronics and Automation in 1991.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Kommersant from 1994 to 1995.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Conseil d'\u00c9tat in December 9, 1992.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Meduza from January, 2020 to August, 2021.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of correspondent from 1994 to 1995.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of editor-in-chief from 2002 to 2007.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of Reichsstatthalter from March 19, 2020 to March 26, 2020.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of city manager from August 23, 2003 to January 28, 2017.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Austin College from 2011 to 2019.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Interfax from January, 2018 to December, 2019.", "Tatyana Lysova works for University of Marburg in 2007.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Institute of Oriental Studies of the Russian Academy of Sciences in November, 2016.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of Minister for Forests in February 25, 2021.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Brunel University London in August, 2008.", "Tatyana Lysova works for Arthur Andersen from July 11, 2015 to December 14, 2016.", "Tatyana Lysova holds the position of Chief of the Naval Staff in 2020."], "answer": ["Kommersant"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 346, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Daniel O'Connell was holding the position of director, which employer did Daniel O'Connell work for within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Daniel O'Connell works for Indiana University Bloomington from June, 1930 to January, 1935.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of president from 1968 to 1972.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of President pro tempore of the Senate of the Philippines in July 10, 1932.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Ioffe Institute from July 14, 1929 to February 26, 1937.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of Vice-President of Kenya in August, 1933.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Vatican Observatory from 1952 to 1970.", "Daniel O'Connell works for College of William & Mary in 1948.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of director from 1952 to 1970.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of Governor General of Canada from April 4, 1925 to January 23, 1934.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Hangzhou University in December, 1933.", "Daniel O'Connell works for University of Iowa College of Law from December 7, 1972 to December 22, 1972.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Harvard College Observatory from 1931 to 1933.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Saint Ignatius' College, Riverview from 1922 to 1926.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of Minister of State at the Department of Enterprise, Trade and Employment from 1929 to 1943.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of Minister for Nordic Co-operation from December 23, 1971 to December 28, 1971.", "Daniel O'Connell attended University College Dublin in 1920.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Cardiff Metropolitan University in 1929.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of Italian Minister of Public Administration in August, 1943.", "Daniel O'Connell works for Ludwig Maximilian University of Munich in 1922.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of Governor of New Mexico in September 14, 1938.", "Daniel O'Connell holds the position of President of the National Assembly of Ecuador in 1923."], "answer": ["Vatican Observatory"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 347, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Toomas Sildm\u00e4e was holding the position of Minister of Economic Affairs and Communications, which political party did Toomas Sildm\u00e4e belong to simultaneously?", "facts": ["Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of Metropolitan Police Department of the District of Columbia Chief in May, 2016.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Res Publica Party from 2001 to 2006.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Hungarian Socialist Party in 1996.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of President of Pakistan from February, 1999 to May, 2007.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the The Patriots in 1990.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of chief human resources officer in December, 2015.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Revolutionary Communist League in June 21, 1996.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of President of the Pontifical Commission for the Vatican City State in September, 1982.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of organizational founder in 1983.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of Bishop of Mauritius from 2014 to 2017.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Isamaa from 2006 to 2022.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of Minister of Mobility from September 18, 2021 to October 25, 2021.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of Governor of New Jersey in 2013.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Direction \u2013 Social Democracy from April 21, 2015 to August 25, 2018.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of Minister of Economic Affairs and Communications from 1993 to 1994.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Communist Party of Austria in November, 2013.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Conservative People's Party of Estonia in 1979.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e holds the position of Governor of the Falkland Islands in 2001.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the National Coalition Party Pro Patria from 1993 to 1994.", "Toomas Sildm\u00e4e is a member of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union in 1979."], "answer": ["National Coalition Party Pro Patria"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 348, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Elselijn Kingma was holding the position of full professor, which employer did Elselijn Kingma work for at the same time?", "facts": ["Elselijn Kingma works for King's College London in January 1, 2021.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of United States Ambassador to Poland in 2016.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of California State Controller in 2020.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of mayor of Tianjin in April, 2017.", "Elselijn Kingma works for Sender Freies Berlin in January, 2015.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of Speaker of the House of Representatives of the Philippines from 2009 to 2013.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of Indiana Attorney General in November, 2013.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of New Jersey Attorney General in July, 2018.", "Elselijn Kingma works for National University of Uzbekistan from July, 2015 to February, 2020.", "Elselijn Kingma works for Queensland Museum in 2009.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of full professor in January 1, 2021.", "Elselijn Kingma works for Medical University of Warsaw from January, 2011 to March, 2016.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of Minister of Law and Justice of India in July, 2013.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of United States Attorney for the Northern District of New York from August 12, 2012 to June 18, 2015.", "Elselijn Kingma works for University of Southampton from 2013 to December 31, 2020.", "Elselijn Kingma works for The Royal London Hospital from April 21, 2013 to November 28, 2015.", "Elselijn Kingma works for Salamanca New Cathedral in March 25, 2017.", "Elselijn Kingma holds the position of Minister for Co-operative Societies in February 11, 2017.", "Elselijn Kingma works for Office of the President of the Philippines from June 26, 2016 to May 28, 2018.", "Elselijn Kingma attended University of Cambridge in 2008.", "Elselijn Kingma works for State University of New York at Plattsburgh in October, 2009."], "answer": ["King's College London"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 349, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Alma Zadi\u0107 was holding the position of Federal Minister of Justice, which employer did Alma Zadi\u0107 work for at the same time?", "facts": ["Alma Zadi\u0107 works for University of Pennsylvania from August 28, 2004 to February 28, 2012.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for University of Massachusetts Dartmouth in May 24, 2016.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Prime Minister of Australia in August, 2003.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Federal Minister of Justice in January 7, 2020.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for University of North Carolina from 2004 to 2018.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Attorney-General for Australia in December, 2004.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston in 2005.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for Dana\u2013Farber Cancer Institute from November, 2005 to December, 2010.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for Austrian Federal Government in January 7, 2020.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 is a member of the Die Gr\u00fcnen in July, 2019.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Prime Minister of Kazakhstan from 2009 to 2014.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Lieutenant Governor of Nevada from August 25, 2011 to November 28, 2019.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Minister for the Union from February, 2007 to February, 2014.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for Amsterdam in 2014.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 attended University of Vienna from 2003 to 2007.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for Georgetown University from November, 2009 to August, 2012.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of list of governors of the Leeward Islands from March 10, 2017 to December 17, 2019.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for Johannes Kepler University Linz from 2018 to 2019.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of President of the Palestinian National Authority in April 14, 2019.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Transport from 2008 to 2016.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 holds the position of Secretary of State for the Southern Department in October 13, 2006.", "Alma Zadi\u0107 works for Sorbonne Nouvelle-Paris 3 from June, 2009 to June, 2015."], "answer": ["Austrian Federal Government"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 350, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Nooshi Dadgostar was holding the position of party leader, which political party did Nooshi Dadgostar belong to within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Kenya African National Union in September, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Social Democratic Workers' Party of Germany in November 27, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the French Socialist Party in September 24, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of b\u00e2tonnier in December 21, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Communist Party of Norway in May 28, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of Defence Minister of Denmark in June, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the National Liberal Party in December, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of party leader in October 31, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Left Party in October 31, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of ambassador of Ukraine to the United States in April 18, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of President of Cuba in July 2, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of archpriest in September 24, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Democratic Social Party in January 25, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Servant of the People in April, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of Senior Advisor to the President of the United States in August 9, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of Prime Minister of South Korea in May, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Western Australian Labor Party in December, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of General Secretary of the Lao People's Revolutionary Party in June 26, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar holds the position of reader in July 16, 2020.", "Nooshi Dadgostar is a member of the Danish People's Party in September, 2020."], "answer": ["Left Party"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 351, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Chavonda Jacobs-Young was holding the position of assistant professor, which employer did Chavonda Jacobs-Young work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Speaker of the Parliament of Singapore from 1989 to 1991.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for Rhodes College in September, 1994.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Minister of Internal Affairs of Georgia from 1990 to 1991.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Lord Lieutenant of Northamptonshire in 1990.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of research associate in June 22, 1990.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Minister of Small Business and Tourism from 1989 to 1992.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for Hiram College in 1991.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young attended North Carolina State University in 1989.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Mayor of Taoyuan in November 20, 1994.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of party chair in February, 1989.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of assistant professor from 1995 to 2002.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for University of Washington from 1995 to 2002.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for University of Maryland Global Campus in 1991.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Prime Minister of Haiti in February 22, 1990.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for University of Eastern Finland from April, 1990 to March, 1991.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for Drexel University in November, 1992.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for Oregon Shakespeare Festival in 1990.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for Notting Hill and Ealing High School in 1992.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for All-Russian Scientific Research Institute of Experimental Physics in February 16, 1991.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young works for University of Dayton from June, 1989 to August, 1989.", "Chavonda Jacobs-Young holds the position of Minister for Western Sydney from January 15, 1990 to December 18, 1993."], "answer": ["University of Washington"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 352, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Daniel L. Ritchie was holding the position of chancellor, which employer did Daniel L. Ritchie work for at the same time?", "facts": ["Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of Minister of State for Consumer Affairs and Food Safety from March 20, 1984 to July 22, 1988.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Rhodes College from January 24, 1980 to December 28, 1986.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Azerbaijan in 1988.", "Daniel L. Ritchie attended Harvard Business School in 1956.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Bauakademie in July 27, 1961.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Sony from 1963 to 1987.", "Daniel L. Ritchie attended Harvard University in 1954.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of mayor of Shanghai from November, 1965 to July, 1980.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of Secretary of State for Economic Affairs in 1960.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of Permanent Representative of Australia to the United Nations in 1982.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of chancellor from July, 1989 to June, 2005.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of list of governors of the Leeward Islands in August, 1983.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Stern School of Business from February 18, 1969 to December 26, 1980.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of Federal Minister of Foreign Affairs of Austria in April, 1959.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Mossovet Theatre in March, 1972.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Confederation of Danish Industries in March, 1962.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for University of Denver from July, 1989 to June, 2005.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of dean of York from April, 1960 to August, 1978.", "Daniel L. Ritchie holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of India in March, 1960.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Shirley Institute in December 10, 1978.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for The Oregonian from June, 1962 to February, 1983.", "Daniel L. Ritchie works for Houston Police Department in April 15, 1977."], "answer": ["University of Denver"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 353, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While John Edensor Littlewood was holding the position of Rouse Ball Professor of Mathematics, which employer did John Edensor Littlewood work for at the same time?", "facts": ["John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Postmaster General of the United Kingdom in 1915.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for University of Cambridge from 1928 to 1950.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of United States Secretary of Housing and Urban Development in October 20, 1902.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Minister for Community Safety and Legal Affairs in January 13, 1920.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for National Gallery of Art in September 8, 1919.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Bishop of Carlisle from June, 1903 to June, 1921.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for Air Force Research Laboratory in December 13, 1922.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for Medical University of South Carolina in December, 1906.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Director of National Intelligence in December, 1924.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for University of the District of Columbia in November 18, 1901.", "John Edensor Littlewood attended St Paul's School from 1900 to 1903.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for National Physical Laboratory in November 9, 1911.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Rouse Ball Professor of Mathematics from 1928 to 1950.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for Victoria University of Manchester from 1907 to 1910.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for Keble College in 1916.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for Office of Economic Opportunity from July 1, 1902 to May 1, 1917.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Prime Minister of New Zealand in 1914.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Counsellor of State in February 20, 1905.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of Speaker of the National Assembly of Azerbaijan in November, 1908.", "John Edensor Littlewood works for Brooklyn College in 1912.", "John Edensor Littlewood holds the position of High Sheriff of Berkshire in September 7, 1905."], "answer": ["University of Cambridge"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 354, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Paul Langevin was holding the position of professor, which employer did Paul Langevin work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Paul Langevin works for University of Padua in 1905.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of Treasurer of Western Australia in 1903.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of Leader of the Labour Party in March 24, 1905.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of director from 1925 to 1946.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of Deputy Premier of South Australia in October 7, 1899.", "Paul Langevin attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure from 1894 to 1897.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of organizational founder from 1934 to 1939.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of Prime Minister of Lithuania in October 14, 1896.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of manager in October, 1894.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of Shadow Home Secretary in November 12, 1897.", "Paul Langevin works for Canadian National Railway in 1895.", "Paul Langevin works for Colorado College in May 19, 1896.", "Paul Langevin works for Coll\u00e8ge de France from 1909 to 1946.", "Paul Langevin works for University of Rennes in August, 1902.", "Paul Langevin works for Augsburg University in 1899.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of professor from 1909 to 1946.", "Paul Langevin works for Gonzaga College High School in June, 1901.", "Paul Langevin holds the position of Minister for Government Coordination in July, 1896.", "Paul Langevin works for Bezalel Academy of Art and Design in July 5, 1894.", "Paul Langevin is a member of the French Communist Party in 1944.", "Paul Langevin works for Northwest Missouri State University in October 6, 1907.", "Paul Langevin works for Brunel University London in 1901."], "answer": ["Coll\u00e8ge de France"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 355, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While John Clarke Young was holding the position of president, which employer did John Clarke Young work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["John Clarke Young works for Hans Apel in August 16, 1824.", "John Clarke Young works for Concordia University in May 15, 1826.", "John Clarke Young works for Tongji University in April 27, 1827.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of ambassador of United States to South Korea in December 11, 1829.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of Chairman of Committees of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly in March 13, 1829.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of Minister of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism in June 18, 1828.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of Minister for Resource Management in July 9, 1829.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of Assistant Secretary of the Treasury for Economic Policy in November 26, 1825.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of United States Ambassador to Burkina Faso in July 1, 1828.", "John Clarke Young works for Centre College from 1830 to 1857.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of Secretary of Budget and Management in September, 1823.", "John Clarke Young works for New York Evening Mail from November, 1827 to October, 1828.", "John Clarke Young works for Gerasimov Institute of Cinematography in March, 1823.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of pastor in 1834.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of President of the European Parliament in May 22, 1828.", "John Clarke Young works for University of Bradford in May, 1824.", "John Clarke Young holds the position of president from 1830 to 1857.", "John Clarke Young works for Austrian Academy of Sciences from December 4, 1823 to December 12, 1826.", "John Clarke Young works for Supreme Court of the United States in January 2, 1826.", "John Clarke Young attended Dickinson College in 1823.", "John Clarke Young attended Princeton Theological Seminary in 1828.", "John Clarke Young works for Greek National Opera in July, 1824."], "answer": ["Centre College"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 356, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Stephen J. Mackwell was holding the position of director, which employer did Stephen J. Mackwell work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Stephen J. Mackwell works for Penn Central Transportation Company in November 23, 1990.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for Telewizja Polska from January, 1979 to September, 1987.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for University of W\u00fcrzburg in 2000.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Transport from August, 1981 to March, 1999.", "Stephen J. Mackwell attended University of Canterbury in 1978.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Under-Secretary-General of the United Nations in January, 1988.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for Lunar and Planetary Institute from 2002 to 2016.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of United States Secretary of Defense from 1993 to 1998.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of senior advisor in 1999.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Finnish Minister for European Affairs in 1978.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Cardinal Secretary of State in February, 1982.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of director from 2002 to 2016.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for New York Evening Mail in 1992.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for Herzen University in March, 1996.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Irish Minister for Health in 1993.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Premier of New South Wales in 1982.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for University of Lancaster in January, 1983.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for Oklahoma State University System from June 28, 1997 to March 28, 1999.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for University of Bonn in March, 1999.", "Stephen J. Mackwell works for FIH Erhvervsbank A/S in April 11, 1989.", "Stephen J. Mackwell attended Australian National University in 1985.", "Stephen J. Mackwell holds the position of Minister for Health of Denmark in August, 1997."], "answer": ["Lunar and Planetary Institute"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 357, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Agnes de Selincourt was holding the position of principal, which employer did Agnes de Selincourt work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of principal from 1913 to 1917.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of assistant professor in June 10, 1897.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of city council in December 14, 1903.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for University of California, Berkeley in 1895.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for The Baltimore Sun in June 28, 1889.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of professor from November, 1892 to September, 1906.", "Agnes de Selincourt attended Girton College from 1891 to 1894.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of Secretary of State of Texas from May, 1890 to December, 1911.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for Carl Zeiss AG in 1906.", "Agnes de Selincourt attended Notting Hill and Ealing High School from 1889 to 1891.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of Bishop of Oxford from June, 1891 to January, 1896.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for University of Siena from September 6, 1890 to June 19, 1897.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for Westfield College from 1913 to 1917.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of Bishop of Gloucester in November, 1895.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of Minister of Finance of Sri Lanka from 1897 to 1900.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for municipality of Paris in 1901.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for GN Store Nord from 1901 to 1912.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for Fairchild Semiconductor from 1895 to 1896.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for Polish Press Agency from April, 1894 to August, 1910.", "Agnes de Selincourt attended Somerville College from 1895 to 1896.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of Mayor of Taipei in May 26, 1894.", "Agnes de Selincourt works for Geod\u00e6tisk Institut in May, 1903.", "Agnes de Selincourt holds the position of Prime Minister of Haiti in January 12, 1902."], "answer": ["Westfield College"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 358, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While C. Lee Giles was holding the position of full professor, which employer did C. Lee Giles work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["C. Lee Giles holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Safeguarding from 1993 to 1994.", "C. Lee Giles works for Harvard Medical School in November, 1981.", "C. Lee Giles works for Museum of London from January 5, 1998 to July 27, 1999.", "C. Lee Giles works for Cranleigh School in November 27, 1984.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of chief operating officer from 1990 to 1996.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of chef de cabinet from 1988 to 1999.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation from 1981 to 1992.", "C. Lee Giles works for Gainax in 1968.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of Federal Chancellor of Germany from May, 1972 to September, 1999.", "C. Lee Giles works for Pennsylvania State University in August 15, 2000.", "C. Lee Giles works for Cambridge Observatory from September, 1991 to October, 1992.", "C. Lee Giles attended Rhodes College from 1964 to 1967.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of Republican Conference Vice-Chairman of the United States House of Representatives from February, 1966 to November, 1971.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of full professor in August 15, 2000.", "C. Lee Giles attended University of Tennessee, Knoxville from 1967 to 1969.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of Cabinet Secretary for Justice in December, 1998.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of President of the Bundestag from August, 1989 to January, 1992.", "C. Lee Giles works for Bletchley Park from 1964 to 1990.", "C. Lee Giles works for Sampension in September, 1992.", "C. Lee Giles attended University of Arizona from 1975 to 1981.", "C. Lee Giles works for Naval Academy at M\u00fcrwik from December 15, 1986 to August 17, 1987.", "C. Lee Giles works for Mattel from May 17, 1969 to December 26, 1969.", "C. Lee Giles holds the position of Vice President of Guyana from October 20, 1981 to December 27, 1986.", "C. Lee Giles attended University of Michigan from 1969 to August 31, 1973."], "answer": ["Pennsylvania State University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 359, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Friedrich Nietzsche was holding the position of full professor, which employer did Friedrich Nietzsche work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of United States Ambassador to Italy from September, 1866 to October, 1867.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of full professor from 1869 to 1878.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Government of South Australia from December 19, 1879 to December 26, 1879.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of Kultus Minister of Denmark in March, 1868.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Danish Health Authority in July 15, 1867.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of Minister for Human Services in 1859.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for University of Basel from 1869 to 1878.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Tagesspiegel from January 20, 1860 to February 20, 1865.", "Friedrich Nietzsche attended University of Bonn from September, 1864 to 1865.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for University of Granada in April, 1867.", "Friedrich Nietzsche attended Leipzig University from 1865 to 1879.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Humboldt University of Berlin in October 9, 1864.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of Governor of British Ceylon in October 13, 1863.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Pontifical Biblical Institute in 1867.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of state treasurer in November 23, 1858.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of Vice President of the European Parliament in February 20, 1879.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of Prime Minister of Latvia in 1858.", "Friedrich Nietzsche attended Landesschule Pforta in October 5, 1858.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Spanish National Research Council from 1858 to 1862.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for Museum of New Zealand Te Papa Tongarewa in March 23, 1861.", "Friedrich Nietzsche works for University of Bucharest in April, 1858.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of Illinois Secretary of State in September 8, 1868.", "Friedrich Nietzsche holds the position of United States Ambassador to the United Nations Human Rights Council in 1868."], "answer": ["University of Basel"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 360, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Robert von Zimmermann was holding the position of wissenschaftlicher Assistent, which employer did Robert von Zimmermann work for concurrently?", "facts": ["Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of First Secretary of the French Socialist Party from July, 1860 to October, 1869.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for Office de Radiodiffusion T\u00e9l\u00e9vision Fran\u00e7aise in June, 1878.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for Niels Bohr Institute in September 22, 1853.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of President of the Liberal Democrats in June, 1864.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for Institute of Advanced Studies in 1853.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of President of the Basque Autonomous Community from December, 1854 to May, 1860.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of Governor of California in 1861.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of wissenschaftlicher Assistent from March, 1847 to 1849.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of rector from 1886 to 1887.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for University of Minnesota from September 8, 1871 to April 21, 1883.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for State University of New York College of Environmental Science and Forestry in January, 1853.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of President of the Chamber of Deputies of Romania from April 22, 1862 to July 28, 1869.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for University of Michigan in July, 1875.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for Tbilisi State Academy of Arts from 1863 to 1864.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for Vienna Observatory from March, 1847 to 1849.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of Secretary of State for Business and Trade from April, 1857 to November, 1866.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for National Theatre in June 27, 1875.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of President of the Australian Senate in July 13, 1885.", "Robert von Zimmermann holds the position of Mayor of Montreal from April, 1874 to February, 1878.", "Robert von Zimmermann works for University of Toledo in July, 1871."], "answer": ["Vienna Observatory"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 361, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While George Frederick James Temple was holding the position of Sedleian Professor of Natural Philosophy, which employer did George Frederick James Temple work for during the identical time period?", "facts": ["George Frederick James Temple works for Instituto Tecnol\u00f3gico de Aeron\u00e1utica in January, 1923.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of Vice Chief of Army Staff in January, 1940.", "George Frederick James Temple works for University of Cambridge from 1929 to 1930.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Innovation from March, 1935 to August, 1947.", "George Frederick James Temple works for German Research Center for Artificial Intelligence in July 14, 1946.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of Bishop of Willesden in December, 1923.", "George Frederick James Temple works for University of Southern Maine in September 23, 1944.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of State Auditor of Mississippi in April 10, 1920.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of European Commissioner for Agriculture in December 22, 1949.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of bishop from July, 1924 to April, 1937.", "George Frederick James Temple works for University of Caen Normandy in 1937.", "George Frederick James Temple works for TDC in December 4, 1919.", "George Frederick James Temple works for HOFOR in March 18, 1941.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of United States Associate Attorney General in May, 1949.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of President of Paraguay in 1944.", "George Frederick James Temple works for Warsaw University of Technology from 1940 to 1943.", "George Frederick James Temple works for University of Oxford from 1953 to 1968.", "George Frederick James Temple works for Prudential plc from 1917 to 1919.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of General Commander of the Peruvian Army in 1927.", "George Frederick James Temple holds the position of Sedleian Professor of Natural Philosophy from 1953 to 1968."], "answer": ["University of Oxford"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 362, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Ant\u00f3nio Guterres was holding the position of United Nations Secretary-General, which employer did Ant\u00f3nio Guterres work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for United Nations in January 1, 2017.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres attended Instituto Superior T\u00e9cnico in 1971.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Tomsk Polytechnic University in December 8, 1976.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs from November 21, 2001 to November 22, 2008.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of assessor in 2004.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Director of the National Security Agency from 1990 to 1995.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees from June 15, 2005 to December 31, 2015.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Minister of Finance of Sri Lanka from February 11, 1981 to October 15, 1984.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Minister of Public Service and Administration in July 20, 2012.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres is a member of the Socialist Party in 1974.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Comptroller of the Household in 1999.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Federal Communications Commission in 1986.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Deputy Prime Minister of the Netherlands in May 6, 1989.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Sveriges Television from 1986 to 2014.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of Prime Minister of Portugal from October 28, 1995 to April 6, 2002.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Amazon Web Services from March, 1972 to March, 1979.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres holds the position of United Nations Secretary-General in January 1, 2017.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Astronomical Observatory of Capodimonte from 1978 to 2003.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Pivdenmash in May, 1975.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for University of Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4 from September 18, 2006 to August 28, 2010.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for Pembroke College from February, 1981 to February, 2004.", "Ant\u00f3nio Guterres works for German Council on Foreign Relations in 1998."], "answer": ["United Nations"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 363, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While George H. W. Bush was holding the position of Director of Central Intelligence, which employer did George H. W. Bush work for simultaneously?", "facts": ["George H. W. Bush holds the position of President-elect of the United States from November 8, 1988 to January 20, 1989.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of postmaster from December 10, 1948 to July 10, 1951.", "George H. W. Bush works for ABC News in May, 1947.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of Shadow First Secretary of State from July 15, 1988 to July 26, 1988.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of Director of Central Intelligence from January 30, 1976 to January 20, 1977.", "George H. W. Bush attended Phillips Academy from 1936 to 1942.", "George H. W. Bush attended Yale University from 1945 to 1948.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of President of the United States from January 20, 1989 to January 20, 1993.", "George H. W. Bush works for Coll\u00e8ge international de philosophie from July, 1948 to December, 1968.", "George H. W. Bush works for Widener University from December, 1950 to January, 1968.", "George H. W. Bush works for Maxim Tank Belarusian State Pedagogical University in June, 1986.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of Vice President of the United States from January 20, 1981 to January 20, 1989.", "George H. W. Bush works for Cleveland State University in August, 1963.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of United States representative from January 3, 1967 to January 3, 1971.", "George H. W. Bush works for Presidential Administration of Russia from February, 1979 to July, 1986.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of President of Slovakia in 1945.", "George H. W. Bush works for United Arab Emirates University in August, 1985.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of diplomat in December, 1943.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of Governor of Kansas from 1988 to 1991.", "George H. W. Bush works for Kingston University in November 27, 1939.", "George H. W. Bush works for University of Granada from July, 1953 to December, 1954.", "George H. W. Bush works for Central Intelligence Agency from January 30, 1976 to January 20, 1977."], "answer": ["Central Intelligence Agency"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 364, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville was holding the position of professor, which employer did Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for Chouinard Art Institute in March 20, 1860.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of heir presumptive in 1846.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for Imperial School of Jurisprudence from December, 1844 to March, 1850.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville attended Mines ParisTech from November 24, 1836 to September, 1838.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of President of the National Assembly of Ecuador in January 18, 1839.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of professor from 1875 to 1876.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of Advocate General for Northern Ireland from March 5, 1846 to January 14, 1868.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for Coll\u00e8ge de France from 1875 to 1876.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of Solicitor General for Scotland from January, 1857 to September, 1860.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of pr\u00e9sident-directeur g\u00e9n\u00e9ral from May, 1866 to December, 1873.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for DADES in November, 1855.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of Interrex in 1855.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of Director of the United States Mint from September, 1849 to January, 1873.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory in 1849.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of United States Ambassador to the Philippines in 1855.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for Gerasimov Institute of Cinematography in 1866.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for University of Maryland, Baltimore County from 1837 to 1842.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for AvtoRadio from 1860 to 1870.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville holds the position of lieutenant general from September, 1848 to December, 1848.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for University of Canterbury from 1872 to 1873.", "Charles Joseph Sainte-Claire Deville works for Otis College of Art and Design from November 12, 1854 to January 28, 1865."], "answer": ["Coll\u00e8ge de France"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 365, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont was holding the position of professor, which employer did Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of United Kingdom Permanent Secretary in October, 1823.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont attended \u00c9cole polytechnique from 1817 to 1819.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont attended Mines ParisTech from 1819 to 1820.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Hairenik in 1831.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of professor from 1832 to 1874.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of Confederate States Secretary of State in April 18, 1818.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Chautauqua Institution in 1830.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of State Auditor of Mississippi in 1827.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Coll\u00e8ge de France from 1832 to 1874.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for National Institute of Standards and Technology in July, 1828.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Artsakh University in 1819.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Admiralty Research Laboratory in 1823.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Sanasarian College from 1820 to 1823.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of trustee in December, 1828.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of Supreme Leader of North Korea in December 18, 1821.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of Minister for Fair Trading in June, 1829.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for King Edward VI High School for Girls, Birmingham in 1831.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of Speaker of the New South Wales Legislative Assembly in 1822.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of Magistrate of Taoyuan County in December 1, 1824.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Department for Transport in April, 1823.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont works for Fagligt F\u00e6lles Forbund from 1823 to 1826.", "Jean Baptiste Armand Louis L\u00e9on\u00e9e Elie de Beaumont holds the position of Minister of Local Government of New Zealand in 1817."], "answer": ["Coll\u00e8ge de France"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 366, "triple_element": "S1_R2_O2", "question": "While Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus was holding the position of Director-General of the World Health Organization, which employer did Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus work for during the same time span?", "facts": ["Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of Director-General of the World Health Organization in July 1, 2017.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for World Health Organization in July 1, 2017.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Presidency University in July 1, 2012.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Academy of Sciences of Albania from 2002 to 2012.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of United States Ambassador to Burkina Faso from 1999 to 2008.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Evangelisches Gymnasium zum Grauen Kloster in March 1, 1995.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of Treasurer of New South Wales in November 26, 1994.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of rector in 2000.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Royal Society for the Protection of Birds in December 4, 2012.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus attended London School of Hygiene & Tropical Medicine in 1992.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for New College from November 22, 2014 to November 23, 2014.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Charles Sturt University in 2014.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of President of the French Republic from 2009 to 2016.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of United States Ambassador to Switzerland and Liechtenstein in 2012.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of Minister of International Trade and Industry in October 2, 2001.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for KMD from August, 2010 to August, 2011.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of Permanent Representative of the United Kingdom to the United Nations, New York in September, 2004.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship in 2013.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus attended University of Nottingham in 2000.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Hanover University of Music, Drama and Media from September 20, 1999 to December 27, 2003.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus holds the position of Shadow Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change from 2005 to 2008.", "Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus works for Carnegie Institute of Technology in June 7, 1993."], "answer": ["World Health Organization"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 367, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Neill Roberts was playing for Durban City F.C., who was also playing for Durban City F.C. simultaneously?", "facts": ["Aleksei Snigiryov plays for Durban City F.C. from April, 1979 to June, 1980.", "Bruce Grobbelaar plays for Durban City F.C. from 1977 to 1978.", "Elison Fagundes dos Santos plays for Durban City F.C. in 1983.", "Mick Channon plays for Durban City F.C. in 1983.", "Ryan Brunt plays for Durban City F.C. in March 7, 1974.", "Adrian Pitu plays for Durban City F.C. in July 28, 1975.", "Carles Domingo Pladevall plays for Durban City F.C. in October 23, 1980.", "Tony Coleman plays for Durban City F.C. from 1972 to 1973.", "Neill Roberts plays for Durban City F.C. from 1977 to 1978.", "Nacho Novo plays for Durban City F.C. in October, 1981."], "answer": ["Bruce Grobbelaar"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 368, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Adrian Hayes was playing for Diss Town F.C., who was also playing for Diss Town F.C. during the same time span?", "facts": ["Ra\u00fal Caballero plays for Diss Town F.C. in August 5, 2010.", "Alessandro Zarrelli plays for Diss Town F.C. from 2012 to 2013.", "Adrian Hayes plays for Diss Town F.C. from 1999 to 2000.", "Myles Weston plays for Diss Town F.C. from July, 2002 to May, 2003.", "Borja Valle plays for Diss Town F.C. from 2005 to 2013.", "Darren Mansaram plays for Diss Town F.C. from August 19, 2010 to November 20, 2012.", "Jos\u00e9 Fonte plays for Diss Town F.C. from October, 2007 to February, 2012.", "Bobby Mayes plays for Diss Town F.C. from 1999 to 2000.", "Lee Norfolk plays for Diss Town F.C. from 2007 to 2008.", "Marcelo Roberto Lima de Mattos plays for Diss Town F.C. in 2004."], "answer": ["Bobby Mayes"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 369, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Ifeoma Mabel Onyemelukwe attended University of Nigeria, who also attended University of Nigeria during the same time period?", "facts": ["Ifeoma Mabel Onyemelukwe attended University of Nigeria from 1972 to 1976.", "William Boone attended University of Nigeria from February 10, 1987 to November 10, 1987.", "Sidney Hemming attended University of Nigeria in October, 1982.", "Alice T. Schafer attended University of Nigeria from 1988 to 1989.", "Mads Tofte works for University of Nigeria from 1989 to 1990.", "Mary Odili attended University of Nigeria from 1972 to 1976.", "Peter DeFazio attended University of Nigeria from July, 1977 to November, 1987.", "Jaime Herrera Beutler attended University of Nigeria in December, 1988.", "Mark Anthony Smith attended University of Nigeria from November, 1988 to August, 1990.", "Sohee Park attended University of Nigeria in July, 1983."], "answer": ["Mary Odili"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 370, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Bracey Wright was playing for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka, who was also playing for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka during the identical time period?", "facts": ["William Maxwell plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka in June, 2017.", "Dominic Waters plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka from 2017 to 2018.", "Colton Iverson plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka from 2015 to 2016.", "Dennis Cagara plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka in 2017.", "Joe McBride plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka from November, 2017 to April, 2018.", "Rico Hill plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka in May 9, 2017.", "Fabrizio Lorieri plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka in December, 2017.", "Peter Johnson plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka from March 9, 2018 to August 10, 2018.", "Bracey Wright plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka from 2015 to 2016.", "Andy White plays for P\u0131nar Kar\u015f\u0131yaka from February, 2018 to December, 2018."], "answer": ["Colton Iverson"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 371, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Haley Cavinder attended California State University, Fresno, who also attended California State University, Fresno during the same time period?", "facts": ["Payson D. Sheets works for California State University, Fresno from 1972 to 1974.", "David Kherdian works for California State University, Fresno from 1968 to 1970.", "Paul George attended California State University, Fresno from 2008 to 2010.", "Robert Upshaw attended California State University, Fresno from 2012 to 2013.", "Herbert S. Scott attended California State University, Fresno in 1964.", "Joseph N. Crowley attended California State University, Fresno in 1963.", "Eric H. Cline works for California State University, Fresno from January, 1992 to May, 1994.", "Daniel Levitin attended California State University, Fresno from 1978 to 1979.", "Hanna Cavinder attended California State University, Fresno from 2019 to 2022.", "Haley Cavinder attended California State University, Fresno from 2019 to 2022.", "Ray Courtright works for California State University, Fresno in 1946.", "Jim Costa attended California State University, Fresno in 1974.", "Braeden Anderson attended California State University, Fresno from 2011 to 2015."], "answer": ["Hanna Cavinder"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 372, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Jamie Doyle was playing for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C., who was also playing for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Russell Robinson plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from June 9, 1999 to June 11, 2007.", "Mate \u0160estan plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from November 2, 2004 to December 5, 2004.", "Kris Bright plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from May 22, 2007 to September 24, 2009.", "Marvin Andrews plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from 2011 to 2012.", "Gianfranco Labarthe plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. in July, 2007.", "Jamie Doyle plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from 2011 to 2012.", "Chic Charnley plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from 1999 to 2002.", "Paulo Jorge Vieira Alves plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. in September 11, 2010.", "Jawad El Hajri plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from January, 2000 to December, 2009.", "Juan Ignacio S\u00e1nchez plays for Kirkintilloch Rob Roy F.C. from June, 2001 to May, 2003."], "answer": ["Marvin Andrews"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 373, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Heidi Allen was a member of Change UK, who was also a member of Change UK during the same time span?", "facts": ["Fraser Anning is a member of the Change UK in December, 2019.", "Mimi Jakobsen is a member of the Change UK in November, 2019.", "Albert Robinson is a member of the Change UK in July 23, 2019.", "Avelino M\u00e9ndez Rangel is a member of the Change UK in July 15, 2019.", "Alain Richard is a member of the Change UK in November 13, 2019.", "J\u00e9r\u00f4me Rivi\u00e8re is a member of the Change UK in June 16, 2019.", "Heidi Allen is a member of the Change UK from February 20, 2019 to June 4, 2019.", "Sarah Wollaston is a member of the Change UK from February 20, 2019 to June 4, 2019.", "Ella Reeve Bloor is a member of the Change UK in August 22, 2019.", "Anna Soubry is a member of the Change UK in February 20, 2019."], "answer": ["Sarah Wollaston"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 374, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Edson Rolando Silva Sousa was playing for FC Solothurn, who was also playing for FC Solothurn during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Christ Bongo plays for FC Solothurn from 2000 to 2001.", "Diego Cabrera plays for FC Solothurn in 2010.", "Joseph Afusi plays for FC Solothurn in 2008.", "Talles Cunha plays for FC Solothurn in June, 2010.", "Edson Rolando Silva Sousa plays for FC Solothurn from 2000 to 2001.", "Robert Archibald plays for FC Solothurn from January, 2006 to November, 2012.", "Paulo Vogt plays for FC Solothurn from 2010 to 2012.", "Owusu Benson plays for FC Solothurn in 1995.", "Ante Vuku\u0161i\u0107 plays for FC Solothurn from 2006 to 2011.", "Dmitry Kozlov plays for FC Solothurn from 2007 to 2008."], "answer": ["Christ Bongo"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 375, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Chen Yun was holding the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party, who also held the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Rahm Emanuel holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party in 1967.", "Zhu De holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from September 28, 1956 to August 1, 1966.", "Joseph Asajir\u014d Satowaki holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party in July, 1981.", "Chen Yun holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from September 28, 1956 to August 1, 1966.", "Hua Guofeng holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from April 7, 1976 to October 7, 1976.", "Zhou Enlai holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from September 28, 1956 to August 1, 1966.", "Li Xiannian holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from July, 1977 to September, 1982.", "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 Boussen holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from October 22, 1969 to February 22, 1982.", "Thomas Playford holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from November, 1977 to February, 1982.", "Rodrigo Arango Vel\u00e1squez holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from June 3, 1982 to September 4, 1982."], "answer": ["Zhu De", "Zhou Enlai"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 376, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Steve Trittschuh was playing for St. Louis Steamers, who was also playing for St. Louis Steamers during the same time period?", "facts": ["Stanton Kidd plays for St. Louis Steamers from February 18, 1982 to June 19, 1982.", "Godfrey Ingram plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1987 to 1988.", "Pasquale Luiso plays for St. Louis Steamers in June 15, 1982.", "Jean Carlos plays for St. Louis Steamers in December 21, 1982.", "Steve Trittschuh plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1987 to 1988.", "Ivan Dragi\u010devi\u0107 plays for St. Louis Steamers in June, 1986.", "Y\u0131lmaz Orhan plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1980 to 1981.", "John Bain plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1987 to 1988.", "Marcos Tamandar\u00e9 plays for St. Louis Steamers in January, 1986.", "Adriano Gabiru plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1985 to 1986."], "answer": ["Godfrey Ingram", "John Bain"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 377, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Westfield Montgomery was owned by Westfield Corporation, who was also owned by Westfield Corporation during the same time span?", "facts": ["Entombment of Christ is owned by Westfield Corporation in September 26, 2018.", "The Geographer is owned by Westfield Corporation in December, 2018.", "Lise with a Parasol is owned by Westfield Corporation in July, 2018.", "Norwegian Majesty is owned by Westfield Corporation in August 21, 2018.", "Northern Counties Committee is owned by Westfield Corporation in July 10, 2018.", "Westfield Montgomery is owned by Westfield Corporation from 2014 to June, 2018.", "Madame Monet wearing a kimono is owned by Westfield Corporation in December 6, 2018.", "Matchbox is owned by Westfield Corporation in August, 2018.", "Westfield Wheaton is owned by Westfield Corporation from 2014 to June, 2018.", "Bulb Fields is owned by Westfield Corporation in August, 2018."], "answer": ["Westfield Wheaton"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 378, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While VELUX was owned by Connie Hedegaard, who was also owned by Connie Hedegaard during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Te Fare is owned by Connie Hedegaard from May, 2021 to January, 2022.", "Lady Writing a Letter with her Maid is owned by Connie Hedegaard in May 4, 2021.", "Portrait of Niccol\u00f2 Vitelli is owned by Connie Hedegaard in July 18, 2017.", "Lilies of the Valley is owned by Connie Hedegaard from March, 2018 to October, 2018.", "Basket of Flowers is owned by Connie Hedegaard in 2017.", "TF1 is owned by Connie Hedegaard from December 16, 2019 to October 22, 2022.", "Aarhus University is owned by Connie Hedegaard from December 13, 2017 to February 1, 2023.", "VELUX is owned by Connie Hedegaard in March 20, 2023.", "Scandinavian is owned by Connie Hedegaard from April, 2021 to June, 2022.", "Villum Foundation is owned by Connie Hedegaard in March 20, 2023."], "answer": ["Villum Foundation"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 379, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While John Bain was playing for St. Louis Steamers, who was also playing for St. Louis Steamers during the same time span?", "facts": ["Y\u0131lmaz Orhan plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1980 to 1981.", "Ivan Peri\u0161i\u0107 plays for St. Louis Steamers in August 27, 1980.", "Nashat Akram plays for St. Louis Steamers in 1985.", "John Bain plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1987 to 1988.", "Milton Cruz plays for St. Louis Steamers in 1983.", "Steve Trittschuh plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1987 to 1988.", "Gary Alexander plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1981 to 1984.", "Magnus Okuonghae plays for St. Louis Steamers in July, 1982.", "Godfrey Ingram plays for St. Louis Steamers from 1987 to 1988.", "Clinton Morrison plays for St. Louis Steamers in 1983."], "answer": ["Godfrey Ingram", "Steve Trittschuh"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 380, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Stefano Dall'Acqua was playing for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio, who was also playing for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio at the same time?", "facts": ["Filippo Cristante plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio from 1993 to 1994.", "Alessandro Cesca plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio from 1999 to 2001.", "Rangelo Janga plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio in July 3, 1993.", "Sean Hessey plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio from 2002 to 2006.", "Pere Tarradellas i C\u00e1mara plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio in January, 1997.", "Filipe Falardo plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio in July 26, 1993.", "Hern\u00e1n Rodrigo L\u00f3pez plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio in 1996.", "Alessandro Moro plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio from 2011 to 2012.", "Javier Dorado plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio from November 15, 1994 to May 20, 2010.", "Stefano Dall'Acqua plays for A.S.D. Sacilese Calcio from 2011 to 2012."], "answer": ["Alessandro Moro"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 381, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Khalilou Fadiga was playing for K.F.C. Lommel S.K., who was also playing for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Carl Hoefkens plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from 2001 to 2003.", "Khalilou Fadiga plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from 1995 to 1997.", "Horacio Chiorazzo plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. in 1987.", "Jo\u00e3o Paulo plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. in October 14, 2003.", "Hakan Bayraktar plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from 1995 to 1997.", "Marc Nygaard plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from 2002 to 2003.", "Ibrahim Tankary plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from 2000 to 2003.", "Patrick Goots plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from 1986 to 1988.", "Robbie Painter plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. from August 17, 2001 to August 28, 2001.", "Kimmo Tarkkio plays for K.F.C. Lommel S.K. in 2003."], "answer": ["Hakan Bayraktar"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 382, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Christophe Aubanel was playing for US Marseille Endoume, who was also playing for US Marseille Endoume during the same time period?", "facts": ["Iain Turner plays for US Marseille Endoume from 1997 to 2003.", "Denys Sokolovskyi plays for US Marseille Endoume in April 1, 2005.", "Jacques R\u00e9my plays for US Marseille Endoume from 1995 to 1996.", "Cristian Zaccardo plays for US Marseille Endoume from 2000 to 2006.", "Christophe Aubanel plays for US Marseille Endoume from 1995 to 1996.", "Mineiro plays for US Marseille Endoume from 2001 to 2005.", "S\u00e9bastien Sansoni plays for US Marseille Endoume from 2000 to 2001.", "Dramane Traor\u00e9 plays for US Marseille Endoume in April, 1999.", "Rapha\u00ebl Romey plays for US Marseille Endoume from 2006 to 2007.", "Luk\u00e1\u0161 Droppa plays for US Marseille Endoume from March, 1999 to October, 2006."], "answer": ["Jacques R\u00e9my"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 383, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Mirza Golubica was playing for HNK Suhopolje, who was also playing for HNK Suhopolje concurrently?", "facts": ["Nikolas Ledgerwood plays for HNK Suhopolje from May, 2007 to June, 2007.", "Viktor Dvirnyk plays for HNK Suhopolje from 1997 to 1999.", "Mirza Golubica plays for HNK Suhopolje from 1997 to 1999.", "Ally Graham plays for HNK Suhopolje in 2005.", "Jos\u00e9 J\u00fanior plays for HNK Suhopolje from 2000 to 2001.", "Josip Fu\u010dek plays for HNK Suhopolje in 2007.", "Da Silva plays for HNK Suhopolje in May, 2000.", "Russell Osman plays for HNK Suhopolje in July 11, 2006.", "Mikhail Afanasyev plays for HNK Suhopolje in May, 2002.", "Leonardo Medina plays for HNK Suhopolje in 2003."], "answer": ["Viktor Dvirnyk"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 384, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Kendall Fletcher was playing for Melbourne Victory FC W-League, who was also playing for Melbourne Victory FC W-League during the same time span?", "facts": ["Natasha Dowie plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League in 2015.", "Antonio Manicone plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League in September, 2014.", "Iorlando Pereira Marques Filho plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League from January 22, 2014 to May 22, 2015.", "Dario Bodru\u0161i\u0107 plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League in January, 2009.", "Jodie Taylor plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League from 2010 to 2012.", "Brown Ideye plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League from 2013 to 2014.", "Kendall Fletcher plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League from 2010 to 2012.", "Dimitris Konstantopoulos plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League from August 23, 2015 to August 24, 2015.", "Julianne Sitch plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League in 2009.", "Melori Bigvava plays for Melbourne Victory FC W-League in 2015."], "answer": ["Jodie Taylor"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 385, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While George Baker was a member of Senate Liberal Caucus, who was also a member of Senate Liberal Caucus during the same time period?", "facts": ["Liu Yi-te is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in May 23, 2014.", "George Baker is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 29, 2014.", "Bernard Weatherill is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in August 17, 2014.", "Vladimir Potapov is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in July 13, 2014.", "Karo Zakarian is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in August, 2014.", "Art Eggleton is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 29, 2014.", "Edward Gierek is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in September 4, 2014.", "Arturo Scotto is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in August 21, 2014.", "Catherine Callbeck is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 29, 2014.", "Klaus Fuchs is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in December 19, 2014."], "answer": ["Art Eggleton", "Catherine Callbeck"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 386, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Ersin Veli was playing for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK, who was also playing for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Maksim Shatskikh plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from March, 2003 to August, 2003.", "Ersin Veli plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2000 to 2001.", "Ahmed Mubarak plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2006 to 2008.", "F\u0131rat Akkoyun plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2004 to 2005.", "Ahmet Aras plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2011 to 2013.", "Hasan Vezir plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 1998 to 1999.", "Orkun U\u015fak plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2000 to 2001.", "G\u00f6khan Bozkaya plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2000 to 2001.", "Daniel Sturridge plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK in September, 1999.", "Konstantin Kaynov plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK in July 12, 2008."], "answer": ["G\u00f6khan Bozkaya", "Orkun U\u015fak"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 387, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While County Hall was owned by Greater London Council, who was also owned by Greater London Council during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Diane Abbott works for Greater London Council from 1985 to 1986.", "Girl with a Pearl Earring is owned by Greater London Council in November 19, 1986.", "Mosaic is owned by Greater London Council in August, 1986.", "Maersk is owned by Greater London Council in November 6, 1986.", "Peter Frank Stott works for Greater London Council from 1965 to 1973.", "A Matador is owned by Greater London Council in November, 1986.", "County Hall is owned by Greater London Council from April 1, 1965 to March 31, 1986.", "Madame Monet wearing a kimono is owned by Greater London Council in April 24, 1986.", "Venus and Mars is owned by Greater London Council in October, 1986.", "Woolwich Ferry is owned by Greater London Council from April 1, 1965 to March 31, 1986."], "answer": ["Woolwich Ferry"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 388, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Matteo Teoldi was playing for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D., who was also playing for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Neil Tarrant plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from June, 2003 to August, 2003.", "Aldo Dolcetti plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from 2001 to 2002.", "Aymen Abdennour plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. in 2008.", "Dave Pearce plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from September, 2006 to June, 2008.", "Pi\u00e1 plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from 2014 to 2015.", "Matteo Teoldi plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from 2014 to 2015.", "Fikru-Teferra Lemessa plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. in 2009.", "Andr\u00e9s Garrone plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from 2007 to 2009.", "Alessandro Belleri plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from 2010 to 2011.", "Atiba Hutchinson plays for U.S. Darfo Boario S.S.D. from July 17, 2008 to April 24, 2012."], "answer": ["Pi\u00e1"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 389, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Iman Mobali was playing for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C., who was also playing for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. concurrently?", "facts": ["Stelios Kritikos plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. from November 7, 2016 to December 26, 2016.", "Sergi Moreno plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. from May 12, 2016 to October 16, 2016.", "Iman Mobali plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. from 2013 to 2014.", "Hossein Kaebi plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. from 2013 to 2014.", "Gary Mills plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. in April 9, 2016.", "Eduardo Ferreira plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. in 2015.", "David Oldfield plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. in December, 2016.", "Dillon Sheppard plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. in August 11, 2015.", "Wayne Gray plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. in June 6, 2016.", "Fellipe Bertoldo plays for Esteghlal Khuzestan F.C. in 2016."], "answer": ["Hossein Kaebi"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 390, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Catherine Callbeck was a member of Senate Liberal Caucus, who was also a member of Senate Liberal Caucus within the same time interval?", "facts": ["Kensaku Morita is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in September 14, 2014.", "George Baker is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 29, 2014.", "Herbert Hudd is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in September, 2014.", "Laurent Schwartz is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in May 20, 2014.", "Nikita Khrushchev is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in November, 2014.", "Kim Il-sung is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in February 3, 2014.", "Catherine Callbeck is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 29, 2014.", "Art Eggleton is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 29, 2014.", "John Darley is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in January 2, 2014.", "Louka Katseli is a member of the Senate Liberal Caucus in April, 2014."], "answer": ["Art Eggleton", "George Baker"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 391, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Luigi Fantappi\u00e8 attended Scuola Normale Superiore, who also attended Scuola Normale Superiore simultaneously?", "facts": ["Onorato Nicoletti attended Scuola Normale Superiore in 1894.", "Federico Cafiero works for Scuola Normale Superiore from 1956 to 1959.", "Mauro Picone attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1904 to 1907.", "Maria Colombo attended Scuola Normale Superiore from October, 2007 to September, 2015.", "Guido Fubini attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1896 to 1900.", "Giovanni Sansone attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1906 to 1910.", "Paolo Emilio Taviani attended Scuola Normale Superiore in 1936.", "Enrico Fermi attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1918 to 1922.", "Annalisa Pastore works for Scuola Normale Superiore in 2018.", "Federigo Enriques attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1887 to 1891.", "Gianfranco Contini works for Scuola Normale Superiore from 1975 to 1987.", "Luigi Fantappi\u00e8 attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1918 to 1922.", "Paolo Piccione attended Scuola Normale Superiore in 2001.", "Wilhelm Blaschke attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1908 to 1909.", "Mario Pieri attended Scuola Normale Superiore from 1881 to 1884.", "Augusto Sagnotti works for Scuola Normale Superiore in 2005."], "answer": ["Enrico Fermi"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 392, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Rory May was playing for Stourport Swifts F.C., who was also playing for Stourport Swifts F.C. at the same time?", "facts": ["Manuel Jos\u00e9 Vieira plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. from 2008 to 2009.", "Jean Harbor plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. in October 7, 2008.", "Des Lyttle plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. in 2003.", "Dennis Pearce plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. in 2011.", "Branko \u0160egota plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. in March 2, 2004.", "Jae Martin plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. from 2005 to 2006.", "Jorge Barbosa de Lima plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. from January 19, 2008 to May 27, 2010.", "Duane Darby plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. from 2008 to 2009.", "Michael Silberbauer plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. from February 19, 2011 to February 27, 2011.", "Rory May plays for Stourport Swifts F.C. from 2005 to 2006."], "answer": ["Jae Martin"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 393, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Moshe Dayan was a member of Mapai, who was also a member of Mapai during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Jacques Boutault is a member of the Mapai in February 15, 1952.", "Shimon Peres is a member of the Mapai from 1959 to 1965.", "Moshe Dayan is a member of the Mapai from 1959 to 1965.", "Eiki Berg is a member of the Mapai in December, 1955.", "S\u00e1ndor Fazekas is a member of the Mapai in 1957.", "David Petel is a member of the Mapai from 1959 to 1965.", "Marc Tarabella is a member of the Mapai in 1954.", "Uri Sebag is a member of the Mapai in 1951.", "Jan Ruml is a member of the Mapai in September 26, 1953.", "Dina Boluarte is a member of the Mapai from November, 1956 to June, 1958."], "answer": ["David Petel", "Shimon Peres"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 394, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Silvia Paracchini attended University of Pavia, who also attended University of Pavia during the same time span?", "facts": ["Salvatore Pincherle works for University of Pavia from 1878 to 1880.", "Enrico Bompiani works for University of Pavia from 1913 to 1915.", "Silvia Paracchini attended University of Pavia from 1993 to 1998.", "Luisa Banti works for University of Pavia from 1948 to 1953.", "Willibald Pirckheimer attended University of Pavia from 1488 to 1495.", "Eugenio Beltrami attended University of Pavia from 1853 to 1856.", "Tommaso Boggio works for University of Pavia from 1903 to 1905.", "Gianfranco Contini attended University of Pavia in 1933.", "Alfio Quarteroni attended University of Pavia from November 1, 1975 to June 24, 1979.", "Cecilia Lunardini attended University of Pavia from 1993 to 1998.", "Carlo Francesco Gabba attended University of Pavia in 1858."], "answer": ["Cecilia Lunardini"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 395, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While HGTV was owned by Discovery Inc., who was also owned by Discovery Inc. simultaneously?", "facts": ["Rover is owned by Discovery Inc. in January 23, 2017.", "HuffPost is owned by Discovery Inc. from March, 2015 to July, 2018.", "Hickory Hill is owned by Discovery Inc. from August, 2017 to December, 2017.", "Primrose Hill Tunnel is owned by Discovery Inc. from July 6, 2013 to August 17, 2013.", "Marriage Contract and Country Dancing is owned by Discovery Inc. in August, 2014.", "HGTV is owned by Discovery Inc. from 2019 to 2022.", "TVNorge is owned by Discovery Inc. in 2013.", "Really is owned by Discovery Inc. from 2019 to 2022.", "Warminster Branch is owned by Discovery Inc. in April 13, 2014.", "Gulskogen Station is owned by Discovery Inc. in September, 2015."], "answer": ["Really"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 396, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Zhu De was holding the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party, who also held the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party at the same time?", "facts": ["Jos\u00e9 Blanco L\u00f3pez holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party in 1979.", "Li Xiannian holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from July, 1977 to September, 1982.", "Gregory King holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from 1978 to 1980.", "Zhou Enlai holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from September 28, 1956 to August 1, 1966.", "Zhu De holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from September 28, 1956 to August 1, 1966.", "Troiano Acquaviva d'Aragona holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from January 11, 1975 to March 21, 1982.", "Chen Yun holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from September 28, 1956 to August 1, 1966.", "John Edgar McCafferty holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party in 1979.", "Hua Guofeng holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from April 7, 1976 to October 7, 1976.", "Johann von Eych holds the position of Vice Chairman of the Chinese Communist Party in April 11, 1981."], "answer": ["Chen Yun", "Zhou Enlai"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 397, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Mauricio Ver\u00f3n was playing for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario, who was also playing for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Fabricio Lenci plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 2007 to 2008.", "Silvio Carrario plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 1993 to 1994.", "Jorge Drovandi plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario in 2013.", "Pablo V\u00e1zquez plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 2005 to 2006.", "Iv\u00e1n Pail\u00f3s plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario in 2012.", "Eduardo Bustos Montoya plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 2010 to 2011.", "Juli\u00e1n Maidana plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario in 2009.", "Andr\u00e9s Garrone plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 1998 to 1999.", "Cristian Jeandet plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 2000 to 2001.", "Mauricio Ver\u00f3n plays for Central C\u00f3rdoba de Rosario from 2005 to 2006."], "answer": ["Pablo V\u00e1zquez"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 398, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Technical University of Denmark was owned by Tobias Colding, who was also owned by Tobias Colding at the same time?", "facts": ["A Landscape with a Ruined Castle and a Church is owned by Tobias Colding in February, 2021.", "JP/Politikens Hus is owned by Tobias Colding in October 20, 2021.", "DTU Science Park is owned by Tobias Colding from December 1, 2017 to January 1, 2021.", "Jupiter and Antiope is owned by Tobias Colding in May 24, 2021.", "Technical University of Denmark is owned by Tobias Colding from December 1, 2017 to January 1, 2021.", "Rauma Line is owned by Tobias Colding in March 11, 2021.", "SS Imperator is owned by Tobias Colding in May 23, 2017.", "Arbejdernes Landsbank is owned by Tobias Colding in May, 2021.", "Interchange is owned by Tobias Colding in April 21, 2017.", "Entombment of Christ is owned by Tobias Colding in September, 2021."], "answer": ["DTU Science Park"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 399, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Gal Mekel was playing for Pallacanestro Treviso, who was also playing for Pallacanestro Treviso simultaneously?", "facts": ["Bo\u0161tjan Nachbar plays for Pallacanestro Treviso from 2000 to 2002.", "Pops Mensah-Bonsu plays for Pallacanestro Treviso from 2007 to 2008.", "Maalik Wayns plays for Pallacanestro Treviso from 2018 to January, 2019.", "Sani Be\u010dirovi\u0107 plays for Pallacanestro Treviso from 2011 to 2012.", "Nastja \u010ceh plays for Pallacanestro Treviso from August 10, 2015 to February 10, 2016.", "Gal Mekel plays for Pallacanestro Treviso from 2011 to 2012.", "Kandia Traor\u00e9 plays for Pallacanestro Treviso in March, 2005.", "J\u00e9r\u00e9my Mathieu plays for Pallacanestro Treviso in October 18, 2000.", "Stefano Pettinari plays for Pallacanestro Treviso in October, 2003.", "Ademola Okulaja plays for Pallacanestro Treviso in 2004."], "answer": ["Sani Be\u010dirovi\u0107"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 400, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While George O'Boyle was playing for Carnoustie Panmure F.C., who was also playing for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. concurrently?", "facts": ["Giorgos Katsikas plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. from 2011 to 2012.", "M\u00e1rcio Giovanini plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. from April 11, 2013 to September 16, 2013.", "Vladimir Dimitrovski plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. in 2012.", "Serges D\u00e9bl\u00e9 plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. in December 19, 2012.", "George O'Boyle plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. from 2006 to 2008.", "Gary Bollan plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. from 2006 to 2008.", "Rafael Chor\u00e3o plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. in December, 2014.", "Stefan Moore plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. from March 20, 2011 to December 27, 2012.", "Yusuf Kurtulu\u015f plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. from 2010 to 2014.", "Garry Kenneth plays for Carnoustie Panmure F.C. in 2014."], "answer": ["Gary Bollan"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 401, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Justin Hamilton was playing for Brooklyn Nets, who was also playing for Brooklyn Nets concurrently?", "facts": ["Damone Brown plays for Brooklyn Nets in 2003.", "Bo\u0161tjan Nachbar plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2006 to 2008.", "Justin Hamilton plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2016 to 2017.", "J\u00e9r\u00f4me Mo\u00efso plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2004 to 2005.", "Alan Anderson plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2013 to 2015.", "Earl Boykins plays for Brooklyn Nets in 1999.", "Sean Kilpatrick plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2016 to 2017.", "Jerome Jordan plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2014 to 2015.", "Luis Scola plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2016 to 2017.", "Sasha Vuja\u010di\u0107 plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2010 to 2011.", "Andre Emmett plays for Brooklyn Nets in 2012."], "answer": ["Sean Kilpatrick", "Luis Scola"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 402, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Selkent was owned by Macquarie Group, who was also owned by Macquarie Group during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Skillsoft is owned by Macquarie Group in April 25, 2006.", "Windsor & Eton Central railway station is owned by Macquarie Group in January, 2006.", "Digital Video Interactive is owned by Macquarie Group in December 4, 2010.", "Fifteenth Anniversary is owned by Macquarie Group in May 16, 2006.", "Joseph and Potiphar's Wife is owned by Macquarie Group in May 27, 2006.", "Numedal Line is owned by Macquarie Group in March 4, 2006.", "East London is owned by Macquarie Group from June 23, 2006 to October 15, 2010.", "Gulskogen Station is owned by Macquarie Group in January 26, 2006.", "Selkent is owned by Macquarie Group from June 23, 2006 to October 15, 2010.", "Scandinavian is owned by Macquarie Group in May, 2006."], "answer": ["East London"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 403, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Jyrki Katainen was holding the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship, who also held the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship during the same time period?", "facts": ["Jyrki Katainen holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from November 1, 2014 to November 30, 2019.", "Gwen Graham holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship in February, 2001.", "B\u00f6rje H\u00f6rnlund holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from May, 2002 to March, 2008.", "Tim Mahoney holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from 2007 to 2012.", "Bernard Heywood holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship in July, 2012.", "G\u00fcnter Verheugen holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from November 22, 2004 to February 9, 2010.", "El\u017cbieta Bie\u0144kowska holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from November 1, 2014 to November 30, 2019.", "Erkki Liikanen holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from September 17, 1999 to July 11, 2004.", "Youhanna Golta holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship in November, 2005.", "Natalino Pescarolo holds the position of European Commissioner for Industry and Entrepreneurship from March, 2000 to August, 2004."], "answer": ["El\u017cbieta Bie\u0144kowska"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 404, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Lubom\u00edr Blaha was playing for SC Ostbahn XI, who was also playing for SC Ostbahn XI during the same time span?", "facts": ["Cl\u00e1udio Mendes Prates plays for SC Ostbahn XI in February, 2008.", "Danny Wring plays for SC Ostbahn XI in 2008.", "Antonio Nocerino plays for SC Ostbahn XI in June 28, 2008.", "Lubom\u00edr Blaha plays for SC Ostbahn XI from 2010 to 2011.", "Almir Memi\u0107 plays for SC Ostbahn XI from April, 2008 to December, 2008.", "Ralph Black plays for SC Ostbahn XI in 2009.", "Aleksandar Stanisavljevi\u0107 plays for SC Ostbahn XI from 2010 to 2011.", "Aleksei Savelyev plays for SC Ostbahn XI from February 16, 2008 to September 22, 2008.", "Jodie Taylor plays for SC Ostbahn XI in 2009.", "Ferenc Horv\u00e1th plays for SC Ostbahn XI from 2008 to 2009."], "answer": ["Aleksandar Stanisavljevi\u0107"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 405, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Jean Ybarnegaray was a member of Democratic and Republican Union, who was also a member of Democratic and Republican Union during the same time period?", "facts": ["Jean Ybarnegaray is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union from 1924 to 1932.", "Pierre Taittinger is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union from 1924 to 1932.", "Nathanael Liminski is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union in 1938.", "Jacques Bardoux is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union from 1938 to 1940.", "Jerzy Buzek is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union from March 9, 1936 to January 22, 1939.", "John Fitzpatrick is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union in March, 1936.", "Alexandr Vondra is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union from May, 1935 to August, 1940.", "Cl\u00e9ment Beaune is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union in January, 1936.", "David Petel is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union in 1937.", "Paul Podolay is a member of the Democratic and Republican Union from July, 1938 to April, 1940."], "answer": ["Pierre Taittinger"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 406, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Shimon Peres was a member of Mapai, who was also a member of Mapai during the same time period?", "facts": ["Uri Sebag is a member of the Mapai in 1951.", "Gernot Erler is a member of the Mapai in 1952.", "Moshe Dayan is a member of the Mapai from 1959 to 1965.", "Maja Gojkovi\u0107 is a member of the Mapai from 1954 to 1957.", "Thomas McCallum is a member of the Mapai from July 27, 1953 to May 28, 1955.", "David Petel is a member of the Mapai from 1959 to 1965.", "Frunze Dovlatyan is a member of the Mapai from 1956 to 1958.", "Jesse Ventura is a member of the Mapai in September, 1954.", "Shimon Peres is a member of the Mapai from 1959 to 1965.", "Heinrich August Winkler is a member of the Mapai in 1952."], "answer": ["David Petel", "Moshe Dayan"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 407, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Mikhail Kasyanov was a member of People's Freedom Party, who was also a member of People's Freedom Party during the same time period?", "facts": ["Pierre Laval is a member of the People's Freedom Party in March 3, 2012.", "Martha Patricia Ram\u00edrez Lucero is a member of the People's Freedom Party in March, 2012.", "Jody Wilson-Raybould is a member of the People's Freedom Party in September 8, 2012.", "Valeriu Stoica is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 11, 2012.", "Kamel Morjane is a member of the People's Freedom Party in January, 2012.", "Jeff Van Drew is a member of the People's Freedom Party in March 16, 2012.", "Ilya Yashin is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 16, 2012.", "Boris Nemtsov is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 16, 2012.", "Helmut Schmidt is a member of the People's Freedom Party in August, 2012.", "Mikhail Kasyanov is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 16, 2012."], "answer": ["Ilya Yashin", "Boris Nemtsov"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 408, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Simone Calori was playing for A.C. Giacomense, who was also playing for A.C. Giacomense concurrently?", "facts": ["Hugo Colace plays for A.C. Giacomense from 2010 to 2011.", "Jos\u00e9 Espinal plays for A.C. Giacomense in 2010.", "Giovanni Savarese plays for A.C. Giacomense from March 5, 2011 to December 10, 2011.", "Simone Calori plays for A.C. Giacomense from 2012 to 2013.", "Andrey Galabinov plays for A.C. Giacomense in 2009.", "Rufino Segovia del Burgo plays for A.C. Giacomense in 2009.", "Jos\u00e9 Manuel Colmenero Crespo plays for A.C. Giacomense in 2010.", "Boni Ginzburg plays for A.C. Giacomense in December, 2009.", "Massimiliano Varricchio plays for A.C. Giacomense from 2012 to 2013.", "Richard Offiong plays for A.C. Giacomense in August 20, 2011."], "answer": ["Massimiliano Varricchio"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 409, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Carles Campuzano was a member of Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya, who was also a member of Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya during the same time period?", "facts": ["Aleksandra Dulkiewicz is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in November, 2020.", "Iveta Radi\u010dov\u00e1 is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in December, 2020.", "Mukhriz Mahathir is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in January, 2020.", "Abderrahmane Youssoufi is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in July 10, 2020.", "Marietta Stepanyants is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in December 7, 2020.", "Jordi Xucl\u00e0 is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 27, 2020.", "Marta Pascal i Capdevila is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 27, 2020.", "Carles Campuzano is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 27, 2020.", "Kathleen Rice is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in July 14, 2020.", "Ratinho J\u00fanior is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in August 15, 2020."], "answer": ["Jordi Xucl\u00e0", "Marta Pascal i Capdevila"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 410, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Ilya Yashin was a member of People's Freedom Party, who was also a member of People's Freedom Party simultaneously?", "facts": ["P\u00e1l Mal\u00e9ter is a member of the People's Freedom Party in November 13, 2012.", "Kaido Kama is a member of the People's Freedom Party in August, 2012.", "Ogden R. Reid is a member of the People's Freedom Party in February, 2012.", "Jochen Ott is a member of the People's Freedom Party in September, 2012.", "Whitmell P. Martin is a member of the People's Freedom Party in February, 2012.", "Boris Nemtsov is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 16, 2012.", "Ilya Yashin is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 16, 2012.", "Jesse Ventura is a member of the People's Freedom Party in May 9, 2012.", "Mikhail Kasyanov is a member of the People's Freedom Party in June 16, 2012.", "Serapio Calder\u00f3n is a member of the People's Freedom Party in February, 2012."], "answer": ["Mikhail Kasyanov", "Boris Nemtsov"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 411, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Christian Tiffert was playing for MSV Duisburg II, who was also playing for MSV Duisburg II during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Moacir Alves de Andrade Junior plays for MSV Duisburg II from September 9, 2013 to September 27, 2015.", "John Rowlands plays for MSV Duisburg II in August 12, 2014.", "Oleh Karamushka plays for MSV Duisburg II from April, 2015 to June, 2015.", "Kelvin Jack plays for MSV Duisburg II in 2011.", "Nicky Adler plays for MSV Duisburg II from 2008 to 2010.", "Christian Tiffert plays for MSV Duisburg II from 2008 to 2010.", "Steve Pittman plays for MSV Duisburg II in October 24, 2015.", "Frank Seator plays for MSV Duisburg II from July, 2013 to November, 2013.", "Haluk T\u00fcrkeri plays for MSV Duisburg II in 2011.", "Sascha Dum plays for MSV Duisburg II in 2015."], "answer": ["Nicky Adler"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 412, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Jean-Claude Pagal was playing for Tiko United F.C., who was also playing for Tiko United F.C. simultaneously?", "facts": ["Steve Banks plays for Tiko United F.C. from 2004 to 2006.", "L\u00e9ster Blanco plays for Tiko United F.C. in August, 2004.", "Jean Paul Yontcha plays for Tiko United F.C. from 2001 to 2002.", "John Oster plays for Tiko United F.C. from 2001 to 2006.", "Edik Sadzhaya plays for Tiko United F.C. in 2002.", "Jean-Claude Pagal plays for Tiko United F.C. from 2008 to 2009.", "Tony Battersby plays for Tiko United F.C. in September, 2004.", "Alberto Malusci plays for Tiko United F.C. in June, 2004.", "Alessio Manzoni plays for Tiko United F.C. from May, 2003 to December, 2007.", "Omega Roberts plays for Tiko United F.C. from 2008 to 2009."], "answer": ["Omega Roberts"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 413, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Arif \u015eahin was playing for Arsinspor, who was also playing for Arsinspor during the same time period?", "facts": ["Eliran George plays for Arsinspor in 2015.", "Muhammet \u00d6zdin plays for Arsinspor from 2014 to 2015.", "Guido Gorges plays for Arsinspor from May, 2013 to October, 2015.", "\u0130brahim \u015eahin plays for Arsinspor from 2006 to 2007.", "R\u0131za \u015een plays for Arsinspor from 2006 to 2007.", "Tiberio Guarente plays for Arsinspor in August, 2008.", "Arif \u015eahin plays for Arsinspor from 2006 to 2007.", "Danijel Mili\u010devi\u0107 plays for Arsinspor in 2012.", "Jonathan Brown plays for Arsinspor in June 25, 2014.", "Nadir Benchenaa plays for Arsinspor from 2011 to 2015."], "answer": ["R\u0131za \u015een", "\u0130brahim \u015eahin"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 414, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Amarildo Zela was playing for NK \u010cakovec, who was also playing for NK \u010cakovec at the same time?", "facts": ["Alex Pinardi plays for NK \u010cakovec from February 7, 1992 to April 22, 1993.", "Edixon Perea plays for NK \u010cakovec in 1991.", "Danijel \u0160tefulj plays for NK \u010cakovec in 1991.", "Glenn Helder plays for NK \u010cakovec in January 9, 1997.", "Tvrtko Kale plays for NK \u010cakovec in 1995.", "Amarildo Zela plays for NK \u010cakovec from 2002 to 2003.", "Dario Jertec plays for NK \u010cakovec from 2002 to 2003.", "Dani Rodrigues plays for NK \u010cakovec from 1991 to 1994.", "Winston White plays for NK \u010cakovec from December 4, 1992 to December 25, 1992.", "Ricardo Lucas plays for NK \u010cakovec in March 10, 2001."], "answer": ["Dario Jertec"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 415, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Luis Scola was playing for Brooklyn Nets, who was also playing for Brooklyn Nets during the same time span?", "facts": ["Earl Boykins plays for Brooklyn Nets in 1999.", "Damone Brown plays for Brooklyn Nets in 2003.", "J\u00e9r\u00f4me Mo\u00efso plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2004 to 2005.", "Sasha Vuja\u010di\u0107 plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2010 to 2011.", "Bo\u0161tjan Nachbar plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2006 to 2008.", "Sean Kilpatrick plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2016 to 2017.", "Luis Scola plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2016 to 2017.", "Andre Emmett plays for Brooklyn Nets in 2012.", "Jerome Jordan plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2014 to 2015.", "Justin Hamilton plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2016 to 2017.", "Alan Anderson plays for Brooklyn Nets from 2013 to 2015."], "answer": ["Sean Kilpatrick", "Justin Hamilton"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 416, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Andreja Milutinovi\u0107 was playing for For\u00e7a Lleida CE, who was also playing for For\u00e7a Lleida CE within the same time interval?", "facts": ["\u00c1lex Llorca plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2013 to 2014.", "Gil Vermouth plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in October, 2021.", "Volodymyr Gerun plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2015 to 2016.", "Andreja Milutinovi\u0107 plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2013 to 2014.", "Alejandro Urtasun plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in 2022.", "Serdar Eylik plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in March 8, 2019.", "Osvaldas Matulionis plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2013 to 2014.", "Bo\u017eo Mili\u0107 plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in 2021.", "Dan Antoniuk plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in 2015.", "David St\u0159ihavka plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in June, 2021."], "answer": ["Osvaldas Matulionis", "\u00c1lex Llorca"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 417, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Cory Carr was playing for Maccabi Haifa B.C., who was also playing for Maccabi Haifa B.C. during the same time span?", "facts": ["Jon Moya plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from 2002 to 2009.", "Curtis Obeng plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from November, 2005 to October, 2006.", "Patrizio Billio plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from January 13, 2002 to April 21, 2006.", "Mauricio Isla plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from February 15, 2004 to February 21, 2006.", "Mikel Arteta plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. in January, 2009.", "Carlos Fumo Gon\u00e7alves plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. in August 15, 2005.", "Gal Mekel plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from 2012 to 2013.", "Spencer Dunkley plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from 2002 to 2003.", "Cory Carr plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. from 2012 to 2013.", "Ander Murillo plays for Maccabi Haifa B.C. in November 17, 2009."], "answer": ["Gal Mekel"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 418, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While G\u00f6khan Bozkaya was playing for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK, who was also playing for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK at the same time?", "facts": ["F\u0131rat Akkoyun plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2004 to 2005.", "Iago Falque plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from September, 2013 to November, 2013.", "Hasan Vezir plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 1998 to 1999.", "Jimmy Corbett plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK in September 25, 1999.", "G\u00f6khan Bozkaya plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2000 to 2001.", "Michy Batshuayi plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from July, 2003 to March, 2011.", "Vinny Mukendi plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK in July, 2002.", "Orkun U\u015fak plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2000 to 2001.", "Ahmet Aras plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2011 to 2013.", "Ersin Veli plays for \u00dcsk\u00fcdar Anadolu SK from 2000 to 2001."], "answer": ["Orkun U\u015fak", "Ersin Veli"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 419, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Nijol\u0117 O\u017eelyt\u0117-Vaitiek\u016bnien\u0117 was a member of Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic, who was also a member of Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic at the same time?", "facts": ["Sergey Girinis is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in 1921.", "Nijol\u0117 O\u017eelyt\u0117-Vaitiek\u016bnien\u0117 is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic from 1989 to 1990.", "T\u00f5nis Lukas is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in April 8, 1968.", "Oswald Teichm\u00fcller is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in January, 1978.", "Zigmantas Bal\u010dytis is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic from 1989 to 1990.", "Grant Woods is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic from 1965 to 1969.", "Pancrazio De Pasquale is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic from March, 1969 to October, 1988.", "Anna J\u00falia Don\u00e1th is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in July 1, 1947.", "Elisabetta Gardini is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in 1973.", "Fausto Bertinotti is a member of the Communist Party of the Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic in April, 1987."], "answer": ["Zigmantas Bal\u010dytis"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 420, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Technical University of Denmark was owned by Ole Sigmund, who was also owned by Ole Sigmund during the same time span?", "facts": ["Balmoral Hotel is owned by Ole Sigmund in July 20, 2021.", "Bank of England is owned by Ole Sigmund in March 10, 2021.", "Matchbox is owned by Ole Sigmund in December, 2021.", "Gulskogen Station is owned by Ole Sigmund in January 7, 2021.", "DTU Science Park is owned by Ole Sigmund in January 1, 2021.", "Technical University of Denmark is owned by Ole Sigmund in January 1, 2021.", "H-33 is owned by Ole Sigmund in December, 2021.", "Portrait of Professor Benjamin H. Rand is owned by Ole Sigmund in October 25, 2021.", "Girl with a Pearl Earring is owned by Ole Sigmund in May, 2021.", "The Denial of Saint Peter is owned by Ole Sigmund in October 26, 2021."], "answer": ["DTU Science Park"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 421, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While S\u00e9bastien Mat\u00e9 was playing for Stade Briochin, who was also playing for Stade Briochin concurrently?", "facts": ["Fritz Emeran plays for Stade Briochin in 2000.", "Camille Abily plays for Stade Briochin from 2000 to 2001.", "Maxime Lestienne plays for Stade Briochin in October, 1998.", "Romario Kortzorg plays for Stade Briochin in 1999.", "S\u00e9bastien Mat\u00e9 plays for Stade Briochin from 1996 to 1997.", "Agent Sawu plays for Stade Briochin from August, 1998 to December, 1998.", "Robert Malm plays for Stade Briochin from 1996 to 1997.", "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Veseli plays for Stade Briochin in 1995.", "Henry Gutierrez plays for Stade Briochin from 1992 to 1993.", "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Piquionne plays for Stade Briochin in November, 1992."], "answer": ["Robert Malm"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 422, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Marta Pascal i Capdevila was a member of Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya, who was also a member of Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya during the same time span?", "facts": ["Richard Ball is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in January, 2020.", "Mehmet Alt\u0131nsoy is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in July, 2020.", "Winston Churchill is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in January 15, 2020.", "Anette H\u00fcbinger is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in February, 2020.", "Marta Pascal i Capdevila is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 27, 2020.", "Enrique Monson\u00eds is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in November, 2020.", "Fran\u00e7ois Patriat is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 25, 2020.", "Edward Hawker is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in November 27, 2020.", "Carles Campuzano is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 27, 2020.", "Jordi Xucl\u00e0 is a member of the Partit Nacionalista de Catalunya in June 27, 2020."], "answer": ["Jordi Xucl\u00e0", "Carles Campuzano"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 423, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Eus\u00e9bio was playing for U.F.C.I. Tomar, who was also playing for U.F.C.I. Tomar simultaneously?", "facts": ["Ihor Bendovskyi plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar in 1985.", "Washington Olivera plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from 1997 to 2000.", "Ant\u00f3nio Sim\u00f5es plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from 1977 to 1978.", "Mostafa Gaafar plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from December, 1986 to July, 2000.", "Giorgos Samaras plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar in December, 1981.", "Paulo Figueiredo plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from 1992 to 1993.", "Eus\u00e9bio plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from 1977 to 1978.", "Peter Davenport plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from September 7, 1999 to December 7, 1999.", "Jo\u00e3o Paulo Andrade plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar from 2000 to 2001.", "Mark Watson plays for U.F.C.I. Tomar in 1995."], "answer": ["Ant\u00f3nio Sim\u00f5es"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 424, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Alexander de Savornin Lohman was a member of Free Anti Revolutionary Party, who was also a member of Free Anti Revolutionary Party simultaneously?", "facts": ["Alexander de Savornin Lohman is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party from 1897 to April 16, 1903.", "Neelam Sanjiva Reddy is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in June 10, 1903.", "Peter-Michael Diestel is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in August, 1903.", "Reiner Haseloff is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in September, 1903.", "Jan Elias Nicolaas Schimmelpenninck van der Oye is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party from 1897 to April 16, 1903.", "Istv\u00e1n Tarl\u00f3s is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in May, 1903.", "Patricia Gallerneau is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in October 3, 1903.", "Novruz Mammadov is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in September, 1903.", "Serhi Leshchenko is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in June, 1903.", "Oliver Wittke is a member of the Free Anti Revolutionary Party in June, 1903."], "answer": ["Jan Elias Nicolaas Schimmelpenninck van der Oye"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 425, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While An Hyo-yeon was playing for South Korea national under-23 football team, who was also playing for South Korea national under-23 football team at the same time?", "facts": ["Oh Beom-seok plays for South Korea national under-23 football team in 2006.", "Jonathan Pereira Rodr\u00edguez plays for South Korea national under-23 football team in November 10, 2003.", "Ji Dong-won plays for South Korea national under-23 football team from 2010 to 2012.", "Milton Rodr\u00edguez plays for South Korea national under-23 football team from August 1, 2001 to December 20, 2011.", "Seol Ki-hyeon plays for South Korea national under-23 football team from 1999 to 2000.", "An Hyo-yeon plays for South Korea national under-23 football team from 1999 to 2000.", "Estevan Pel\u00e9\u00e8 plays for South Korea national under-23 football team in March, 2002.", "Yun Suk-young plays for South Korea national under-23 football team from 2010 to 2012.", "Suk Hyun-jun plays for South Korea national under-23 football team in 2011.", "Marcus Feinbier plays for South Korea national under-23 football team in 2005."], "answer": ["Seol Ki-hyeon"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 426, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While \u0130brahim \u015eahin was playing for Arsinspor, who was also playing for Arsinspor concurrently?", "facts": ["Mikel Santamar\u00eda plays for Arsinspor in 2009.", "Bojan Pavlovi\u0107 plays for Arsinspor in March 28, 2012.", "Sa\u0161a Dobri\u0107 plays for Arsinspor in March 2, 2009.", "Alfred Gettins plays for Arsinspor in February 19, 2015.", "Jerome Jordan plays for Arsinspor from November 23, 2014 to November 28, 2015.", "Nemanja Milovanovi\u0107 plays for Arsinspor from 2009 to 2010.", "Arif \u015eahin plays for Arsinspor from 2006 to 2007.", "R\u0131za \u015een plays for Arsinspor from 2006 to 2007.", "Muhammet \u00d6zdin plays for Arsinspor from 2014 to 2015.", "\u0130brahim \u015eahin plays for Arsinspor from 2006 to 2007."], "answer": ["R\u0131za \u015een", "Arif \u015eahin"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 427, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Maciej \u015aliwowski was playing for FC Tirol Innsbruck, who was also playing for FC Tirol Innsbruck during the identical time period?", "facts": ["Maciej \u015aliwowski plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Florian Sturm plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1998 to 2000.", "Ibrahima Sidibe plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck in 2001.", "Mitar Novakovi\u0107 plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from December, 2000 to February, 2001.", "Walter Schachner plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Christian Aflenzer plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck in 1994.", "Edson plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck in 1999.", "Christian Mayrleb plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Andrei Ivanov plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Rados\u0142aw Gilewicz plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1999 to 2002."], "answer": ["Andrei Ivanov", "Christian Mayrleb", "Walter Schachner"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 428, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Osvaldas Matulionis was playing for For\u00e7a Lleida CE, who was also playing for For\u00e7a Lleida CE during the same time span?", "facts": ["Eduard Sobol plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from January 19, 2015 to June 20, 2020.", "James Milner plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from July 7, 2019 to October 12, 2019.", "Simon Grand plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in 2018.", "Alejandro Urtasun plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in 2022.", "Sandro da Silva Mendon\u00e7a plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in June, 2019.", "Volodymyr Gerun plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2015 to 2016.", "Andreja Milutinovi\u0107 plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2013 to 2014.", "Osvaldas Matulionis plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2013 to 2014.", "Fernando Livramento plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE in November, 2022.", "\u00c1lex Llorca plays for For\u00e7a Lleida CE from 2013 to 2014."], "answer": ["\u00c1lex Llorca", "Andreja Milutinovi\u0107"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 429, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Technical University of Denmark was owned by Eva Berneke, who was also owned by Eva Berneke concurrently?", "facts": ["DTU Science Park is owned by Eva Berneke from December 1, 2017 to January 1, 2021.", "Madame Monet wearing a kimono is owned by Eva Berneke in May, 2021.", "Technical University of Denmark is owned by Eva Berneke from December 1, 2017 to January 1, 2021.", "Elizabeth Arden, Inc. is owned by Eva Berneke in April 18, 2017.", "North Stafford Hotel is owned by Eva Berneke in February, 2021.", "MS Gemini is owned by Eva Berneke in July, 2017.", "Montaudran Airport is owned by Eva Berneke in March 23, 2017.", "Portrait of Niccol\u00f2 Vitelli is owned by Eva Berneke in October 25, 2021.", "Portrait of Georges Clemenceau is owned by Eva Berneke in February, 2021.", "ABC Family Worldwide is owned by Eva Berneke in May 16, 2017."], "answer": ["DTU Science Park"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 430, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Nicholas Caglioni was playing for Aglianese Calcio 1923, who was also playing for Aglianese Calcio 1923 simultaneously?", "facts": ["Simone Guerri plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from 2003 to 2004.", "Branimir Petrovi\u0107 plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 in 2002.", "Anthony Charles plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from February 27, 2001 to August 28, 2001.", "Victor Veljko Paunovi\u0107 Ramirez plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 in 2001.", "Riccardo Nardini plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from 2001 to 2002.", "Gianluca Sordo plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from 2003 to 2004.", "Nicholas Caglioni plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from 2003 to 2004.", "Marcus Phillips plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from June, 2001 to March, 2002.", "Simone Basso plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 from 2003 to 2004.", "Hern\u00e1n Rodrigo L\u00f3pez plays for Aglianese Calcio 1923 in October 20, 2001."], "answer": ["Gianluca Sordo", "Simone Basso", "Simone Guerri"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 431, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O1", "question": "While Andrei Ivanov was playing for FC Tirol Innsbruck, who was also playing for FC Tirol Innsbruck during the same time span?", "facts": ["Christian Aflenzer plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck in 1994.", "Andrei Ivanov plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Walter Schachner plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Harry Saputra plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from August, 2002 to December, 2002.", "Christian Mayrleb plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997.", "Charles Gbeke plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 2000 to 2001.", "Rados\u0142aw Gilewicz plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1999 to 2002.", "Florian Sturm plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1998 to 2000.", "Ibrahima Sidibe plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck in 2001.", "Maciej \u015aliwowski plays for FC Tirol Innsbruck from 1996 to 1997."], "answer": ["Maciej \u015aliwowski", "Christian Mayrleb", "Walter Schachner"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 432, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O2", "question": "While Patrick Cabanel attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure, which school was Kathleen Campbell attending at the same time?", "facts": ["Kathleen Campbell attended University of California from 1981 to 1985.", "Patrick Cabanel attended Xavier High School from August, 2004 to September, 2007.", "Kathleen Campbell works for Ames Research Center from 1995 to 1997.", "Patrick Cabanel works for Paul-Val\u00e9ry-Montpellier University from 1985 to 1986.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Trinity University in September 22, 2014.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Georgia Military College from 2006 to 2019.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Birmingham\u2013Southern College from September, 2010 to August, 2019.", "Kathleen Campbell attended University of Washington from 1986 to 1989.", "Patrick Cabanel attended University of Provence - Aix-Marseille I in 1992.", "Kathleen Campbell works for California Academy of Sciences from 1997 to December, 2019.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Sherborne School from September 1, 2002 to October 24, 2016.", "Patrick Cabanel attended Indian Institute of Science, Bengaluru from August 7, 1991 to November 13, 2018.", "Patrick Cabanel attended McCormick Theological Seminary in January, 2002.", "Patrick Cabanel attended Baltimore City College from September, 2006 to April, 2015.", "Patrick Cabanel attended Paris-Sorbonne University - Paris IV in 1982.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Suffolk University from 1995 to 2006.", "Patrick Cabanel works for University Toulouse - Jean Jaur\u00e8s from 1992 to 2015.", "Kathleen Campbell attended University of California, Santa Cruz from 1981 to 1985.", "Patrick Cabanel attended Saint Michael's College in April, 1990.", "Patrick Cabanel attended Oklahoma Baptist University from 2001 to 2015.", "Patrick Cabanel attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure from 1981 to 1985.", "Patrick Cabanel attended National Cheng Kung University from May, 2017 to January, 2019.", "Kathleen Campbell works for University of Auckland in 1997.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Hendrix College from July 3, 2013 to April 19, 2015.", "Kathleen Campbell attended Stanford Law School from 2013 to 2014.", "Patrick Cabanel works for Paris Nanterre University from 1988 to 1992.", "Patrick Cabanel works for \u00c9cole pratique des hautes \u00e9tudes in 2015."], "answer": ["University of California", "University of California, Santa Cruz"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 433, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O2", "question": "While Christopher Celenza was working for American Academy in Rome, which employer did Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez work for during the same time period?", "facts": ["Christopher Celenza works for Georgetown University in 2017.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure from 1974 to 1993.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for Paris-Sorbonne University - Paris IV from 2010 to 2014.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for Institut Fran\u00e7ais d'Arch\u00e9ologie Orientale from February 2, 2003 to April 26, 2009.", "Christopher Celenza works for Johns Hopkins University from 2005 to 2017.", "Christopher Celenza holds the position of associate professor from 2000 to 2004.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for Paris 12 University from 1999 to 2004.", "Christopher Celenza attended University of Hamburg in 2001.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez attended University of Paris 1 Pantheon-Sorbonne in 1973.", "Christopher Celenza holds the position of vice dean in 2015.", "Christopher Celenza works for Michigan State University from 1996 to 2005.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for Warsaw University of Technology in February, 2016.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for McMaster University in 1967.", "Christopher Celenza works for Sapienza University of Rome from November, 1996 to December, 2007.", "Christopher Celenza holds the position of assistant professor from 1996 to 2000.", "Christopher Celenza attended Duke University in 1996.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for University of Orl\u00e9ans from 1993 to 1995.", "Christopher Celenza works for Department of Health and Social Care in September, 1975.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez attended \u00c9cole normale sup\u00e9rieure de jeunes filles from 1966 to 1970.", "Christopher Celenza works for Northwestern University in July, 1985.", "Christopher Celenza attended Monsignor Farrell High School in 1985.", "Christopher Celenza works for Vanderbilt University in October 2, 2001.", "Christopher Celenza works for W9 in 1975.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for University of Rennes 2 \u2013 Upper Brittany from 1995 to 1999.", "Christopher Celenza works for American Academy in Rome from 2010 to 2014.", "Christopher Celenza attended State University of New York at Albany in 1988.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for Steklov Institute of Mathematics from 1996 to 2005.", "Marie-Fran\u00e7oise Baslez works for Paris Nanterre University from 1970 to 1974.", "Christopher Celenza works for West Virginia State University from June 14, 1967 to March 18, 2000.", "Christopher Celenza holds the position of director from July 1, 2010 to June 30, 2014."], "answer": ["Paris-Sorbonne University - Paris IV"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 434, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O2", "question": "While Mark Kac attended Johns Hopkins University, which school was Gustave Choquet attending simultaneously?", "facts": ["Gustave Choquet attended Boston College Law School from January 7, 1966 to May 17, 1983.", "Gustave Choquet works for University of Paris from 1949 to 1984.", "Mark Kac attended William Jewell College from April 14, 1945 to September 24, 1960.", "Gustave Choquet attended Stanford Law School in 1953.", "Mark Kac attended Saint Mary's College in 1968.", "Gustave Choquet attended Sherborne School from 1965 to 1969.", "Gustave Choquet works for \u00c9cole polytechnique from 1960 to 1969.", "Gustave Choquet works for National Center for Scientific Research from 1941 to 1946.", "Gustave Choquet works for French Armed Forces from 1939 to 1940.", "Mark Kac attended Fordham University School of Law from October 19, 1947 to July 28, 1976.", "Mark Kac works for Leiden University from October 4, 1962 to May 31, 1963.", "Gustave Choquet works for Jagiellonian University from 1946 to 1947.", "Mark Kac works for The Rockefeller University from 1961 to 1981.", "Gustave Choquet attended Lyc\u00e9e Saint-Louis from 1933 to 1934.", "Mark Kac works for Cornell University from 1939 to 1961.", "Mark Kac works for University of Southern California from 1981 to 1984.", "Mark Kac attended Winona State University in May, 1957.", "Mark Kac attended Johns Hopkins University from 1938 to 1939.", "Mark Kac attended King Juan Carlos University in February, 1961.", "Mark Kac attended Sorbonne University in 1955.", "Gustave Choquet attended Princeton University from 1938 to 1939.", "Mark Kac attended Indiana University Robert H. McKinney School of Law from 1951 to 1957.", "Mark Kac attended Lviv University from 1931 to 1937.", "Gustave Choquet attended University of Applied Arts Vienna in 1965.", "Gustave Choquet works for Grenoble Alpes University from 1947 to 1949.", "Gustave Choquet attended Semmelweis University in August 16, 1933.", "Mark Kac works for Utrecht University from March 1, 1980 to April 30, 1980.", "Gustave Choquet attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure from 1934 to 1937.", "Mark Kac attended Henry Clay High School in January 26, 1962.", "Gustave Choquet attended Twyford School from May, 1958 to November, 1961.", "Gustave Choquet attended INSEAD in November, 1946."], "answer": ["Princeton University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
{"index": 435, "triple_element": "S2_R1_O2", "question": "While George H. W. Bush attended Yale University, which school was Herman Chernoff attending during the same time span?", "facts": ["George H. W. Bush holds the position of President of the United States from January 20, 1989 to January 20, 1993.", "George H. W. Bush attended Harvard College in March, 1951.", "Herman Chernoff works for Harvard University from 1985 to 1997.", "Herman Chernoff attended University College School from 1954 to 1966.", "Herman Chernoff works for Massachusetts Institute of Technology from 1974 to 1985.", "Herman Chernoff attended National Chiao Tung University in 1968.", "George H. W. Bush attended College of Charleston in 1950.", "Herman Chernoff attended Brown University from 1945 to 1948.", "George H. W. Bush attended Yale University from 1945 to 1948.", "Herman Chernoff works for University of Illinois at Urbana\u2013Champaign from 1949 to 1951.", "Herman Chernoff attended Willamette University College of Law in 1960.", "Herman Chernoff attended Chestnut Hill Academy from June, 1996 to November, 1996.", "Herman Chernoff works for United States Navy from 1943 to 1945.", "Herman Chernoff attended University of Chicago Graduate Library School from 1994 to 1996.", "Herman Chernoff works for University of Chicago from 1948 to 1949.", "Herman Chernoff works for Stanford University from 1951 to 1974.", "Herman Chernoff attended Townsend Harris High School in 1940.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of United States representative from January 3, 1967 to January 3, 1971.", "George H. W. Bush attended Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health in October 15, 1990.", "George H. W. Bush attended Phillips Academy from 1936 to 1942.", "George H. W. Bush attended Katharineum from 1992 to 1995.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of Vice President of the United States from January 20, 1981 to January 20, 1989.", "Herman Chernoff attended Twyford School in 1971.", "George H. W. Bush attended The Bronx High School of Science in June 5, 1963.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of Director of Central Intelligence from January 30, 1976 to January 20, 1977.", "George H. W. Bush attended \u00c9cole nationale d'administration from 1938 to 1941.", "Herman Chernoff attended City College of New York from 1940 to 1943.", "George H. W. Bush attended Gagarin Air Force Academy in 1997.", "George H. W. Bush holds the position of President-elect of the United States from November 8, 1988 to January 20, 1989.", "George H. W. Bush attended Padjadjaran University from January, 1957 to March, 1979.", "Herman Chernoff attended Goethe-Institut in September, 1962."], "answer": ["Brown University"], "reasoning_trace": "The temporal relation between the event in question and the event in context is: equal.\n"}
